<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report pdfFiles="Letters/ATS12" extends="Letters/Base">
    <ReportSection id="letter" title="Preliminary Position of ATSEC">
        <ReportItem id="from">
            <![CDATA[
                Eleni Stroulia<br />
                Vice Dean of Science<br />
                Chair Academic Teaching Staff Evaluation Committee
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="body">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Each year, the Academic Teaching Staff Evaluation Committee (ATSEC) is charged with the responsibility of awarding merit increments to its Academic Teaching Staff, from an increment pool that is currently equal to 1.2 times the number of eligible staff within the Faculty of Science.</p>
                
                <p>As per Article D6 of Schedule D, I am informing you that at its meeting of April 3, {$next_year}, the ATSEC did not support the recommendation of a {getText(RP_CHAIR, FEC_REVIEW, INCREMENT, {$user_id}, 0, 0)} increment made by your Department Chair and instead, is prepared to award an increment of {getText(RP_FEC_TABLE, TABLE, INCREMENT, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}. The Chair {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, CHAIR_POSITION, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}. Under Article D6 of Schedule D this becomes the preliminary position of ATSEC. This decision was based on the following: </p>

                <ul><li>{getText({$report_type}, TABLE, COMMENT, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}</li></ul><br />

                You may wish to consider the following options:
                <ul>
                    <li>I am offering to meet with you during the week of {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)} to discuss your individual case as it was presented before ATSEC. Please email vicedsci@ualberta.ca for an appointment.</li>
                    <li>As per Article D6, you have the right to request reconsideration of the ATSEC’s preliminary decision by informing me, in writing, within 5 working days from the receipt of this letter.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>It is advisable that you consult the Association of Academic Staff of the University of Alberta (AASUA).</p>

                <p>If you have your case reconsidered by ATSEC and they stand by their preliminary decision, you have the right to appeal this decision to the General Appeals Committee (GAC) under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A. A request must be made to the Chair of the GAC (Provost, cc’d to Faculty Relations), in writing, within 10 working days from the receipt of the letter confirming ATSEC’s reconsideration decision.</p>

                <p>If you choose not to appear before ATSEC to present your case or submit documentation in support of your case, the decision will be final and binding. As per Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A, you may not appeal this decision to the GAC.</p>

                <p>Should you have any procedural questions, please contact sciea@ualberta.ca.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="footer">
            <![CDATA[
                Sincerely,<br />
                <br />
                <div class='previewnodisplay'><img src='skins/Signature2.png' style='height: 3em;' /></div>
                <div class='generatenodisplay'><img src='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/skins/Signature.png' style='height: 3em;' /></div>
                <br />
                Eleni Stroulia<br />
                Vice Dean of Science<br />
                Chair of the Academic Teaching Staff Evaluation Committee<br />
                ES/jb
                </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
