<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report pdfFiles="Letters/20" extends="Letters/Base">
    <ReportSection id="letter" title="Right to Appear before FEC - Promotion has not been supported by Department Chair">
        <ReportItem id="from">
            <![CDATA[
                Declan Ali<br />
                Dean of Science
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="body">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This is to inform you that I have received your Department Chair’s recommendation not to support your application for promotion to Professor. The recommendation has been referred to FEC. Under Article A6.17.1 of Schedule A, you have a right to appear before FEC and contest the recommendation.</p>
                
                <p>It is advisable that you consult the Association of Academic Staff University of Alberta (AASUA) for advice.</p>
                
                <p>Please be advised that the date for your case has been scheduled for {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)} in {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, LOCATION, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}.</p>
                
                <p>Should you decide to contest the recommendation, the following information is to be included in your written submission to FEC by {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}:</p>
                <p style='margin-left:1em;'>
                    a) a statement advising FEC whether or not you will be appearing in person before FEC to present a case;<br />
                    b) any material in response to the Chair’s recommendation as communicated to you under Article A5.03.1 of Schedule A, and any other material relevant to the case;<br />
                    c) a list of names of persons who will attend the FEC hearing as your witnesses.
                </p>
                
                <p>At the same time, a copy of this material must be provided to your Department Chair. Materials submitted to the FEC Chair and Department Chair should be submitted electronically, if feasible.</p>
                
                <p>If FEC supports your Department Chair’s recommendation, you have the right to appeal this decision to the General Appeals Committee (GAC) under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A. A request must be made to the Chair of the GAC (Provost, cc’d to Faculty Relations), in writing, within 10 working days from the receipt of the letter confirming FEC's decision.</p>
                
                <p>Should you have any procedural questions, please contact the Secretary to FEC, Brigitte Martin, at 780-863-9232 or brigitt2@ualberta.ca.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="footer">
            <![CDATA[
                Sincerely,<br />
                <br />
                <div class='previewnodisplay'><img src='skins/Signature.png' style='height: 3em;' /></div>
                <div class='generatenodisplay'><img src='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/skins/Signature.png' style='height: 3em;' /></div>
                <br />
                Declan Ali<br />
                Dean of Science
                </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
