<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="HQP Application" headerName="{$user_name}: {$hqp_application_uni} / {$hqp_application_program}" reportType="RP_HQP_APPLICATION" pdfType="RPTP_HQP_APPLICATION" pdfFiles="HQPApplicationPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" role="HQP">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Background Information" name="Information" type="ReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below.</li>
                    <li>Late or incomplete applications may not be reviewed. </li>
                    <li>Submit the online application via NETWORK Forum by June 30, 2015</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by Jul 31, 2015.</li>
                    <li>Expected start date of fellowship is September 1, 2015</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>About NETWORK</h3>
<p>The NETWORK Training Program in Technology and Aging awards partial funding to highly qualified master’s, doctoral and postdoctoral candidates and provides them with access to training and mentorship opportunities through the NETWORK Network of Centres of Excellence. NETWORK aims to provide a unique training environment that exposes trainees to multi-disciplinary research environments and to its industry and community partners. NETWORK is committed to attracting, developing, and retaining outstanding Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) in Canada.</p>

<p>NETWORK is a pan-Canadian network of industry, non-profit organizations, government, care providers, caregivers, end-users, and academic partners working together using high-quality research to drive innovation and create technologies and services that benefit older adults. Our vision is to harness and build upon the potential of emerging and advanced technologies in areas such as artificial intelligence (AI), e-health, information communication technologies (ICTs), and mobile technologies to stimulate technological, social, and policy innovation.</p>

<h3>Eligibility</h3>
<p>In order to be considered for NETWORK Awards, funding applicants must:</p>
<ol>
    <li>Receive financial support from additional sources: home department, supervisor research grants, and/or through government and agency scholarships or awards.</li> 
    <li>Participate full‐time in their respective programs.</li>
    <li>Be engaged in academic study/research aligned with the mission and vision of NETWORK.</li>
</ol>

<h3>The Awards</h3>
<p>Awards are intended to enhance existing funding support awarded to promising new scholars. Matching funds will be considered as part of the review of each applicant. Awards are awarded in amounts up to the following maximums per academic year:</p>
<ul>
    <li>$14,000 for Masters students (1 year award)</li>
    <li>$18,000 for PhD students (2 year award)</li>
    <li>$40,000 for Post-doctoral fellows (1 year award)</li>
</ul>
<p>The HQP Review Committee reserves the right to award additional funding to extraordinary candidates.</p>

<h3>Program Requirements</h3>
<p>Funded trainees are expected to participate in NETWORK seminar series, professional development activities (e.g. workshops in commercialization or entrepreneurship), the NETWORK trainee-led network, as well as complete a report on their activities annually or at the end of their award.</p>

<p>NETWORK funded trainees will acknowledge the NETWORK Award program in their presentations, publications, and other knowledge translation activities related to research conducted during their funding period.  Funded trainees are required to use the NETWORK logo on their posters and other materials related to research conducted during their funding period.</p>

<p>Written acknowledgement:</p>

<p><i>"This research was (partially) funded by the NETWORK NCE Trainee Award Program." </i></p>

<h3>Renewal</h3>
<p>Funded doctoral and postdoctoral applicants may submit one-year renewal applications for a third year of doctoral funding and a second year of postdoctoral funding. Ongoing funding is dependent on performance and achieving milestones outlined in the original application. Funded trainees are expected to submit an annual report through the NETWORK Forum reporting system each year. This report is required whether or not the trainee is applying for renewal of funding.</p>

<p>If successful, trainee funding will be held by the trainee’s supervisor in an account that must be established at the supervisor’s home institution.</p>

<h3>Admission Criteria</h3> 
<p>All applicants will be reviewed by the HQP Review Committee using the following criteria: </p>
<ol>
    <li>Scholarly Merit &amp; Quality of Proposed Research (40%)</li>
    <li>Fit with NETWORK Goals and Priorities (40%)</li>
    <li>Quality of training environment and proposed supervisor (20%)</li>
</ol>
<h3>Required Documents</h3>
<p>Award applicants must submit the following:</p>
<ol>
    <li>Online Application Form; </li>
    <li>Two Confidential Letters of Support (one must be from your proposed supervisor)</li>
    <li>Formal evidence of enrolment in a Master’s or Doctoral program or Post‐Doctoral position;</li> 
    <li>Formal evidence of awarded funding for 2015-16;</li>
    <li>Transcripts from all post‐secondary institutions;</li>
    <li>Curriculum Vitae.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Important Dates</h3>
Applications Due: June 30, 2015<br />
Results Available: July 31, 2015<br />
Funding Commences: September 1, 2015<br />
        ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="application" tooltip="Core Research Program Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) Application" name="Application" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_FORM" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below.</li>
                    <li>Late or incomplete applications may not be reviewed. </li>
                    <li>Submit the online application via NETWORK Forum by June 30, 2015</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by Jul 31, 2015.</li>
                    <li>Expected start date of fellowship is September 1, 2015</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Applicant Name:</b></td><td>{$user_name}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="uni" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UNI" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>University:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_PROGRAM" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Program:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="supervisor" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUP" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Supervisor Name:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="level" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_LVL" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($14,000, 1 year award)|PhD ($18,000, 2 year award)|Post-doctoral Award ($40,000, 1 year award)">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Funding Category:</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="project" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_PROJ" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Project Title:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_KEYWORDS" multiple="true" max="6" sizes="180">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Keywords (maximum 6):</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="research" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_RESEARCH" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Statement of research focus (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>NETWORK is inviting proposals in the broad area of technology and aging. The research project may be linked to one of NETWORK’s eight <a href='http://www.agewell-nce.ca/research' target='_blank'>Research Workpackages</a>, but does not need to limited to these.  Research should address at least one of our key research questions:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>What are the needs of older adults and caregivers?</li>
                            <li>What technology-based systems and services should be used to meet those needs?</li>
                            <li>How can we foster innovation in the technology and aging sector? </li>
                        </ol>
                        <p>The project may also support one of NETWORK’s four Crosscutting (CC) themes- Knowledge Mobilization, Commercialization, Transdisciplinarity and Training and Mentorship.</p>
                        <p>In this section, applicants should describe:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>How does your research connect to research foci of the NETWORK NCE?</li>
                            <li>Why is your project important?</li>
                            <li>Who is your target user population(s)?</li>
                            <li>What is the expected impact of your research?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="biography" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_BIO" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Biography and career goals (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section briefly describe:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Your current goals</li>
                            <li>Where you see yourself in 5-10 years</li>
                            <li>How you see NETWORK helping you to achieve your goals</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="objectives" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_OBJ" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Research objectives/aims (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research: </p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Overall aim of the research</li>
                            <li>Specific objectives - these should include both the research objectives AND the ”non-academic” objectives, such as knowledge transfer etc. (these objectives should be related to the specific project activities that will be mapped out in “tasks/activities” in the next section)</li>
                            <li>Specific research question(s) (if appropriate)</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_GOALS" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>How will you achieve your project goals? (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research: </p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Brief overview of the approach (design/methods) you will use to meet your project objectives</li>
                            <li>Describe the type of research being undertaken e.g. technology development, review, feasibility study, pilot study, requirements analysis, prototype development, intervention study, evaluation study, etc.</li>
                            <li>Describe the tasks and activities planned (provide detail on specific tasks to be carried out to meet the project objectives you identified above). “Activities” may include research activities, KT, innovation, commercialization, team-building and training, etc.</li>
                            <li>Provide specific timing of the various tasks, activities and milestones, where milestones are critical points in the project (e.g. completion of a task)</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="align" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_ALIGN" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Alignment to the mission and goals of NETWORK (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Successful applications will need to be aligned with the key strategic goals of NETWORK. Applicants are strongly encouraged to familiarize themselves with the document entitled NETWORK Network Goals available on the NETWORK website</p>
                        <p>As well as scientific excellence, applicants will need to demonstrate that their research has potential for real world impact.  In this section, describe how your research fits with NETWORK’s vision and strategic goals.</p>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="commercialization" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_COMM" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Potential for commercialization and/or knowledge mobilization (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>NETWORK research is designed to produce social and economic impact. Success in either ultimately depends on the rate of uptake and meaningful application of knowledge or products by end users. Commercialization and knowledge mobilization are vital activities of NETWORK.</p>
                        <p>Not every project is expected to be directly responsible for a commercial outcome or uptake of knowledge, but all projects should be actively contributing to these overall goals.  In this section address the following:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Are there new products/systems and services that may result from this research?</li>
                            <li>How could your research support the commercialization of other products and services (e.g. user-based research)?</li>
                            <li>What audiences/user groups might benefit from the knowledge produced by your research?</li>
                            <li>How will these user groups be engaged in your research?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="industry" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_IND" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Industry and/or community partners (if applicable) (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>The NETWORK Network unites leading Canadian private and public companies, government bodies, care providers, end-users and academic partners to develop cohesive critical mass in the technology and aging sector. All NETWORK researchers and trainees have access to the NETWORK partner network. We expect that the majority of NETWORK research projects will be carried out in conjunction with a community or industrial partner, for example: a technology company, a service provider, or a government department or agency.</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Specify how your project is aligned with partner goals, their role and contribution in the project and how you will work directly with this partner(s).</li>
                            <li>If your research does not currently involve working with a partner organization, identify the type of partner that would be appropriate for your research and how your research might benefit from partner engagement (e.g. Co-.development of technology, knowledge mobilization, experiential learning). Where possible, NETWORK will attempt to link trainee projects with appropriate NETWORK partners.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="innovation" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_INN" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Potential for innovation (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Innovation is a critical outcome of the NETWORK Network.  Innovation may come in various forms, including social innovation, scientific innovation, technological innovation, and policy-based innovation.  In this section, as applicable, address the following:</p>
                        <p><i>Social innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are practical benefits of your research to the wider community?</li>
                            <li>How will these benefits be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Technological innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are the novel aspects and contributions of your research from a technical point of view?</li>
                            <li>How will these be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Policy and practice innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>How might policies, services and care be transformed by your research?</li>
                            <li>How will these changes be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Scientific innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are the key scientific outputs from this research?</li>
                            <li>How will these be communicated to the scientific and/or knowledge-using communities?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="boundary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_BOUNDARY" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>In what ways will your project go beyond conventional disciplinary boundaries? (1/2 page)</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Transdisciplinary working - that is working across and with other disciplines than your own – is an important aspect of NETWORK. In this section please address the following:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Describe networking that may occur across disciplines and sites within NETWORK</li>
                            <li>How does the project link with other projects/activities in the NETWORK Network?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="training" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_TRAIN" height="200px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Training context</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Describe resources available through your proposed supervisor and department/institute.</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Is this project part of a bigger program of research? </li>
                            <li>How will these link to and support your specific project?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="funding" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_FUND" height="200px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Other funding obtained/applied for</h2>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Provide the total amount of matching funds and support already received or applied for (including stipends from supervisor), and source of funding. See "Background Information"</p>
                    </div>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="documents" type="ReportSection" tooltip="Required Documents" name="Documents" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_DOCS">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below.</li>
                    <li>Late or incomplete applications may not be reviewed. </li>
                    <li>Submit the online application via NETWORK Forum by June 30, 2015</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by Jul 31, 2015.</li>
                    <li>Expected start date of fellowship is September 1, 2015</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="support1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUPPORT1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Two Confidential Letters of Support (one must be from your proposed supervisor)</h2>
                <p>You need two confidential letters of support:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>a letter from an individuals familiar with your research, academic background, and aptitude; and</li>
                    <li>a letter from your proposed academic supervisor. </li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUPPORT2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="admission" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_ADMISSION" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Formal evidence of admission to a Master's or Doctoral program or Post-Doctoral position</h2>
                <p>Master’s and Doctoral students can submit their acceptance letters as formal evidence of admission to a graduate program. Applicants can also submit their transcripts as evidence of registration to a graduate program.</p>

<p>Post‐Doctoral fellows can submit a copy of their engagement letters as formal evidence of admission to a post‐doctoral position. In the event that engagement letters are not available, a letter from the applicant’s supervisor is sufficient. Please ensure to include the Award period and funding amount in the letter.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="evidence" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_EVIDENCE" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Formal evidence of application or awarded funding for 2015-2016</h2>
                <p>NETWORK Awards are intended to enhance existing funding support to promising new scholars. Applicants must receive financial support from additional sources.</p>

                <p>You can use any of the following as formal evidence of application or awarded funding</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Award Offer Letter</li>
                    <li>Email confirmation on submitted application for an award</li>
                    <li>Email confirmation from your supervisor of committed funds</li>
                    <li>Letter from funding agency</li>
                    <li>Post‐Doctoral Award Engagement Letters</li>
                    <li>Letter from Post‐Doctoral supervisor which outlines the Award period & funding amount</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="transcript1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_TRANS1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Transcripts from all post-secondary institutions</h2>
                <p>Submit transcripts from each post-secondary institution attended. Ensure to include the transcript legend usually found at the back of the paper transcript. All non‐English language documents must be officially translated into English and submitted together with the transcript. Transcripts with multiple pages must be scanned into a single PDF document</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="transcript2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_TRANS2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="cv" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_CV" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Curriculum Vitae</h2>
                <p>Please prepare the document and submit as a PDF.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below.</li>
                    <li>Late or incomplete applications may not be reviewed. </li>
                    <li>Submit the online application via NETWORK Forum by June 30, 2015</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by Jul 31, 2015.</li>
                    <li>Expected start date of fellowship is September 1, 2015</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below.</li>
                    <li>Late or incomplete applications may not be reviewed. </li>
                    <li>Submit the online application via NETWORK Forum by June 30, 2015</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by Jul 31, 2015.</li>
                    <li>Expected start date of fellowship is September 1, 2015</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
