<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Catalyst Grant Application" reportType="RP_CATALYST" pdfType="RPTP_CATALYST" pdfFiles="CatalystReportPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2024">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="" subRole="Catalyst2024">

        </Role>
        <Role role="Staff">
        
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions and Deadline" name="Catalyst" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>In this Request for Proposals, we are seeking to fund exploratory projects the successful completion of which would provide preliminary data to support other funding applications either to GlycoNet, or other funding sources. This opportunity is open <b>only</b> to individuals who are considered <b>Early Career Researchers</b>, and who are eligible to hold research funds at a Canadian University.</p>
                <h3>Requirements</h3>
                Projects should:
                <ul>
                    <li>Be aligned with GlycoNet’s research mandate (see <a href='https://canadianglycomics.ca/research/' target='_blank'>glyconet.ca</a>).</li>
                    <li>Be of an applied nature so that after additional funding through other means, the outcomes could lead to the development of a project with a translational direction.</li>
                    <li>Involve the training of Highly Qualified Personnel.</li>
                </ul>
                Projects should not:
                <ul>
                    <li>Concern development or performance of a high-throughput screen for ligands/inhibitors.</li>
                    <li>Concern development of synthetic methodology.</li>
                    <li>Concern basic biochemistry or biology with no tangible translational outcome.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p><b>Matching contributions are required, although these do not need to be cash. Eligible matching (please see <a href='https://drive.google.com/file/d/1htIEuiU1weYrAB5g1DX4JTOKD3oM9KPX/view
' target='_blank'>Appendix A</a>) contributions can come from non-federally funded student/post-doctoral scholarships, start-up funding, or other partner contributions. Matching of 10% or $7,500 is required (can be in-kind).</b></p>
                
                <h3>Funding Available</h3>
                <p>Proposals may request up to $75,000 in funding. All projects should be completed within 12 – 18 months.</p>
                
                <h3>Eligibility</h3>
                <p>This opportunity is open <b>only</b> to individuals who are considered <b>Early Career Researchers</b>, and who are eligible to hold research funds at a Canadian University. Having obtained other research funding would be viewed favorably.</p>
                
                <p>GlycoNet defines an ECR as pre-tenure, or within one year of having obtained tenure.</p>
                
                <p><b>Individuals who have previously received funding from GlycoNet are not eligible.</b></p>
                
                <p>An individual may serve as the Project Leader on only one Catalyst Grant application and may not be involved in more than two GlycoNet Grant applications.</p>
                
                <p>Questions about project suitability can be directed to the GlycoNet Administrative Centre (<a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> cc: <a href='mailto:vsharko@glyconet.ca'>vsharko@glyconet.ca</a>).</p>
                
                <h3>General Instructions and Deadline</h3>
                <p>All applications will be completed in the GlycoNet Forum, https://forum.glyconet.ca. Please read the following in-structions carefully. A complete application consists of:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li><b>Application/Proposal</b> (single PDF file, use Application Template)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Project Title</li>
                            <li>Project Leader / Lead Investigator</li>
                            <li>Other Investigators</li>
                            <li>Key Words</li>
                            <li>List of Partners and Matching Funds (Companies, Agencies, etc.)</li>
                            <li>Suggested Reviewers</li>
                            <li>Environmental Impact</li>
                            <li>Project Summary</li>
                            <li>Translational Strategy and Impact Statement</li>
                            <li>Project Proposal</li>
                            <li>References</li>
                            <li>Training Environment, including Equity, Diversity and Inclusion considerations</li>
                            <li>Conflict of Interest</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li><b>Budget</b> (a single Excel file in the correct format and with a budget for the project (12 – 18 months))</li>
                    <li><b>Budget Justification</b></li>
                    <li><b>Milestones</b> (a single Excel file)</li>
                    <li><b>Partner Letters of Support</b> (as separate PDF files)</li>
                    <li><b>CCV</b> (CIHR/NSERC Academic Format) for each Network Investigator (as separate PDF files)</li>
                </ol>
                <p><b>Deadline: 23:59 MDT on July 2, 2024.</b></p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="criteria" name="Review Criteria" title="Scientific Review Criteria" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The proposal will be evaluated based on the following criteria and rated as: <i>Very Weak, Weak, Average, Strong, or Very Strong</i>. An overall score will then be assigned to the proposal.</p>
                
                <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>1. Scientific Excellence</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall scientific excellence and soundness of the project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Quality and logic of the rationale</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Existence of strong preliminary data that supports the hypothesis. State of the technology</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the experimental plan</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to generate applicable results at the end of the project</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>2. Positioning of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Originality and novelty of the proposed research</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Added value of product/computational tool/technology compared to existing/in development ones</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Positioning of the project relative to the most current and powerful approaches or technologies that address the same end goal</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Competitiveness of the project on an international scale based on what is available or what is in development stage by public or private entities</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>3. Impact of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Potential impact of the project on the development of diagnostics/treatments/technology development</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to address important non-resolved specific challenges in the translational process.<br />Example include:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Potential to open new therapeutic approaches and research avenues</li>
                            <li>Contribution of the project to the development of more effective cost-effective diagnostics</li>
                            <li>Overall impact on the reduction of R&D costs, time to market, and development risks</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>4. Feasibility</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Clear deliverables, milestones, and schedule</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Feasibility of the project (clear deliverables, timetable, human and financial resources</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall quality of the infrastructure, facilities and equipment available for the proposed project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the project overall costs</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>5. Team</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>If this application is led by an ECR, what is the research potential of this researcher</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall track record of the PI and co-applicants:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the PI in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                            <li>Capacity of the PI to lead and coordinate the research – if the researcher is an ECR then comment on the risk of an ECR undertaking this project</li>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the co-applicants in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>6. Long-Term Plan (~5 years) and Commercialization</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the long-term development plan sound and feasible?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The technology will likely create commercial opportunities in the biopharma R&D sector or the clinic and elsewhere such as in one-health applications</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the technology easily transferable for use by partners or is the plan to access the technology well laid out (ex. service option)?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The project is well aligned with goals of the research partners</td></tr>
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="Application" name="Application" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_APPLICATION" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
                    <li>The application must be uploaded as a single PDF file to the GlycoNet Forum (after completing the application template, convert it to PDF format).</li>
                    <li>Please ensure that each section of the document is filled out carefully. All sections are obligatory to complete. Partially filled proposals will not be considered.</li>
                    <li>Use Times Roman/Times New Roman 11 for the text format</li>
                    <li>Download the <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/2024 Catalyst Grant Application Template.docx"><b>Application Template</b></a></li>
                    <li>Use <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/2024 Catalyst Grant Application Instructions.pdf" target='_blank'><b>Application Instructions</b></a> to complete the application</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>Application Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_ENV_IMPACT" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Environmental Impact Form</h3>
                If you have an Environmental Impact Form, please upload it as a pdf below.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The front page in the Excel file is the total project budget. The other pages (labeled NPI-1, NPI-2 etc; NPI = Network Principal Investigator) are for each involved NI. The budget requested by each NI should be filled in on their respective pages, including the partner contributions that are to be directed to their laboratories. The totals will populate automatically on the first page. <b><i>The project leader is responsible for combining all of the NI budgets into a single Excel file.</i></b> Failure to report on milestones will lead to loss of funding.</p>
                
                <b>Budget Guidelines:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Projects can request maximum of $75,000 from GlycoNet. Project can also request less than $75,000.</li>
                    <li>Projects require a 10% budget match which need not be cash. Matching funds cannot be from Canadian Federal funding sources (i.e. CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC, and CFI), as these are ineligible for matching.
                        <ul><li>Projects with a higher level of matching funds will be viewed more favorably.</li></ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>The project budget should clearly show the co-contribution of partner funds in alignment with SSF and eligible project expenses.</li>
                    <li>The maximum salary for Graduate Students is $30,000/year and for Postdoctoral Fellows is $55,000/year.</li>
                    <li>Trainee support should be limited to co-op students and should be listed in the technician line item.</li>
                    <li>Equipment is capped at $5,000/year/project.</li>
                    <li>Travel
                        <ul>
                            <li>Conference travel is capped at $2,000/year/NI/project. Note: Travel to the Annual General Meeting/Symposium is compulsory and will NOT be fully funded centrally through GlycoNet, as such, some travel funds should be kept for this purpose.</li>
                            <li>Travel and accommodation for trainees to visit collaborating labs should be included in project budgets.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Work with <b><a href='https://canadianglycomics.ca/integrated-services/' target='_blank'>GlycoNet Integrated Services</a></b>. Network investigators will receive a 20% discount on requested services. A quote can be provided upon request by <a href='mailto:coreservices@glyconet.ca'>coreservices@glyconet.ca</a></li>
                    <li>All partner contributions need to be supported by a letter from the partner institution (see below)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Based on federal funding guidelines, teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from federal sources cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching and a supporting letter documenting support is needed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>

                <p>Questions on eligibility of matching can be directed to GlycoNet Administrative Centre (<a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> cc: <a href='mailto:vsharko@glyconet.ca'>vsharko@glyconet.ca</a>).</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="" template="GlycoNet Budget Template.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget_justification" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_BUD_JUSTIF">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provide concise, but sufficient, justification for expenses. Benefit rates for employees should be clearly stipulated.</li>
                    <li>The project leader is responsible for generating a single budget justification document containing information from all NI groups.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="milestones" name="Milestones" blobSection="CAT_MILESTONES" tooltip="Project Milestones" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_MIL_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet,application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    Please download the following <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/GlycoNet Milestones Template (for Catalyst).xlsx"><b>Milestone Template</b></a> and upload it below.
                </p>
                <h3>Milestones Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Letters" title="Partner Letters of Support" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Letters of Support" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 5 Partner Support Letters</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ccv" name="NI CCVs" blobSection="CAT_CCV" tooltip="Common CV" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 10 CCVs</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$my_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
