<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Request for Letters of Intent Cycle II – Competition II" reportType="RP_CYCLEII" pdfType="RPTP_CYCLEII" pdfFiles="CycleIILOIPDF" ajax="true" allowIdProjects="true" disabled="false" year="2020">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="INACTIVE+" subRole="CycleIILOI">

        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Background and Description of Opportunity" name="Background" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The Canadian Glycomics Network (GlycoNet) is a Network of Centres of Excellence that focuses on the role of glycans (carbohydrates) in health. Areas of focus for GlycoNet in Cycle II (2020–23) are antimicrobials, chronic diseases (including diabetes & obesity), neurodegenerative diseases, and cancer. Additional information about Network research can be found at <a href='http://www.glyconet.ca/' target="_blank">www.glyconet.ca</a>.</p>
                
                <p>GlycoNet funds projects along the research innovation continuum: 1) translational R&D, 2) clinical engagement, 3) technology development, and 4) Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation (KTEE). The Network is currently seeking Letters of Intent (LOI) for the following funding programs:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Collaborative Team Grants. These grants involve two or more research groups in different disciplines. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li>Translational Grants. These grants further advance/translate projects with proof of concept and protected IP. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li>Strategic Initiatives. These grants fund partner-led initiatives to advance a partner challenge. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, with possibility of one year renewal, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li>Clinical Partnerships. These grants offer funding opportunities for clinicians to validate glycomics data from clinical studies. Maximum request: $50,000 for one year.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>The intent of the request for Letter of Intent (LOI) is to understand the community’s interest in these funding initiatives. LOIs will be screened and, if selected, will be invited to submit a full proposal in the most suitable funding program. It could be that, upon review of the LOI, the Network considers a different funding program from the one requested. LOIs that involve an investigator who is primarily funded by one of the tri-council agencies (e.g., CIHR) working with others primarily funded by one or both of the other tri-council agencies (e.g., NSERC and/or SSHRC) will be viewed most favourably.</p>
                
                <h2>Requirements for Cycle II LOIs</h2>
                
                <p>Letters of Intent must:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Primarily be targeted to the role/use of glycans in the treatment or prevention of infectious diseases, chronic diseases, neurodegenerative diseases, and/or cancer and/or lessening the economic burden of these diseases.</li>
                    <li>Lead to tangible deliverables by the end of the project that contribute to disease treatment or diagnosis.
                        <ul>
                            <li>Deliverables include intellectual property, processes, products, services, policies and/or clinical practice guidelines that can be developed with Partners and/or Stakeholders
                                <ul>
                                    <li><b>Partner</b> refers to an organization providing cash or in-kind contributions towards a Network project or the Network’s activities. A <b>Stakeholder</b> is an end-user organization that does not provide a financial contribution.</li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Present a knowledge mobilization plan to communicate results to partners and stakeholders.
                        <ul>
                            <li><b>Knowledge Mobilization</b>: A continual strategy involving bi-directional learning with partners and end-users using communication and education events each year.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Demonstrate a 1:1 financial match with partner funding (except for Clinical Partnerships); at least 50% of the matching funds should be cash. Partner funding must be NCE eligible; in particular, other Canadian Federal funding (e.g., CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC, CFI) is ineligible for matching. Please contact <a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> if you have specific questions about matching eligibility. The project budget clearly shows the co-contribution of partner funds in alignment with NCE and eligible project expenses.</li>
                    <li>Projects with a higher level of matching funds (e.g. 2:1, Partners:GlycoNet) will be viewed more favorably.</li>
                    <li>Provide information on the number and type (i.e. undergraduate, graduate student, PDF, etc.) of expected Highly Qualified Personnel trained each year of the project.</li>
                    <li>Demonstration of equity, diversity and inclusion within the project team (both at the Network Investigator and trainee level) and its activities will be viewed more favorably.</li>
                    <li>List the desired type of professional development training that GlycoNet could provide to HQP, for example, lab rotations, communication and writing skills improvement, etc.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h2>Eligibility</h2>
                <p>Based on NCE requirements, this opportunity is open only to individuals who are eligible to hold Tri-Council funds; CIHR, NSERC or SSHRC. Furthermore, GlycoNet requires that all investigators receiving Network funding must have other peer-reviewed support. Such support need not be from the Tri-Council. Questions about project suitability can be directed to the GlycoNet Administrative Office (<a href='mailto:glyconet@ualberta.ca'>glyconet@ualberta.ca</a>).</p>
                
                <h2>Letter of Intent</h2>
                <p>There will be a two-step application process:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Notice of Intent (NOI)</b>: Potential applicants must register by email to the GlycoNet Administrative Office (<a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a>) by December 13, 2019. The NOI will include the project title, key words, a list of investigators and partners involved in the project, preferred funding program, and an anticipated budget request (including matching funds). Upon registration, applicants will receive detailed instructions for completing the LOI in the GlycoNet Forum.</li>
                    <li><b>Letter of Intent (LOI)</b>: The LOI will include the project title, a one-page project description, potential deliverables, a knowledge mobilization plan, a list of investigators and partners involved in the project, and an anticipated budget request (including matching funds). LOIs will be peer-reviewed by external reviewers and the RMC. The deadline for LOI submission is January 13, 2020 (23:59 PST).
                        <ul>
                            <li>GlycoNet Management will conduct a review of the LOI to ensure compliance with NCE evaluation criteria. If an LOI is missing critical information, the applicants will be requested to provide the missing information within 48 hours, then re-submit through the GlycoNet forum. If an LOI is not updated as requested, it will be eliminated from the further review.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                
                <h2>Deadline</h2>
                <p>The LOI must be submitted through the GlycoNet Forum by 23:59 (PST) on January 13, 2020. LOIs received after this deadline will not be considered.</p>
                
                <h2>Full Application</h2>
                <p>We anticipate that Full Applications from those LOIs selected to move forward will be due in early March 2020 with funding release in April–May 2020.</p>
                
                <h2>Additional Information</h2>
                <p>Questions about this opportunity can be sent to <a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="General Information about the project" name="Description" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <!-- Program -->
        <ReportItem id="program" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PROGRAM" orientation="vertical" descriptions="These grants involve two or more research groups in different disciplines. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.|These grants further advance/translate projects with proof of concept and protected IP. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.|These grants fund partner-led initiatives to advance a partner challenge. Maximum request: $150,000 for one year, with possibility of one year renewal, 1:1 matching required.|These grants offer funding opportunities for clinicians to validate glycomics data from clinical studies. Maximum request: $50,000." options="Collaborative Team Grants|Translational Grants|Strategic Initiatives|Clinical Partnerships">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Program</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Theme -->
        <ReportItem id="theme" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_THEME" orientation="vertical" options="Antimicrobials|Chronic Diseases|Neurodegenerative Diseases|Cancer">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Theme</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Project Title -->
        <ReportItem id="title" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_TITLE" width="400px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Project Title</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Lead Investigator -->
        <ReportItem id="lead" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                              blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                              blobItem="CAT_DESC_LEAD" 
                              multiple="true" 
                              max="2" 
                              labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                              types="NI|text|text|text"
                              sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Lead Investigator</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Other Investigators -->
        <ReportItem id="other" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                               blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                               blobItem="CAT_DESC_OTHER" 
                               multiple="true" 
                               labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                               types="NI|text|text|text"
                               sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Other Investigators</h2>
                <p>Equity, diversity and inclusion should be taken into account when selecting members for the Project Team.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Key Words -->
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                                  blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                                  blobItem="CAT_DESC_WORDS" 
                                  multiple="true" 
                                  labels="Key Word" 
                                  types="text"
                                  sizes="150"
                                  max="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Key Words</h2>
                <p>A minimum of 5 keywords must be provided.  There can be no more than 10 keywords</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc) -->
        <ReportItem id="part" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PART" multiple="true" labels="Partner Name|Contact Name|Dollars requested|Partner Dollars: Cash|Partner Dollars: In-Kind" types="text|text|text|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Suggested reviewers -->
        <ReportItem id="reviewers" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_REV" multiple="true" labels="Name|E-Mail|Affiliation" types="text|text|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Suggested Reviewers</h2>
                At least seven suggested reviewers for the application.  At least five of the seven suggested reviewers must be working at locations outside of Canada.  Suggested reviewers should not be members of the GlycoNet Scientific Advisory Board, Research Management Committee or Board of Directors.  GlycoNet follows the <a target='_blank' href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/CIHR_Harmonized_COIC_Form-e.pdf'>CIHR/NSERC Conflict of Interest Policy</a>.  Please consult the policy before suggesting reviewers.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Question -->
        <ReportItem id="env_q" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV" orientation="horizontal" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Environmental Impact</h2>
                Does any phase of the research described in this proposal take place outside an office or a laboratory?
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Upload -->
        <ReportItem id="env_u" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV_UP">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                If Yes, please go to the NSERC web site (<a href="http://www.nserc.ca" target="_blank">www.nserc.ca</a>) and obtain the environmental impact form (Appendix A), complete this and submit it with your application.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_SUMMARY" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Summary</h2>
                <p>A project summary using <b>lay language</b> that describes the current unmet clinical need or the theme to which the proposed project applies, and that makes the case for GlycoNet to fund it (250 words maximum).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="relevance" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_RELEVANCE" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Relevance & Impact</h2>
                <p>Provide the relevance and impact (including socio-economic) of the project, and identify the key deliverables (250 words maximum).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>

        <ReportItem id="proposal" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PROPOSAL" rich="true" height="300px" limit="750">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Description</h2>
                <p>A research proposal (750 words maximum, not including figure/scheme legends and references)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="bib" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_BIB" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>References</b>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="knowledge" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_KNOW" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation</h2>
                <p>A summary of a knowledge mobilization plan to communicate results to partners and stakeholders (250 words maximum).<br />
                <small><b>Knowledge Mobilization:</b> A continual strategy involving bi-directional learning with partners and end-users using communication and education events each year.</small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="training" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_TRAIN" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Training Potential</h2>
                <p>A summary of the project’s training plan (250 words maximum).</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provide information on the number and type (i.e., undergraduate, graduate student, PDF, etc.) of expected Highly Qualified Personnel trained each year of the project.</li>
                    <li>List the desired type of professional development training that GlycoNet could provide to HQP, for example, lab rotations, communication and writing skills improvement, etc.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="abstract_upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ABSTRACT_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Figures & Schemes</h2>
                <p>Upload a PDF document containing your application's figures & schemes (optional)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A preliminary budget request should be summarized in the LOI.</p>
                Budget Guidelines:
                <ul>
                    <li>Projects can request up to $150,000/year from GlycoNet</li>
                    <li>Projects require a 1:1 match with Partner funding (except for Clinical Partnership); at least 50% of the matching funds must be cash. Partner funding must be NCE eligible; other Tri-Council and CFI funding is ineligible for matching.</li>
                    <li>Based on NCE guidelines, teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from CIHR, NSERC or SSHRC cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching. Questions on eligibility of matching can be directed to <a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a>.</li>
                    <li>The LOI project budget clearly shows the co-contribution of partner funds in alignment with NCE and eligible project expenses.</li>
                    <li>Projects with a higher level of matching funds (e.g. 2:1, Partners:GlycoNet) will be viewed more favorably (except for Clinical Partnership).</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="GLYCONET_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="GlycoNet Budget Template.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Involvement" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Involvement" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Letters from partners indicating the nature of their involvement in the project and their anticipated contribution (cash and/or in-kind) are recommended for the LOI, but not required. Partnerships and potential for leveraged funding (in-kind and/or cash) will increase suitability of the LOI standing for the GlycoNet renewal application.</p>

                <p>If a partner letter is not feasible then discuss existing partnerships with industry, foundations, health charities and/or other non-federal organizations that have supported your work within the last three years. Existing partner involvement should be described using a free format and attached as a one-page pdf.</p>

                <p>If a partner support letter is provided in the LOI, please use the following format:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Name of the Partner (e.g. company, foundation, institution, etc.) on letterhead.</li>
                    <li>Contact name and contact information.</li>
                    <li>Amount, nature, and area of anticipated support. 
                    <li>Letters must:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Come from a senior executive with signing authority for the contributions being committed.</li>
                            <li>Indicate the amount, duration, and nature (cash and/or in-kind) of support for the project.</li>
                            <li>Be on partner letterhead, be dated and signed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Please take into account University overhead for sponsored research when discussing funding with partners. This amount cannot be counted as matching.</li>
                    <li>Partner funding does not need to start by the LOI submission date. Partner funds, however, will need to be available by April 1, 2020, the projected start of GlycoNet Cycle II. Letters of support will be required at the full proposal stage.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission to the RMC" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="ReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$my_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
