<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Research Pipeline Grant" reportType="RP_RPG" pdfType="RPTP_RPG" pdfFiles="RPGReportPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2025">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="" subRole="RPGApplicant">

        </Role>
        <Role role="Staff">
        
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions and Deadline" name="Research Pipeline Grant" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>In this Request for Proposals, we are seeking to fund early and mid-stage projects the successful completion of which would provide preliminary data to support other funding applications either to GlycoNet, or other funding sources. This opportunity is open <b>only to individuals who do not currently hold GlycoNet funding.</b></p>

                <h3>Requirements</h3>
                Projects should:
                <ul>
                    <li>Be aligned with GlycoNet’s research mandate (see <a href='https://canadianglycomics.ca/research/' target='_blank'>glyconet.ca</a>).</li>
                    <li>Be of an <b>applied nature</b> so that after additional funding through other means, the outcomes could lead to the development of a project with a translational direction.</li>
                    <li>Involve the <b>training of Highly Qualified Personnel</b>.</li>
                </ul>
                Projects should not:
                <ul>
                    <li>Concern development or performance of a high-throughput screen for ligands/inhibitors.</li>
                    <li>Concern development of synthetic methodology.</li>
                    <li>Concern basic biochemistry or biology with no tangible translational outcome.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p><b>Matching contributions are required at a minimum of 1:1, with at least 50% in cash contributions ($37,500 in cash minimum and $37,500 in in-kind minimum). Larger matching contributions are encouraged (please see Appendix A for in-kind contributions calculation).</b></p>
                
                <h3>Funding Available</h3>
                <p>Proposals may request up to $75,000 in funding. All projects should be completed within 12 months with the possibility of extension.</p>
                
                <h3>Eligibility</h3>
                This opportunity is open only to individuals who:
                <ul>
                    <li>Do NOT currently hold GlycoNet funding, and</li>
                    <li>Are eligible to hold research funds at a Canadian University</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>Previous service within the Network and a willingness to provide service will be taken into consideration for funding decisions.</p>
                
                <p>Questions about project suitability can be directed to the GlycoNet Administrative Centre (<a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> cc: <a href='mailto:vsharko@glyconet.ca'>vsharko@glyconet.ca</a>).</p>
                
                <h3>General Instructions and Deadline</h3>
                <p>All applications will be completed in the GlycoNet Forum, https://forum.glyconet.ca. Please read the following in-structions carefully. A complete application consists of:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li><b>Application/Proposal</b> (single PDF file, use Application Template)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Project Title</li>
                            <li>Research Area</li>
                            <li>Project Leader / Lead Investigator</li>
                            <li>Other Funded Investigators</li>
                            <li>Collaborators</li>
                            <li>Key Words</li>
                            <li>List of Partners and Matching Funds (Companies, Agencies, etc.)</li>
                            <li>Suggested Reviewers</li>
                            <li>Investigators’ Contribution to GlycoNet’s Committees and Board</li>
                            <li>Environmental Impact</li>
                            <li>Conflict of Interest</li>
                            <li>Outcomes from previous GlycoNet funding (on the same subject/topic/project) (if applicable)</li>
                            <li>Project Summary</li>
                            <li>Plain Language Project Summary</li>
                            <li>Project Proposal</li>
                            <li>References</li>
                            <li>Commercialization Strategy and Impact Statement</li>
                            <li>Current IP Status</li>
                            <li>Integration with GlycoNet Programs and Other Funding Opportunities</li>
                            <li>Training Environment, including Equity, Diversity and Inclusion considerations</li>
                            <li>Research Security</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li><b>Budget</b> (a single Excel file in the correct format and with a budget for the project (12 – 18 months))</li>
                    <li><b>Budget Justification</b></li>
                    <li><b>Milestones</b> (a single Excel file)</li>
                    <li><b>Research Security Attestation Forms</b></li>
                    <li><b>Partner Letters of Support</b> (as separate PDF files)</li>
                    <li><b>CCV</b> (CIHR/NSERC Academic Format) for each Network Investigator (as separate PDF files)</li>
                </ol>
                <p><b>Deadline: 23:59 PST on February 20, 2025.</b></p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="criteria" name="Review Criteria" title="Scientific Review Criteria" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The proposal will be evaluated based on the following criteria and rated as: <i>Very Weak, Weak, Average, Strong, or Very Strong</i>. An overall score will then be assigned to the proposal.</p>
                
                <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>1. Scientific Excellence</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall scientific excellence and soundness of the project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Quality and logic of the rationale</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Existence of strong preliminary data that supports the hypothesis. State of the technology</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the experimental plan</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to generate applicable results at the end of the project</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>2. Positioning of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Originality and novelty of the proposed research</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Added value of product/computational tool/technology compared to existing/in development ones</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Positioning of the project relative to the most current and powerful approaches or technologies that address the same end goal</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Competitiveness of the project on an international scale based on what is available or what is in development stage by public or private entities</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>3. Impact of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Potential impact of the project on the development of diagnostics/treatments/technology development</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to address important non-resolved specific challenges in the translational process.<br />Example include:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Potential to open new therapeutic approaches and research avenues</li>
                            <li>Contribution of the project to the development of more effective cost-effective diagnostics</li>
                            <li>Overall impact on the reduction of R&D costs, time to market, and development risks</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>4. Feasibility</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Clear deliverables, milestones, and schedule</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Feasibility of the project (clear deliverables, timetable, human and financial resources</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall quality of the infrastructure, facilities and equipment available for the proposed project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the project overall costs</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>5. Team</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>If this application is led by an ECR, what is the research potential of this researcher</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall track record of the PI and co-applicants:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the PI in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                            <li>Capacity of the PI to lead and coordinate the research – if the researcher is an ECR then comment on the risk of an ECR undertaking this project</li>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the co-applicants in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>6. Long-Term Plan (~5 years) and Commercialization</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the long-term development plan sound and feasible?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The technology will likely create commercial opportunities in the biopharma R&D sector or the clinic and elsewhere such as in one-health applications</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the technology easily transferable for use by partners or is the plan to access the technology well laid out (ex. service option)?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The project is well aligned with goals of the research partners</td></tr>
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="Application" name="Application" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_APPLICATION" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
                    <li>The application must be uploaded as a single PDF file to the GlycoNet Forum (after completing the application template, convert it to PDF format).</li>
                    <li>Please ensure that each section of the document is filled out carefully. All sections are obligatory to complete. Partially filled proposals will not be considered.</li>
                    <li>Use Times Roman/Times New Roman 11 for the text format</li>
                    <li>Download the <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/Research Pipeline Grant - Application Template.docx"><b>Application Template</b></a></li>
                    <li>Use <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/Research Pipeline Grant - Application Instructions.pdf" target='_blank'><b>Application Instructions</b></a> to complete the application</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>Application Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_ENV_IMPACT" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Environmental Impact Form</h3>
                If you have an Environmental Impact Form, please upload it as a pdf below.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The front page in the Excel file is the total project budget. The other pages (labeled NPI-1, NPI-2 etc; NPI = Network Principal Investigator) are for each involved NI. The budget requested by each NI should be filled in on their respective pages, including the partner contributions that are to be directed to their laboratories. The totals will populate automatically on the first page. <b><i>The project leader is responsible for combining all of the NI budgets into a single Excel file. Failure to report on milestones will lead to loss of funding.</i></b></p>
                
                <b>Budget Guidelines:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Projects can request maximum of $75,000 from GlycoNet. Project can also request less than $75,000.</li>
                    <li>Projects require a 1:1 match with Partner funding; at least 50% of the matching funds must be cash. <b>Partner funding cannot come from Canadian Federal funding sources</b> (i.e., CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC, and CFI) as these are ineligible for matching. Larger matching contributions are encouraged</li>
                    <li>The project budget should clearly show the co-contribution of partner funds in alignment with SSF and eligible project expenses (Refer to <a href='https://drive.google.com/file/d/1rSRuurBSOkgnt3wqWEigrFoHNrHrN5dW/view' target='_blank'>Eligible Costs and Activities</a>).</li>
                    <li>The maximum salary for Graduate Students is $30,000/year and for Postdoctoral Fellows is $55,000/year.</li>
                    <li>Trainee support should be limited to co-op students and should be listed in the technician line item.</li>
                    <li>Equipment is capped at $5,000/year/project.</li>
                    <li>Travel
                        <ul>
                            <li>Conference travel is capped at $3,000/year/NI/project. Note: Travel to the Annual General Meeting/Symposium is compulsory and will NOT be fully funded centrally through GlycoNet, as such, <b>the travel funds should be kept for this purpose.</b></li>
                            <li>Travel and accommodation for trainees to visit collaborating labs should be included in project budgets.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Work with <b>GlycoNet Integrated Services</b>. A quote can be provided upon request by <a href='mailto:coreservices@glyconet.ca'>coreservices@glyconet.ca</a>.</li>
                    <li>
                        All partner contributions need to be supported by a letter from the partner institution (see below)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Based on federal funding guidelines, teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from federal sources cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching and a supporting letter documenting support is needed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>

                <p>Questions on eligibility of matching can be directed to GlycoNet Administrative Centre (<a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> cc: <a href='mailto:vsharko@glyconet.ca'>vsharko@glyconet.ca</a>).</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="" template="GlycoNet Budget Template (RPG).xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget_justification" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_BUD_JUSTIF">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provide concise, but sufficient, justification for expenses (<b>in accordance with the submitted budget</b>). Benefit rates for employees should be clearly stipulated. The budget justification should be detailed enough to clearly explain why and for what each expense is needed, but concise enough not to overwhelm with unnecessary information.</li>
                    <li><b>Justify expenses listed in the budget spreadsheet. The justifications must correspond to the budget line items in the spreadsheet.</b></li>
                    <li>The project leader is responsible for generating a single budget justification document containing information from all NI groups.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="milestones" name="Milestones" blobSection="CAT_MILESTONES" tooltip="Project Milestones" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_MIL_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet,application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Provide as a single Excel file, uploaded to Forum, use the template</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Download the <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/GlycoNet Milestones Template.xlsx"><b>Milestone Template</b></a> from the Forum </li>
                    <li><b>Indicate milestones containing clear go/no-go decision points</b></li>
                    <li>Quarterly milestones should be provided and should contain sufficient detail that progress toward them can be clearly monitored. Progress toward stated milestones will be a significant component of evaluation for continued project funding</li>
                    <li>Add an “X” to the shaded boxes</li>
                    <li>Names should be added in the format: First Name Last Name</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Milestones Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Letters" title="Partner Letters of Support" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Letters of Support" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Letters from partners are required, indicating the nature of their involvement in the project and their anticipated contribution, both cash and in-kind. These amounts should match those listed in the budget). Partnerships and potential for leveraged funding (in-kind and/or cash) will increase suitability of the project for the GlycoNet renewal application.</p>
                
                Partner letters must use the following format: 
                <ul>
                    <li>Name of the Partner (e.g. company, foundation, institution, etc.) on letterhead.</li>
                    <li>Contact name and contact information.</li>
                    <li><b>Amount (cash and in-kind), nature, and area of anticipated support.</b></li>
                    <li>Letters must:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Come from a senior executive with signing authority for the contributions being committed.</li>
                            <li>Indicate the amount, duration, and nature (cash and/or in-kind) of support for the project.</li>
                            <li>Be on partner letterhead, be dated and signed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Please take into account University overhead for sponsored research when discussing funding with partners. This amount cannot be counted as matching.</li>
                </ul><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="security" name="Research Security" blobSection="CAT_SECURITY" tooltip="Research Security" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="attestation1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <a href='https://www.nserc-crsng.gc.ca/InterAgency-Interorganismes/RS-SR/_doc/Attestation_e.pdf' target='_blank'>Attestation Form</a>. <b>Fill in and upload the Attestation Form for each project member</b> (The research team includes researchers with named roles in the grant applications, as well as any other researchers involved in activities supported by the grant, such as highly qualified personnel (HQP), co-authors, or informal collaborators who may or may not be identified in the grant application. HQP can include undergraduate and graduate students, post-doctoral researchers, as well as research staff).
                <div style='display:flex; width: 100%;'>
                    <div style='width: 50%; min-width: 500px;'>
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION3" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION4" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
                    </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION5" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                    <div style='width: 50%; min-width: 500px;'>
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION6" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION7" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION8" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
                    </div>
                </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="private" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_PRIVATE" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <div id='private' style='margin-top: 1em;'>
                    Will the research involve a private sector partner organization?  (Partner organizations from a private sector (those that are not owned or operated by any order of government and include all for-profit organizations), including industrial associations and producer groups (since their member organizations are principally from the private sector)
                    {$item}
                </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="risk" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_RISK" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <div id='risk' style='display:none; margin-top: 1em;'>
                    In case of involvement of a private sector partner in the project, fill in the <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/sites/default/files/attachments/2023/risk_assessment_form_ISED-ISDE3832E.pdf' target='_blank'>Risk Assessment Form</a> and upload it to the Forum. <br />
                    In case risks are identified in the Risk Assessment Form, develop a risk mitigation plan with the institution and must be submitted to GlycoNet.  One Risk Assessment Form is needed per project, developed with the Project Leader’s institution. It is also recommended to utilize existing government resources, such as <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/en/safeguarding-your-research' target='_blank'>Safeguarding Your Research</a> portal and particularly <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/en/safeguarding-your-research/guidelines-and-tools-implement-research-security/mitigating-your-research-security-risks/what-steps-can-you-take-protect-your-research' target='_blank'>Mitigating Your Research Security Risks</a> page.
                    {$item}
                </div>
                <div id='risk_no' style='display:none; margin-top: 1em;'>No further requirements</div>
                <script type='text/javascript'>
                    $('#private input').change(function(){
                        var privateValue = $('#private input:checked').val();
                        if(privateValue == "Yes"){
                            $('#risk').show();
                            $('#risk_no').hide();
                        }
                        else if(privateValue == "No"){
                            $('#risk').hide();
                            $('#risk_no').show();
                        }
                        else{
                            $('#risk').hide();
                            $('#risk_no').hide();
                        }
                    }).change();
                </script>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ccv" name="NI CCVs" blobSection="CAT_CCV" tooltip="Common CV" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Please upload <b>CCV (CIHR/NSERC academic format)</b> for each Network Investigator</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <If if="{==({getText(RP_RPG,CAT_SECURITY,CAT_SECURITY_PRIVATE,0,{$user_id},{$project_id})},)}">
            <![CDATA[
                You must answer the risk assessment question on the "Research Security" section.
            ]]>
        </If>
        <Else>
            <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$my_email},vsharko@glyconet.ca" />
        </Else>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
