<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="LOI for Strategic Science Fund" reportType="RP_SSF_LOI" pdfType="RPTP_SSF_LOI" pdfFiles="SSFLOIPDF" ajax="true" allowIdProjects="true" disabled="false" year="2022">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="INACTIVE+" subRole="SSFLOI">

        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Background and Description of Opportunity" name="Background" title="LOI for Strategic Science Fund" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Upon registration, applicants will be sent a link to the GlycoNet Forum (a web-based tool), which will be used to complete the application. All applications are to be submitted by the principal investigator on the project. This individual must be eligible to receive Tri-Council funding (i.e. the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR), the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) or the Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada (SSHRC)). Working with others primarily funded by one or both of the other tri-council agencies (e.g., NSERC and/or SSHRC) will be viewed most favorably.</p>
                A complete application consists of:
                <ol>
                    <li>Project Description and References (details below)</li>
                    <li>Figures/Schemes (a single PDF file)</li>
                    <li>Budget (a single Excel file)</li>
                    <li>Letter(s) of Conditional Support from Partners (as separate PDF Files)</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="General Information about the project" name="Description" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <!-- Stream -->
        <ReportItem id="stream" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_STREAM" orientation="vertical" options="Collaborative Team|Translational|Strategic Initiatives" labels="&lt;b>Collaborative Team:&lt;/b> These grants involve two or more research groups in different disciplines. Maximum request: $200,000/year for up to three years, 1:1 matching required.|&lt;b>Translational:&lt;/b> These grants further advance/translate projects with proof of concept and protected IP. Maximum request: $200,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.|&lt;b>Strategic Initiatives:&lt;/b> These grants fund partner-led initiatives to advance a partner challenge. Maximum request: $200,000 for one year, with possibility of one-year renewal, 1:1 matching required.">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Select the funding stream you are applying for:</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Theme -->
        <ReportItem id="theme" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_THEME" orientation="vertical" options="Antimicrobials|Chronic Diseases|Neurodegenerative Diseases|Cancer">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Theme</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Project Title -->
        <ReportItem id="title" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_TITLE" width="400px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Project Title</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Lead Investigator -->
        <ReportItem id="lead" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                              blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                              blobItem="CAT_DESC_LEAD" 
                              multiple="true" 
                              max="2" 
                              labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                              types="NI|text|text|text"
                              sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Lead Investigator</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Other Investigators -->
        <ReportItem id="other" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                               blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                               blobItem="CAT_DESC_OTHER" 
                               multiple="true" 
                               labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                               types="NI|text|text|text"
                               sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Other Investigators</h2>
                <p>Equity, diversity and inclusion should be taken into account when selecting members for the Project Team.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Key Words -->
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                                  blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                                  blobItem="CAT_DESC_WORDS" 
                                  multiple="true" 
                                  labels="Key Word" 
                                  types="text"
                                  sizes="150"
                                  max="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Key Words</h2>
                <p>A minimum of 5 keywords must be provided.  There can be no more than 10 keywords</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- EDI -->
        <ReportItem id="edi" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_EDI" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Equity, Diversity and Inclusion</h2>
                <p>Demonstrate how equity, diversity and inclusion (EDI) has been incorporated into the project (see application instructions for more details).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc) -->
        <ReportItem id="part" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PART" multiple="true" labels="Partner Name|Contact Name|Dollars requested|Partner Dollars: Cash|Partner Dollars: In-Kind" types="text|text|text|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Suggested reviewers -->
        <ReportItem id="reviewers" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_REV" multiple="true" labels="Name|E-Mail|Affiliation" types="text|text|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Suggested Reviewers</h2>
                At least three suggested reviewers for the application. At least two of the three suggested reviewers must be working at locations outside of Canada. Suggested reviewers should not be members of the GlycoNet Scientific Advisory Board, Research Management Committee or Board of Directors.  GlycoNet follows the <a target='_blank' href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/CIHR_Harmonized_COIC_Form-e.pdf'>CIHR/NSERC Conflict of Interest Policy</a>. Please consult the policy before suggesting reviewers.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Question -->
        <ReportItem id="env_q" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV" orientation="horizontal" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Environmental Impact</h2>
                Does any phase of the research described in this proposal take place outside an office or a laboratory?
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Upload -->
        <ReportItem id="env_u" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV_UP">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                If Yes, please go to the NSERC web site (<a href="http://www.nserc.ca" target="_blank">www.nserc.ca</a>) and obtain the environmental impact form (Appendix A), complete this and submit it with your application.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_SUMMARY" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Summary</h2>
                <p>A project summary using <b>lay language</b> that describes the current unmet clinical need or the theme to which the proposed project applies, and that makes the case for GlycoNet to fund it (250 words maximum).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="relevance" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_RELEVANCE" rich="true" height="300px" limit="500">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Relevance & Impact</h2>
                <p>Describe relevance and impact of the project which will lead to tangible deliverables by the end of the project that contribute to disease treatment or diagnosis. (500 words maximum).</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Deliverables include intellectual property, processes, products, services, scientific publications, policies and/or clinical practice guidelines that can be developed with Partners and/or Stakeholders
                        <ul>
                            <li><b>Partner</b> refers to an organization providing cash or in-kind contributions towards a project or GlycoNet activities. A <b>Stakeholder</b> is an end-user organization that does not provide a financial contribution. </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="ktee" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_KTEE" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Knowledge Mobilization</h2>
                <p>Present a knowledge mobilization plan to communicate results to partners and stakeholders. (250 words maximum)</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Knowledge Mobilization:</b> A continual strategy involving bi-directional learning with partners and end-users using communication and education events each year.</li>
                    <li>The impact on target communities (e.g., demonstrating ability to conduct outreach to those communities, conducting activities in culturally appropriate ways, addressing and mitigating systemic barriers, and keeping communities meaningfully engaged and apprised of the results of their participation).</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_HQP" rich="true" height="300px" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Highly Qualified Personnel</h2>
                <p>Provide information on the number and type (i.e. undergraduate, graduate student, PDF, etc.) of expected Highly Qualified Personnel trained each year of the project. (250 words maximum)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>

        <ReportItem id="proposal" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PROPOSAL" rich="true" height="300px" limit="1500">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Description</h2>
                <p>A two-page research proposal (1500 words maximum, not including figure/scheme legends and references)<p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="bib" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_BIB" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>References</b>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="abstract_upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ABSTRACT_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Figures & Schemes</h2>
                <p>Upload a PDF document containing your application's figures & schemes (optional)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The front page in the Excel file is the total project budget.  The other pages (labeled NPI-1, NPI-2 etc; NPI = Network Principal Investigator) are for each involved NI. The budget requested by each NI should be filled in on their respective pages, including the partner contributions that are to be directed to their laboratories. The totals will populate automatically on the first page.  <b>The project leader is responsible for combining all of the NI budgets into a single Excel file</b>.  The first page also contains the budget for the use of the core services in the project. <b>The project leader should coordinate the core services budget for the project</b>. If you are asked for a password when entering a number, you are attempting to enter a number in a field that will automatically populate.</p>
                
                Budget Guidelines:<br />
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Collaborative Team:</b> Maximum request: $200,000/year for up to three years, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li><b>Translational:</b> Maximum request: $200,000 for one year, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li><b>Strategic Initiatives:</b>  Maximum request: $200,000 for one year, with possibility of one-year renewal, 1:1 matching required.</li>
                    <li>Demonstrate a 1:1 financial match with partner funding; at least 50% of the matching funds should be cash from eligible partners. Other Canadian Federal funding (e.g., CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC, CFI) is ineligible for matching. Please note that SSF does not consider funding from federal agencies (e.g. AAFC, NRC) as matching but as leveraging. These leveraged funds are not mandatory but are assets to the application.
                        <ul>
                            <li>Contact <a href='mailto:mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> if you have specific questions about matching eligibility. The project budget must clearly show the co-contribution of partner funds in alignment with SSF and eligible project expenses. Projects with a higher level of matching funds (e.g. 2:1, Partners:GlycoNet) will be viewed more favorably.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>The maximum salary for Graduate Students is $25,000/year and for Postdoctoral Fellows is $45,000/year.</li>
                    <li>Undergraduate student support should be limited to co-op students and should be listed in the technician line item.</li>
                    <li>Equipment is capped at $5,000/project.</li>
                    <li>Travel
                        <ul>
                            <li>Conference travel is capped at $1,500/year/NI with a maximum of $3,000/project. This fund can be used for the annual Canadian Glycomics Symposium.</li>
                            <li>Travel and accommodation for trainees to visit collaborating labs should be included in project budgets.</li>
                            <li>Travel to the Annual General Meeting will be funded centrally through the Network. It should not be incorporated into project budgets.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Chemical Synthesis and Glycan Structure Analysis Cores
                        <ul>
                            <li>Those of you who have an anticipated need for these core services should contact Warren Wakarchuk (warren.wakarchuk@ualberta.ca).  We will generate an estimate that can be incorporated into the budget.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>All partner contributions need to be supported by a letter from the partner institution (see below)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from CIHR, NSERC or SSHRC cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching and a supporting letter documenting support is needed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Up to $5,000 of the requested budget can be used to reimburse expenses associated with development of a commercialization plan. These expenses should be budgeted under “Animal Work or Other Services”.</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="GLYCONET_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="GlycoNet Budget Template3.xls">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Involvement" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Involvement" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The LOI must be accompanied by letter(s) of conditional support from eligible partner(s). Please follow the guidelines below for the letter of support:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Name of the Partner (e.g. company, foundation, institution, etc.) on letterhead.</li>
                    <li>Contact name and contact information</li>
                    <li>Be signed by a representative of the key stakeholders described in the presence at the national level section of the proposal document</li>
                    <li>Should be sent by a senior executive with influence over a budget</li>
                    <li>Indicate the anticipated level, duration and nature of support for the applicant’s proposed activities, using quantifiable metrics to the extent possible (e.g., amount of cash and in-kind support, expected time commitment, etc.)</li>
                    <li>Describe the potential involvement and added-value of the applicant’s proposed activities to the stakeholder’s current and future activities</li>
                    <li>Indicate current and past associations with individuals participating in the proposed activities</li>
                    <li>Be written and formatted by stakeholders only (i.e., not be a template formatted by the applicant)</li>
                    <li>Be dated and signed no earlier than August 13, 2021 (launch date of SSF competition)</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission to the RMC" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="ReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$my_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
