<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Strategic Initiatives Application" reportType="RP_STRAT" pdfType="RPTP_STRAT" pdfFiles="StrategicReportPDF" ajax="true" year="2025" allowIdProjects="true" prepend="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="" subRole="Strat2025">

        </Role>
        <Role role="STAFF+">

        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions and Deadline" name="Strategic" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This Request for Proposals seeks to fund <b>partner-led projects</b> that address research needs of the pharmaceutical, biotechnology, or agri-food industry.</p>
                
                <h3>Requirements</h3>
                Projects should:
                <ul>
                    <li>Be aligned with GlycoNet’s research mandate (see <a href='https://canadianglycomics.ca/research/' target='_blank'>glyconet.ca</a>)</li>
                    <li>Must have an articulated IP and patentability strategy</li>
                    <li>Be accompanied by a commercialization plan provided by the Technology Transfer Office of the project leader’s institution or the project’s industrial partner</li>
                    <li>Must address partner’s research needs or challenges</li>
                    <li>Have an identified partner that could take over the outcomes of the research</li>
                    <li>Partner matching of 1:1.5 is required, greater matching will be viewed more favorably by the committee. 50% of matching must be cash (for a $150,000 request, matching should be $225,000 with at least $112,500 cash and $112,500 in-kind – please see <a href='https://drive.google.com/file/d/17qTip8z0mogjsER4Kn9y2zFaSFeOShEF/view' target='_blank'><b>Appendix A</b></a>). Partner funding must be SSF eligible; in particular, other Canadian Federal funding is <b>ineligible</b> for matching. Industry partner is preferred.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>Funding Available</h3>
                <p>Proposals may request up to $150,000 in funding. It is anticipated that projects will be completed within 12 months.  Continued funding for projects past the 12-month period will be considered on a case-by-case basis after review by the Commercialization Committee; however, all projects must be completed by March 31, 2027.</p>
                
                <h3>Eligibility</h3>
                <p>This opportunity is open only to individuals at post-secondary institutions and research hospitals who are eligible to hold research funds, including Tri-Council funds; i.e., the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR), the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) or the Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada (SSHRC).</p>
                
                <h3>Application Form and Submission</h3>
                <p>This is a rolling competition. Applicants can submit their proposals when they are ready. Competitions will be offered on a quarterly basis and will depend on funding availability.</p>
                
                <p>Potential applicants must register by email to info@glyconet.ca (cc vsharko@glyconet.ca) please provide the project title, project leader, list of investigators involved in the project, anticipated budget request, along with the matching amount (cash/in-kind and sources), a summary of the project, and a short summary addressing the question: "How will your research project further glycobiology research?". Please note that the matching cannot come from federal sources. This information can be modified when the application is submitted although the overall focus must remain the same. Upon registration, applicants will receive instructions for completing the application.</p>
                
                <h3>Additional Information</h3>
                <p>Questions about this opportunity can be sent to <a href='mailto:info@glyconet.ca'>info@glyconet.ca</a> (cc <a href='mailto:vsharko@glyconet.ca'>vsharko@glyconet.ca</a>).</p>
                
                <h3>General Instructions and Deadline</h3>
                <p>All applications will be completed in the GlycoNet Forum, https://forum.glyconet.ca. Please read the following instructions carefully. A complete application consists of:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li><b>Application/Proposal</b> (single PDF file, use Application Template)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Project Title</li>
                            <li>Project Leader / Lead Investigator</li>
                            <li>Other Investigators</li>
                            <li>Key Words</li>
                            <li>List of Partners and Matching Funds (Companies, Agencies, etc.)</li>
                            <li>Suggested Reviewers</li>
                            <li>Environmental Impact</li>
                            <li>Conflict of Interest</li>
                            <li>Response to Reviewer's Comments (if applicable)</li>
                            <li>Outcomes from previous GlycoNet funding (on the same subject/topic/project) (if applicable)</li>
                            <li>Project Summary</li>
                            <li>Project Proposal</li>
                            <li>References</li>
                            <li>Relevance and Impact</li>
                            <li>Training Environment, including Equity, Diversity and Inclusion Considerations</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li><b>Budget</b> (a single Excel file in the correct format and with a budget for the project)</li>
                    <li><b>Budget Justification</b></li>
                    <li><b>Milestones</b> (a single Excel file)</li>
                    <li><b>Commercialization Plan</b> (as a separate PDF file)</li>
                    <li><b>Partner Letters of Support</b> (as separate PDF files)</li>
                    <li><b>CCV</b> (CIHR/NSERC Academic Format) for each Network Investigator (as separate PDF files)</li>
                </ol>
                
                <p><b><i>Deadline: Rolling Call</i></b>. Competitions will be offered on a quarterly basis.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="criteria" name="Review Criteria" title="Scientific Review Criteria" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The proposal will be evaluated based on the following criteria and rated as: <i>Very Weak, Weak, Average, Strong, or Very Strong</i>. An overall score will then be assigned to the proposal.</p>
                
                <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>1. Scientific Excellence</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall scientific excellence and soundness of the project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Quality and logic of the rationale</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Existence of strong preliminary data that supports the hypothesis. State of the technology</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the experimental plan</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to generate applicable results at the end of the project</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>2. Positioning of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Originality and novelty of the proposed research</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Added value of product/computational tool/technology compared to existing/in development ones</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Positioning of the project relative to the most current and powerful approaches or technologies that address the same end goal</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Competitiveness of the project on an international scale based on what is available or what is in development stage by public or private entities</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>3. Impact of the Research Project</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Potential impact of the project on the development of diagnostics/treatments/technology development</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Capacity to address important non-resolved specific challenges in the translational process.<br />Example include:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Potential to open new therapeutic approaches and research avenues</li>
                            <li>Contribution of the project to the development of more effective cost-effective diagnostics</li>
                            <li>Overall impact on the reduction of R&D costs, time to market, and development risks</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>4. Feasibility</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Clear deliverables, milestones, and schedule</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Feasibility of the project (clear deliverables, timetable, human and financial resources</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall quality of the infrastructure, facilities and equipment available for the proposed project</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Soundness of the project overall costs</td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>5. Team</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>If this application is led by an ECR, what is the research potential of this researcher</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Overall track record of the PI and co-applicants:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the PI in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                            <li>Capacity of the PI to lead and coordinate the research – if the researcher is an ECR then comment on the risk of an ECR undertaking this project</li>
                            <li>Relevance of the expertise and productivity of the co-applicants in the achievement of the proposed project</li>
                        </ul>
                    </td></tr>
                    
                    <tr><th style='text-align:left;'>6. Long-Term Plan (~5 years) and Commercialization</th></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the long-term development plan sound and feasible?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The technology will likely create commercial opportunities in the biopharma R&D sector or the clinic and elsewhere such as in one-health applications</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>Is the technology easily transferable for use by partners or is the plan to access the technology well laid out (ex. service option)?</td></tr>
                    <tr><td style='padding-left:18px;'>The project is well aligned with goals of the research partners</td></tr>
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="Application" name="Application" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_APPLICATION" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
                    <li>The application must be uploaded as a single PDF file to the GlycoNet Forum (after completing the application template, convert it to PDF format).</li>
                    <li>Please ensure that each section of the document is filled out carefully. All sections are obligatory to complete. Partially filled proposals will not be considered.</li>
                    <li>Use Times Roman/Times New Roman 11 for the text format</li>
                    <li>Download the <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/2025 Strategic Initiatives Application Template.docx"><b>Application Template</b></a></li>
                    <li>Use <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/2025-2026 Strategic Initiatives Application Instructions.pdf" target='_blank'><b>Application Instructions</b></a> to complete the application</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>Application Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_ENV_IMPACT" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Environmental Impact Form</h3>
                If you have an Environmental Impact Form, please upload it as a pdf below.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The front page in the Excel file is the total project budget. The other pages (labeled NPI-1, NPI-2, etc; NPI = Network Principal Investigator) are for each involved NI. The budget requested by each NI should be filled in on their respective pages, including the partner contributions that are to be directed to their laboratories. The totals will populate automatically on the first page. <b><i>The project leader is responsible for combining all of the NI budgets into a single Excel file</i></b>. Failure to report on milestones will lead to loss of funding.</p>
                
                <b>Budget Guidelines:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Projects can request up to $150,000 for 12 months.</li>
                    <li>Projects require a 1:1.5 match with Partner funding; greater matching will be viewed more favorably; 50% of matching must be cash (for a $100,000 request, matching should be $150,000 with at least $75,000 cash and $75,000 in-kind – please see <a href='https://drive.google.com/file/d/1htIEuiU1weYrAB5g1DX4JTOKD3oM9KPX/view' target='_blank'><b>Appendix A</b></a>). Partner funding must be SSF eligible; in particular, other Canadian Federal funding is ineligible for matching</li>
                    <li>The maximum salary for Graduate Students is $30,000/year and for Postdoctoral Fellows is $55,000/year.</li>
                    <li>Trainee support should be limited to co-op students and should be listed in the technician line item.</li>
                    <li>Equipment is capped at $2,000/project.</li>
                    <li>Travel
                        <ul>
                            <li>Conference travel is capped at $3,000/year/NI/project. Note: Travel to the Annual General Meeting/Symposium is compulsory and will NOT be fully funded centrally through GlycoNet, as such, some travel funds should be kept for this purpose.</li>
                            <li>Travel and accommodation for trainees to visit collaborating labs should be included in project budgets.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Work with <b><a href='https://canadianglycomics.ca/integrated-services/' target='_blank'>GlycoNet Integrated Services</a></b>. Network investigators will receive a 20% discount on requested services. A quote can be provided upon request by <a href='mailto:coreservices@glyconet.ca'>coreservices@glyconet.ca</a></li>
                    <li>All partner contributions need to be supported by a letter from the partner institution (see below)
                        <ul>
                            <li>Based on federal funding guidelines, teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from federal sources cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching and a supporting letter documenting support is needed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Up to $5,000 of the requested budget can be used to reimburse expenses associated with development of a commercialization plan. These expenses should be budgeted under “Animal Work or Other Services”.</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="" template="GlycoNet Budget Template_SI 2025.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget_justification" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_BUD_JUSTIF">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provide concise, but sufficient, justification for expenses. Benefit rates for employees should be clearly stipulated.</li>
                    <li>The project leader is responsible for generating a single budget justification document containing information from all NI groups.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="milestones" name="Milestones" blobSection="CAT_MILESTONES" tooltip="Project Milestones" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_MIL_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet,application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    Please download the following <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/GlycoNet Milestones Template_SI 2025.xls"><b>Milestone Template</b></a> and upload it below.
                </p>
                <h3>Milestones Upload</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="commercial" name="Commercialization" blobSection="CAT_COMM" tooltip="Commercialization Plan" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_COMM_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Commercialization Plan Guidelines:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provided by the Technology Transfer Office of the Project Leader’s Institution.</li>
                    <li>Five pages maximum (2 cm (0.75 inch) margins, 11 point Times New Roman font (regular, not condensed) and a minimum of six lines per inch</li>
                    <li>The plan should address the following items:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Intellectual Property and Relevant Patents, or Patentability Strategy</li>
                            <li>Market</li>
                            <li>Barriers</li>
                            <li>Commercialization Opportunity</li>
                            <li>Competitive Advantage over other Technologies</li>
                            <li>Business Expertise</li>
                            <li>Commercialization Strategy</li>
                            <li>Timelines</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Letters" title="Partner Letters of Support" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Letters of Support" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 5 Partner Support Letters</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="security" name="Research Security" blobSection="CAT_SECURITY" tooltip="Research Security" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="attestation1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                <li>
                    <b>Fill in and upload the <a href='https://www.nserc-crsng.gc.ca/InterAgency-Interorganismes/RS-SR/_doc/Attestation_e.pdf' target='_blank'>Attestation Form</a> for each project member</b> (The research team includes researchers with named roles in the grant applications, as well as any other researchers involved in activities supported by the grant, such as highly qualified personnel (HQP), co-authors, or informal collaborators who may or may not be identified in the grant application. HQP can include undergraduate and graduate students, post-doctoral researchers, as well as research staff).
                    <div style='display:flex; width: 100%; margin-top: 1em;'>
                        <div style='width: 50%; min-width: 500px;'>
                            {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION3" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION4" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
                    </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION5" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                    <div style='width: 50%; min-width: 500px;'>
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION6" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION7" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attestation8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_ATTESTATION8" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                        {$item}
                    </div>
                </div></li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="private" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_PRIVATE" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <li id='private'>
                    Will the research involve a private sector partner organization?  (Partner organizations from a private sector (those that are not owned or operated by any order of government and include all for-profit organizations), including industrial associations and producer groups (since their member organizations are principally from the private sector)
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="risk" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SECURITY_RISK" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                    <li id='risk' style='display:none;'>
                        In case of involvement of a private sector partner in the project, fill in the <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/sites/default/files/attachments/2023/risk_assessment_form_ISED-ISDE3832E.pdf' target='_blank'><b>Risk Assessment Form</b></a> and upload it to the Forum. <br />
                        In case risks are identified in the Risk Assessment Form, develop a risk mitigation plan with the institution and must be submitted to GlycoNet.  One Risk Assessment Form is needed per project, developed with the Project Leader’s institution. It is also recommended to utilize existing government resources, such as <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/en/safeguarding-your-research' target='_blank'>Safeguarding Your Research</a> portal and particularly <a href='https://science.gc.ca/site/science/en/safeguarding-your-research/guidelines-and-tools-implement-research-security/mitigating-your-research-security-risks/what-steps-can-you-take-protect-your-research' target='_blank'>Mitigating Your Research Security Risks</a> page.
                    {$item}
                    </li>
                </ol>
                <div id='risk_no' style='display:none; margin-top: 1em;'>No further requirements</div>
                <script type='text/javascript'>
                    $('#private input').change(function(){
                        var privateValue = $('#private input:checked').val();
                        if(privateValue == "Yes"){
                            $('#risk').show();
                            $('#risk_no').hide();
                        }
                        else if(privateValue == "No"){
                            $('#risk').hide();
                            $('#risk_no').show();
                        }
                        else{
                            $('#risk').hide();
                            $('#risk_no').hide();
                        }
                    }).change();
                </script>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ccv" name="NI CCVs" blobSection="CAT_CCV" tooltip="Common CV" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 10 CCVs</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$my_email},vsharko@glyconet.ca" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
