<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="{$this_year} Translational Funding Application" reportType="RP_TRANS" pdfType="RPTP_TRANS" pdfFiles="TranslationalReportPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="NI">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="budget" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="milestones" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="letters" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="commercial" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="NI-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="budget" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="milestones" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="letters" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="commercial" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions and Deadline" name="Instructions" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="instructions" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A complete application consists of:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Project Description and References</li>
                    <li>Figures/Schemes (a single PDF file)</li>
                    <li>Budget (a single Excel file)</li>
                    <li>Budget Justification</li>
                    <li>Proposed Milestones (a single Excel File)</li>
                    <li>Letters of Support from Partners (as separate PDF Files, as separate PDF Files, Phase I, not required but encouraged; Phase II required)</li>
                    <li>CCV (CIHR Academic Format) for each Network Investigator (as separate PDF files)</li>
                    <li>Commercialisation plan provided by the Technology Transfer Office of the Project Leader’s Institution (a single PDF file).</li>
                </ol>
                <p><b>Deadline: Midnight PST Sunday, September 13, 2015</b></p>
                <p><b>Note: Protected Intellectual Property related to the project is required for both Phase I and Phase II applications.</b></p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="General Information about the project" name="Description" blobSection="CAT_DESC" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Project Description</h3>
                <p>You should include:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>A completed cover page</li>
                    <li>A project summary (500 words maximum)</li>
                    <li>A graphical abstract (included with Figures/Schemes, below)</li>
                    <li>A proposal (7000 words maximum, not including figure/scheme legends and references)</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Formatting requirements:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Use the following format for references (<i>Journal of Biological Chemistry style</i>):
                        <ul>
                            <li>Stover, C. K., de la Cruz, V. F., Fuerst, T. R., Burlein, J. E., Benson, L. A., Bennett, L. T., Bansal,
                                G. P., Young, J. F., Lee, M. H., Hatfull, G. F., Snapper, S. B., Barletta, R. G., Jacobs, W. R., Jr.,
                                and Bloom, B. R. (1991) New use of BCG for recombinant vaccines. Nature 351, 456–460
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Please include Figure and Scheme legends with the Figure or Scheme, not as a separate list. Please place each Figure/Scheme on its own page with the legend. All Figures should be uploaded as a single PDF file. The graphical abstract should be placed on the first page of the file, followed by Figures, Schemes and Tables, in that order.</li>
                    <li>Although there is no limit on Figures, Schemes, Tables and references, please use them judiciously.</li>
                    <li>The reference section should contain only bibliographical information, no Figures or key information about the approach you will take.</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <!-- Theme -->
        <ReportItem id="theme" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_THEME" orientation="vertical" options="Diabetes/Obesity|Therapeutic proteins/Vaccines|Chronic Disease|Antimicrobials|Rare Genetic diseases">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Theme</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Project Title -->
        <ReportItem id="title" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_TITLE" width="400px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Project Title</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Lead Investigator -->
        <ReportItem id="lead" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                              blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                              blobItem="CAT_DESC_LEAD" 
                              multiple="true" 
                              max="2" 
                              labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                              types="NI|text|text|text"
                              sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Lead Investigator</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Other Investigators -->
        <ReportItem id="other" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                               blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                               blobItem="CAT_DESC_OTHER" 
                               multiple="true" 
                               labels="Name|Affiliation|Phone|E-Mail" 
                               types="NI|text|text|text"
                               sizes="0|150|125|150">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Other Investigators</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Key Words -->
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" 
                                  blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" 
                                  blobItem="CAT_DESC_WORDS" 
                                  multiple="true" 
                                  labels="Key Word" 
                                  types="text"
                                  sizes="150"
                                  max="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Key Words</h2>
                <p>A minimum of 5 keywords must be provided.  There can be no more than 10 keywords</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc) -->
        <ReportItem id="part" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PART" multiple="true" labels="Name|Dollars requested|Partner Dollars: Cash|Partner Dollars: In-Kind" types="text|text|text|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Partners involved (Companies, agencies etc)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Suggested reviewers -->
        <ReportItem id="reviewers" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="CAT_DESC_REV" multiple="true" labels="Name|E-Mail|Affiliation" types="text|text|text|">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Suggested Reviewers</h2>
                Please suggest at least 5 reviewers for the application.  At least three of the five suggested reviewers must be working at locations outside of Canada. Suggested reviewers should not be members of the GlycoNet  Scientific Advisory Board or Research Management Committee.  In addition, the Network follows the <a target='_blank' href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/CIHR_Harmonized_COIC_Form-e.pdf'>CIHR/NSERC Conflict of Interest Policy</a>; please consult that policy before suggesting reviewers.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Question -->
        <ReportItem id="env_q" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV" orientation="horizontal" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Environmental Impact</h2>
                Does any phase of the research described in this proposal take place outside an office or a laboratory?
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Environmental Impact Upload -->
        <ReportItem id="env_u" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ENV_UP">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                If Yes, please go to the NSERC web site (<a href="http://www.nserc.ca" target="_blank">www.nserc.ca</a>) and obtain the environmental impact form (Appendix A), complete this and submit it with your application.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Conflict of Interest Question -->
        <ReportItem id="conflict_q" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_CONFLICT" orientation="horizontal" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Conflict of Interest</h2>
                Do any of the researchers involved in this project stand to receive a potential personal financial gain (i.e. ownership of shares in an industrial partner, consulting fees with industry partner, etc.) from the results of the proposed research?
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Conflict of Interest Multi -->
        <ReportItem id="conflict_which" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" optional="true" blobItem="CAT_DESC_CONFLICT_WHICH" multiple="true" labels="Name|Company" types="NI|text">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>If Yes, please indicate which researcher and the relevant company.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <!-- Conflict of Interest Companies -->
        <ReportItem id="conflict_comp" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" optional="true" blobItem="CAT_DESC_CONFLICT_COMP" multiple="true" labels="Company" types="text">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Will any company benefit substantially if this grant is awarded? If so, please identify the companies below</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="resub" type="RadioReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_RESUB" options="Yes|No">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Is this application a resubmission of a previously unsuccessful GlycoNet grant</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="response" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_RESPONSE" rich="true" limit="2000">
            <![CDATA[
                <script type="text/javascript">
                    var resub = function(){
                        var value = $("input[name=Description_resub]:checked").val();
                        if(value == "Yes"){
                            $("#response_div").show();
                        }
                        else{
                            $("#response_div").hide();
                        }
                    }
                    $("input[name=Description_resub]").change(resub);
                    resub();
                </script>
                <div id="response_div">
                    <p>Please provide a response to the previous reviews</p>
                    {$item}
                </div>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_SUMMARY" rich="true" height="300px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Summary (500 words maximum)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>

        <ReportItem id="abstract_upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_ABSTRACT_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Graphical Abstract</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="proposal" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_DESC_PROPOSAL" rich="true" height="300px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project Proposal (7000 words maximum)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget" blobSection="CAT_BUDGET" tooltip="Project Budget" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget (provide as a single Excel file)</h3>
                <p>The front page in the excel file is the total project budget. The other pages (labeled NPI-1, NPI-2 etc; NPI = Network Principal Investigator) are for each involved PI. The budget requested by each PI should be filled in on their respective pages, including the partner contributions that are to be directed to their laboratories. The totals will populate automatically on the first page. The project leader is responsible for combining all of the PI budgets into a single excel file. The first page also contains the budget for the use of the core services in the project.</p> 
                <p><b><i>The project leader should coordinate the core services budget for the project.</i></b> If you are asked for a password when entering a number, you are attempting to enter a number in a field that will automatically populate.</p>
                <p>Budget Guidelines:<p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Projects can request up to $200,000 (Phase I) or $300,000 (Phase II) for 12 months; longer time periods will be considered on a case-by-case basis and only with sufficient justification.</li>
                    <li>The maximum salary for Graduate Students is $25,000/year and for Postdoctoral Fellows is $42,000/year.</li>
                    <li>Undergraduate student support should be limited to co-op students and should be listed in the technician line item.</li>
                    <li>Equipment is capped at $2,000/year/project.</li>
                    <li>Travel
                        <ul>
                            <li>Conference travel is capped at $1,500/year/PI/project.</li>
                            <li>Travel and accommodation for trainees to visit collaborating labs should be included in project budgets.</li>
                            <li>Travel to the annual general meeting will be funded centrally through the Network. It should not be incorporated into project budgets.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>HTS Core
                        <ul>
                            <li>You should work with one of the Network screening partners (CDRD, McMaster HTS lab, SPARC) to develop a budget and a plan of action (i.e., milestones). These costs should be incorporated into the project budget.</li>
                            <li>Funding for the screen itself will go to the screening partner. The development of the assay can be done either at the screening partner, or in the lab of a PI (to be determined in your discussions with the screening partner), with the funding going to the location where the work will be carried out. Please note that all projects will need to develop not only a primary screening method but also a secondary screening method for hit validation.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Glycan Screening, Glycan Synthesis and Glycan Structure Analysis Cores
                        <ul>
                            <li>Those of you who have an anticipated need for these core services should contact Todd Lowary(<a href='mailto:tlowary@ualberta.ca'>tlowary@ualberta.ca</a>) by August 15, 2015. We will generate an estimate that can be incorporated into the budget.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>All partner contributions need to be supported by a letter from the partner institution (see below).
                        <ul>
                            <li>Based on NCE guidelines, teaching assistantship support cannot be counted as matching. Similarly, student and PDF fellowships from CIHR, NSERC or SSHRC cannot be counted as matching. Therefore, please do not include these as a partner contribution in your budget. Research fellowships provided by universities or non-federal agencies should be listed as matching and a supporting letter documenting support is needed.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Up to $5000 of the requested budget can be used to reimburse expenses associated with development of a commercialisation plan. These expenses should be budgeted under “Animal Work or Other Services”.</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <p>Guidelines:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Please provide concise, but sufficient, justification for expenses. Benefit rates for employees should be clearly stipulated.</li>
                    <li><b><i>The project leader is responsible for generating a single budget justification document containing information from all PI groups.</i></b></li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_BUD_UPLOAD" structure="GLYCONET_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="GlycoNet Budget Template.xls">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget_justification" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAT_BUD_JUSTIF">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="milestones" name="Milestones" blobSection="CAT_MILESTONES" tooltip="Project Milestones" type="ReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Milestones (provide as a single Excel file)</h3>
                <p>Guidelines:
                    <ul>
                        <li>Quarterly milestones should be provided and should contain sufficient detail that progress toward them can be clearly monitored.</li>
                        <li><b><i>The project leader is responsible for combining all of the milestones into a single excel file.</i></b></li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="upload" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="CAT_MIL_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet,application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    Please download the following <a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/GlycoNet%20Milestones.xls">milestone template</a> and upload it below.
                </p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="letters" name="Partner Letters" blobSection="CAT_SUPPORT" tooltip="Partner Support Letters" type="ReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Partner Support Letters (provide as a separate PDF files)</h3>
                <p>A letter must be provided supporting all partner contributions listed in the budget. Inclusion of Partners are required for Phase II and optional, but encouraged, for Phase I.<br />
                Letters must:
                <ul>
                    <li>Come from a senior executive with signing authority for the contributions being committed.</li>
                    <li>Indicate the amount, duration, and nature (cash and/or in-kind) of support for the project.</li>
                    <li>Be on partner letterhead, be dated and signed within the past two months.</li>
                </ul>
                </p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 5 Partner Support Letters</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_SUP_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ccv" name="NI CCVs" blobSection="CAT_CCV" tooltip="Common CV" type="ReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Common CV (provide as a separate PDF files)</h3>
                <p>Upload the CCV PDF files for the NIs on this project.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You can upload up to 10 CCVs</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload6" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD6" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload7" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD7" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload8" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD8" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload9" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD9" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload10" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_CCV_UPLOAD10" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="commercial" name="Commercialization" blobSection="CAT_COMM" tooltip="Commercialization Plan" type="ReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Commercialization Plan (provide as a single PDF file)</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>Provided by the Technology Transfer Office of the Project Leader’s Institution.</li>
                    <li>Five pages maximum (2 cm (0.75 inch) margins, 12 point Times New Roman font (regular, not condensed) and a minimum of six lines per inch</li>
                    <li>The plan should address the following items:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Intellectual Property and Relevant Patents</li>
                            <li>Market</li>
                            <li>Barriers</li>
                            <li>Commercialization Opportunity</li>
                            <li>Competitive Advantage over other Technologies</li>
                            <li>Business Expertise</li>
                            <li>Commercialization Strategy</li>
                            <li>Timelines</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CAT_COMM_UPLOAD" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The intent of <b><i>Review</i></b> page is to provide
                <ul>
                  <li>an online document with all the information currently contained in the report, and </li>
                  <li>an online approximation of what the resulting PDF document will look like. </li>
                </ul>
                If you are satisfied with this content, then you can proceed to the final step of the reporting workflow where you can <b><i>Submit</i></b> your report to be forwarded to the RMC.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission to the RMC" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[

            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="review" type="ReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
