<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Mind the Gap" reportType="RP_MTG" pdfType="RPTP_MTG" pdfFiles="MindTheGapPDF" ajax="true">
    <Permissions>
        <Role start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" role="PNI">
            <SectionPermission id="intro" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="music" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="firstnations" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="socialproblems" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="other" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" role="CNI">
            <SectionPermission id="intro" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="music" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="firstnations" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="socialproblems" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="other" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="intro" name="Mind the Gap" tooltip="" blobSection="MTG_INTRO" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="intro" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>GRAND has identified a set of projects that will form the basis for the research program in Phase 2 of the GRAND NCE. These span a diverse set of areas in which digital media is impacting Canadian society. As part of the ongoing planning effort for the renewal application, GRAND is identifying critical areas that may not currently be in its portfolio. Your help is being enlisted.</p>
                <p>If you are working in one of the areas below, please provide us some information about the nature of your involvement, any partners or collaborators that you have, the source(s) of funding for the work, the connection to digital media, the opportunities you think exist for future GRAND research, and whether the work is currently associated with a Phase 1 or Phase 2 GRAND project.</p>
                <p>Each tab has a short description of the area of research that might be underway or needed within the GRAND research portfolio. The “Other” tab can be used to provide information on additional areas (one or more) that are not included in the existing tabs. The descriptions are purposely open-ended and should be interpreted broadly.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="music" name="Music" tooltip="" blobSection="MTG_MUSIC" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="music" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One of the earliest impacts of digital media on consumer culture was the switch from analog to digital recording and distribution of music. There has been a long history of electronic music composition and performance, which pre-dates the digital era but which has seen significant innovations since the advent of digital media tools. These and other technological changes have triggered significant social, economic, and legal responses.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="music_text" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="MTG_MUSIC">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="firstnations" name="First Nations" tooltip="" blobSection="MTG_FIRST_NATIONS" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="firstnations" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>There is widespread activity within aboriginal communities across Canada and world-wide to explore digital media as a means of reclaiming and celebrating their distinct cultures, and also as a tool for economic development.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="firstnations_text" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="MTG_FIRST_NATIONS">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="socialproblems" name="Social Problems" tooltip="" blobSection="MTG_SOCIAL_PROBLEMS" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="socialproblems" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Digital media has brought many improvements to quality of life, but it has also introduced or exacerbated a number of social problems, such as addictive game play, over-indulgence in social media, and cyber-bullying.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="socialproblems_text" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="MTG_SOCIAL_PROBLEMS">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="other" name="Other" tooltip="" blobSection="MTG_OTHER" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="other" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Areas of importance in digital media that are not currently part of GRAND’s research portfolio but should be can be noted here. (Please clearly indicate the beginning of the description for each area if more than one is provided.)</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="other_text" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="MTG_OTHER">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" name="Submit" tooltip="" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
