<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report pdfFiles="Letters/12" extends="Letters/Base">
    <ReportSection id="letter" title="End of First Probationary Period - No Further Appointment">
        <ReportItem id="body">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This is to inform you that the Faculty Evaluation Committee (FEC) did not support your Department Chair’s recommendation to award tenure and has made a preliminary decision that no further appointment be offered to you at the end of your first probationary period.</p>
                
                <p>Pursuant to Article A.6.19.1, this is the preliminary position of FEC which enables you to request a reconsideration by FEC.</p>
                
                <p>The matters of concern to FEC were as follows:</p>
                <p>{getText({$report_type}, TABLE, COMMENT, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}</p>
                
                <p>I was advised by your Department Chair that they continue to support their original recommendation to award tenure now support the preliminary position of the FEC to offer no further appointment.</p>
                
                You may wish to consider the following options:
                <ul style='margin-left: 1em;'>
                    <li>Pursuant to Article A6.19.3 of Schedule A, I am able to meet with you during the week of {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)} to discuss your individual case, as it was presented before FEC. Please contact my office at sciea@ualberta.ca for an appointment.</li>
                    <li>Pursuant to Article A6.20.1 of Schedule A, you have the right to request reconsideration of the FEC’s preliminary decision by informing me, in writing, within 5 working days from the receipt of this letter.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>It is advisable that you consult the Association of Academic Staff University of Alberta (AASUA) for advice.</p>
                
                <p>If you have your case reconsidered by FEC and they stand by their preliminary decision, you have the right to appeal this decision to the General Appeals Committee (GAC) under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A.</p>
                
                <p>Should you choose not to have your case reconsidered by FEC, in accordance with A6.20.2 the preliminary position of FEC shall become the final and binding decision of FEC. Thus, your appointment with the {$user_dept} at the University of Alberta will terminate effective June 30, {$next_year}. You would be entitled to severance in accordance with Article A5.06 of Schedule A.</p>
                
                <p>If you have any procedural questions, please contact the FEC Administrator, Lakhan Khara, at sciea@ualberta.ca.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
