<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="KT Intent Review" reportType="RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2019">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="EVALUATOR">
            <SectionPermission id="eula" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="ex_review" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="RMC">
            <SectionPermission id="eula" permissions="-" />
            <SectionPermission id="ex_review" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="KTC">
            <SectionPermission id="eula" permissions="-" />
            <SectionPermission id="ex_review" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="eula" name="Agreement" title="Confidentiality Agreement" tooltip="Confidentiality Agreement" blobSection="KT_EULA" type="EULA">
        <ReportItem id="eula" type="EULA" blobItem="EULA" yes="&lt;b&gt;Yes&lt;/b&gt;, I agree to abide by the confidentiality agreement" 
                                                          no="&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt;, I do not agree to abide by the confidentiality agreement">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>CONFIDENTIALITY AGREEMENT</b>
                <p>This Confidentiality Agreement is given to the Canadian Frailty Network (CFN) in consideration of my role as a Grant Reviewer to review grant application(s) (Information) for CFN.</p>
                <p>I acknowledge that as part of my role as a Grant Reviewer for CFN I may be given access to information that is of a personal, confidential and/ or proprietary nature, for example: names, e-mail addresses, financial information, funding applications and their status, trade secrets, research data, and any other information for the purpose of fulfilling my obligations.</p>
                <p>I, therefore agree:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>To hold all Information in trust and strict confidence and agree that it shall be used only for the purposes required to fulfill my role as a Grant Reviewer, and shall not be used for any other purpose, or disclosed to any third party.</li>
                    <li>To keep all Information in my control or possession in a secure location to which only I and other persons who are authorized to view this information, and have signed a confidentiality agreement with CFN, have access.</li>
                    <li>To take all necessary steps to keep all Information secure and to protect such Information from unauthorized use, reproduction or disclosure.</li>
                    <li>To maintain the absolute confidentiality of all Information in recognition of the privacy and proprietary rights of others at all times.</li>
                    <li>To comply with all privacy laws and regulations, which apply to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information.</li>
                    <li>At the conclusion of my role as a Grant Reviewer, or upon demand by CFN, to return all Information, including prototypes, code, written notes, photographs, sketches, models, memoranda or notes taken, to CFN’s possession and the responsible manager/director.</li>
                    <li>Not to disclose any Information to any employee, consultant or third party unless they agree to execute and be bound by the terms of this agreement and have been approved by CFN in an official, legal capacity.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>I understand that a breach of confidentiality or misuse of Information could result legal action.</p>
                <p>I understand that this Agreement survives the termination of my relationship with CFN.</p>
                <p>The laws of Ontario, Canada shall govern this Agreement and its validity, construction and effect.</p>
                <p>I fully understand and accept responsibilities set above relating to personal, confidential and/or proprietary Information:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Personal Information is any information about an "identifiable individual".</li>
                    <li>Confidential Information is any information which is designated by CFN as confidential.</li>
                    <li>Proprietary Information is any information which is designated by CFN as proprietary like trade secrets, and research data.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ex_review" name="External Review" blobSection="KT_EX_REVIEW" tooltip="Review of KT Grants" type="EditableReportSection" saveText="Save &amp; Submit">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <ol>
                    <li>Please score all sections.  You can use decimals in your scores.</li>
                    <li>Overall competition goal: To advance evidence into practice thereby, ultimately strengthening Canada's healthcare system and improving care of Canadians living with frailty.</li>
                    <li>Priority areas for this competition are: 1) Integrated models of care to improve frailty outcomes, and 2) Strategies for improving functional outcomes in older adults living with frailty</li>
                    <li>Although these are the two priorities, the LOI should be considered even if is does not fit in one of the two.</li>
                    <li>Adjudication based on the importance of the endeavour, feasibility of the implementation plan, and potential reach. Only top-rated projects will be invited to submit a full application.</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItemSet id="if_eula" type="If" if="{or({or({or({==({getText(RP_KT_REVIEW,KT_EULA,EULA,0,{$user_id},0)},Yes)},
                                                          {contains({$user_full_roles},ISAC)}
                                                         )},
                                                      {contains({$user_full_roles},KTC)})},
                                                  {contains({$user_full_roles},RMC)})}">
            <ReportItemSet id="project_materials" type="MaterialsReportItemSet" subType="KT_INTENT-EX" class="Person">
                <ReportItemSet id="toggle" type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" title="{getText(RP_KT_APPLICATION,INTENT,TITLE,0,{$user_id},0)} - {$user_name}">
                    <ReportItem id="table" type="PDFReportItem" reportType="KT2019Intent" buttonName="Download Application">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <div id="proj{$user_id}">
                            <table class='wikitable'>
                                <tr><td><b>Project Leader:</b></td><td>{getArray(RP_KT_APPLICATION,INTENT,PL,0,{$user_id},0,pl|0|firstname)} {getArray(RP_KT_APPLICATION,INTENT,PL,0,{$user_id},0,pl|0|lastname)}</td></tr>
                                <tr><td><b>Project Title:</b></td><td>{getText(RP_KT_APPLICATION,INTENT,TITLE,0,{$user_id},0)}</td></tr>
                            </table>
                            {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="q1" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="Q1" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="Radio" options="Yes|No|Unsure" optional="true">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p><b>Q1: Knowledge translation (KT) is about raising knowledge users' awareness of research findings and facilitating the use of those findings. In your opinion, does this proposal describe a KT project?</b></p>
                            {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="q2" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="Q2" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="Radio" options="Yes|No|Unsure" optional="true">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p><b>Q2: If no, would this proposal be more appropriate for a research competition?</b>
                            {$item}</p>
                            <p class='info'>Please enter a score from 0 to 4 in each input box below for each criteria.  Scores can include up to two decimal places.</p>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <!--ReportItem id="ex_1" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="KT_EX_1" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="IntegerReportItem" size="5" align="left" max="4" min="0" decimals="2">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <h2>1. Partnerships</h2>
                            <p>Do the applicants have the appropriate partners to carry out the study?</p>
                            <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width='23%'>Unacceptable<br />
                                        <small>(score = 0)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Borderline<br />
                                        <small>(score = 1)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Good/Solid<br />
                                        <small>(score = 3)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Excellent<br />
                                        <small>(score = 4)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='8%'>Your score<br />
                                        <small>(Max 4)</small></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Applicants have not established partnerships for the proposed study.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Many of the partners appear to be inappropriate (i.e., lack the expertise, experience etc...) for the planned study.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Most partners appear to be appropriate (i.e., have the expertise, experience etc...) for the planned study.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>All partners appear to be appropriate (i.e., have the expertise, experience etc...) for the planned study.</td>
                                    <td align='center'>{$item}</td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_1_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_1_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>Comments: Please provide comments to justify your score:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem-->
                    
                    <ReportItem id="ex_2" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="KT_EX_2" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="IntegerReportItem" size="5" align="left" max="4" min="0" decimals="2">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <h2>1. Fit with CFN research objectives and themes</h2>
                            <p>How well does the applicant describe how the study will contribute to advancing health-related knowledge, health research, health care, health systems and/or health outcomes related to the care of Canadians living with frailty?</p>
                            <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width='23%'>Unacceptable<br />
                                        <small>(score = 0)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Borderline<br />
                                        <small>(score = 1)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Good/Solid<br />
                                        <small>(score = 3)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Excellent<br />
                                        <small>(score = 4)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='8%'>Your score<br />
                                        <small>(Max 4)</small></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>It is not clear how the study relates to Canadians living with frailty and/or it is not clear how will improve care for Canadians living with frailty.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The study is somewhat relevant to Canadians living with frailty.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The study is clearly relevant to Canadians living with frailty.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The study is highly relevant to Canadians living with frailty and fits in one of the two priority areas for this competition.</td>
                                    <td align='center'>{$item}</td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_2_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_2_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>Comments: Please provide comments to justify your score:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    
                    <ReportItem id="ex_3" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="KT_EX_3" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="IntegerReportItem" size="5" align="left" max="4" min="0" decimals="2">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <h2>2. Importance of the Endeavour</h2>
                            <p>What is the evidence supporting the care or quality gap? Does it merit a KT intervention at this time? Are the outcomes described achievable, measurable and important?</p>
                            <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width='23%'>Unacceptable<br />
                                        <small>(score = 0)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Borderline<br />
                                        <small>(score = 1)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Good/Solid<br />
                                        <small>(score = 3)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Excellent<br />
                                        <small>(score = 4)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='8%'>Your score<br />
                                        <small>(Max 4)</small></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Insufficient evidence or evidence of low quality supports the KT proposal. Care or quality gap is unclear.  Outputs not described.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Some evidence to support the KT proposal is described. The care or quality gap  is reasonably described. Outcomes may not not measurable, are incompletely described or are not important.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>Good evidence supports the KT proposal is presented with a clearly described care or quality gap. Outcomes are described, are measurable and important.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>There is strong evidence supporting the KT proposal. The care or quality gap  is clearly articulated.  Outcomes are readilty measurable, achievable and are very important.</td>
                                    <td align='center'>{$item}</td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_3_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_3_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>Comments: Please provide comments to justify your score:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    
                    <ReportItem id="ex_4" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="KT_EX_4" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="IntegerReportItem" size="5" align="left" max="4" min="0" decimals="2">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <h2>3. Feasibility of the Approach and Implementation Plan</h2>
                            <p>How well does the applicant describe the study so that it addresses the care or quality gap?  The applicant was asked to: a. describe the approaches and methods used in the study,  and b. describe the involvement of knowledge users, decision makers, researchers, and partnering organizations. Applicants were also asked to include a timeline and milestones.</p>
                            <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width='23%'>Unacceptable<br />
                                        <small>(score = 0)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Borderline<br />
                                        <small>(score = 1)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Good/Solid<br />
                                        <small>(score = 3)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Excellent<br />
                                        <small>(score = 4)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='8%'>Your score<br />
                                        <small>(Max 4)</small></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>There is significant concern about meeting the goals and objectives of the study based on the approach described.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The approach for meeting the study goals and objectives is reasonable but needs improvement.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The approach for meeting the study goals and objectives is reasonable, and uses an appropriate KT strategy.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>A comprehensive approach for meeting the study goals and objectives is well described, is excellent and uses an appropriate KT strategy.</td>
                                    <td align='center'>{$item}</td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_4_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_4_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>Comments: Please provide comments to justify your score:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    
                    <ReportItem id="ex_5" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="KT_EX_5" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" type="IntegerReportItem" size="5" align="left" max="4" min="0" decimals="2">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <h2>4. Budget Amount and Potential Impact</h2>
                            <p>Does the potential impact of the study justify the requested total study budget?  How well will the impact of the study will be measured and evaluated? Note that there was no maximum budget amount stipulated to applicants and thus applicants were advised that increasing budgetary requests will be expected to produce a proportionately greater impact and will undergo commensurate scrutiny as to their ability to achieve these impacts.</p>
                            <table class='wikitable' width='100%'>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width='23%'>Unacceptable<br />
                                        <small>(score = 0)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Borderline<br />
                                        <small>(score = 1)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Good/Solid<br />
                                        <small>(score = 3)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='23%'>Excellent<br />
                                        <small>(score = 4)</small>
                                    </th>
                                    <th width='8%'>Your score<br />
                                        <small>(Max 4)</small></th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>The impact of the study is expected to be minimal.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>This study will have impact but the requested budget is likely inappropiate given the potential impact.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>This study will have impact and the requested budget is likely appropiate given the potential impact.</td>
                                    <td class='small' valign='top'>This study will have a large impact and the requested budget is very appropiate given the potential impact.</td>
                                    <td align='center'>{$item}</td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_5_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_5_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>Comments: Please provide comments to justify your score:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    
                    <ReportItem id="total1" type="StaticReportItem">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <p style='font-size:125%;background: #EEEEEE;padding:2px;'>
                                <b id="proj{$user_id}_total">
                                    {add({getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_2,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                         {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_3,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                         {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_4,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                         {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_5,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)}
                                    )}
                                </b> (Score out of 16)</p>
                            <p style='font-size:125%;background: #EEEEEE;padding:2px;'>
                                <b id="proj{$user_id}_total5">
                                    {round(
                                        {multiply(
                                            {divide(
                                                {add({getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_2,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                                     {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_3,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                                     {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_4,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)},
                                                     {getNumber(RP_KT_INTENT_REVIEW,KT_EX_REVIEW,KT_EX_5,{$user_id},{$my_id},0)}
                                                )}
                                            , 16)}
                                        , 5)}
                                    ,2 )}
                                </b> (Score converted out of 5)</p>
                            <script type="text/javascript">
                                $("#proj{$user_id} input[type=text]").change(function(){
                                    var total = 0;
                                    $("#proj{$user_id} input[type=text]").each(function(i, v){
                                        if(!_.isNaN(parseFloat($(v).val()))){
                                            total += parseFloat($(v).val());
                                        }
                                    });
                                    $("#proj{$user_id}_total").html(Math.round(total*100)/100);
                                    $("#proj{$user_id}_total5").html(Math.round((total/16)*4*100)/100 );
                                });
                            </script>
                            </div>
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                    <ReportItem id="ex_comments" type="Textarea" blobItem="KT_EX_COMMENTS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" optional="true">
                        <![CDATA[
                            <b>General Comments - Please provide any general comments that are not captured in above section:</b> {$item}
                        ]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
        <ReportItem id="if_not_eula" type="If" if="{and({and({and({!=({getText(RP_KT_REVIEW,KT_EULA,EULA,0,{$user_id},0)},Yes)},
                                                            {!contains({$user_full_roles},ISAC)}
                                                           )},
                                                       {!contains({$user_full_roles},KTC)})},
                                                   {!contains({$user_full_roles},RMC)})}">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You need to accept the confidentiality agreement before you have access to any of the review materials.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="dialog" type="SaveDialogReportItem" message="Thank you for submitting your External Review.">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
