<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AVOID Frailty Regional Centres for Healthy Aging (RCHA) Grants Competition" reportType="RP_RCHA_APPLICATION" pdfType="RP_RCHA_APPLICATION" pdfFiles="RCHA2021ApplicationPDF" year="2021">
    <ReportSection id="information" type="HeaderReportSection" blobSection="INFORMATION" name="1 - Admin Information" title="Section 1 - Administrative Information">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <img class='logo' style="position:static; float:right;margin-top:0;" src='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/skins/{$networkName}_Logo.png' />
                <h4 style='font-size:1.20em;'>AVOID Frailty Regional Centres for Healthy Aging (RCHA) Grants Competition</h4>
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
                <br />
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="bookmark" type="Bookmark" title="Section 1 - Administrative Information">
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="file_number" blobItem="FILE_NUMBER" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1>Section 1 - Administrative Information</h1>
                <table class="wikitable" frame="box" rules="all" style="width:100%">
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <b>CFN File Number:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>{$item}</td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="title" blobItem="TITLE" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <b>Title of KT Proposal provided in Intent to Apply:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>{$item}</td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="cfn_type" blobItem="CFN_TYPE" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Indicate the CFN Research Grant that this KT proposal builds upon.</b>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        &nbsp;&nbsp;Type of CFN Grant:
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="cfn_title" blobItem="CFN_TITLE" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        &nbsp;&nbsp;CFN Grant Title:
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="cfn_pl" blobItem="CFN_PL" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        &nbsp;&nbsp;CFN Grant Project Leader:
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="term" blobItem="TERM" type="Integer" min="0" max="24">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <b>Term of KT Proposal:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>{$item}</td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" blobItem="BUDGET" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <b>Budget:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>{$item}</td>
                    </tr>
                </table><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="first_name" blobItem="FIRST_NAME" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Please provide information on the Principal Investigator who will act as Project Leader for proposal</h2>
                <table class="wikitable" frame="box" rules="all" style="width: 100%;">
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>First Name:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="last_name" blobItem="LAST_NAME" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Last Name:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="designations" blobItem="DESIGNATIONS" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Designations:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="email" blobItem="EMAIL" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Email:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="day_phone" blobItem="DAY_PHONE" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Daytime Phone:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="other_phone" blobItem="OTHER_PHONE" type="Text" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Other Phone (optional):</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="institution" blobItem="INSTITUTION" type="Text" width='250px'>
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td colspan='3' align="right">
                            <b>Host Institution that will receive and administer funds:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td colspan='3'>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="contact_name" blobItem="CONTACT_NAME" type="Text" width='250px'>
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right">
                            <b>Secondary Contact Name:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td colspan="2">
                            {$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="contact_phone" blobItem="CONTACT_PHONE" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td colspan="2" align="right">
                            <b>Secondary Telephone Number:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="contact_email" blobItem="CONTACT_EMAIL" type="Text">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td colspan="3"></td>
                        <td colspan="2" align="right">
                            <b>Secondary Email:</b>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            {$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="objective" type="Radio" blobItem="OBJECTIVE" options="Matching care to values|Empowering, engaging and supporting patients and their families/caregivers|Improving clinical outcomes|Improving care across the continuum">
            <![CDATA[
                <table class="wikitable" frame="box" rules="all" style="width: 100%;">
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top"><b>CFN Strategic Objective:</b>{$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="theme" type="Radio" blobItem="THEME" options="Improved end-of-life care/advance care planning|Improved acute/critical care|Optimization of community/residential care|Optimization of transitions of care">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td valign="top"><b>Theme:</b>{$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="care" type="Radio" blobItem="CARE" options="Palliative/EOL care|Acute/critical care in hospital|Long-term care facility|Home care">
            <![CDATA[
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top"><b>Setting of Care:</b>{$item}
                        </td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="impact" type="Radio" blobItem="IMPACT" options="Patients, their families and informal caregivers/support systems (volunteer)|Health care professionals and caregivers (paid)|Health care facilities|Health care system">
            <![CDATA[
                        <td valign="top"><b>Focus of Impact:</b>{$item}
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ethics" blobItem="ETHICS" type="Radio" options="Yes, I expect that this research will require an ethics review|No, I do not expect that this research will require an ethics review">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Ethics/Environmental Assessment</h2>
                <p><small><i>Please answer the two questions below.</i></small></p>
                <ol>
                    <li><b>Ethics Approval:</b> <small><i>If the proposed study involves biohazards, humans, human embryonic stem cells or animals, AND is funded by CFN, certification of approval by your institutional certification committee must be provided to CFN prior to the release of funds</i></small><br />{$item}</li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="assessment" blobItem="ASSESSMENT" type="Radio" options="Yes, I expect that this research will require an environmental impact review|No, I do not expect that this research will require an environmental impact review">
            <![CDATA[
                    <li><b>Environmental Assessment:</b> <small><i>Does any phase or part of the research described in this proposal a) take place outside an office or laboratory, or b) involve an undertaking as described in part 1 of Appendix B of the Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council of Canada (NSERC) Form 101 (<a href='http://www.nserc-crsng.gc.ca/OnlineServices-ServicesEnLigne/pdf/F101_e.pdf' target='_blank'>http://www.nserc-crsng.gc.ca/OnlineServices-ServicesEnLigne/pdf/F101_e.pdf</a>)?.</i></small><br />{$item}</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="summary" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="SUMMARY" name="2 - Proposal Summary" title="Section 2 - Proposal Summary">
        <ReportItem id="lay_summary" blobItem="LAY_SUMMARY" type="Textarea" limit="350" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2.1: Lay Summary</h2>
                <p><small><i>Provide a non-confidential summary in lay terms of the KT proposal.  A lay summary is an overview of a research project described in a way that can be easily understood by those without prior experience of the subject. It is not a slight modification of the scientific abstract or a simplification of the study; a well-written lay summary allows the public to understand research and its value, impact, and applications. Lay summaries also help juries evaluate research grant applications and facilitate use of the research by government, the public and private sectors, and the community at large. (For funded KT proposals, this summary will be used externally in media releases, communications and posted on the CFN’s website.)</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="sci_summary" blobItem="SCI_SUMMARY" type="Textarea" limit="350" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2.2: Scientific Summary</h2>
                <p><small><i>Provide a non-confidential scientific summary of the KT proposal, highlighting the study objectives, milestones and deliverables and potential socioeconomic impact. (For funded KT proposals, this summary will be used externally in media releases, communications and posted on the CFN’s website.)</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="proposal" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="PROPOSAL" name="3 - KT Proposal" title="Section 3 - KT Proposal">
        <ReportItem id="quality" blobItem="QUALITY" type="Textarea" limit="1100" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3.1: Concept</h2>
                <h3>3.1.1: Quality of the Idea</h3>
                <small><i>
                <ol type="a">
                    <li>Please describe any success stories or real-world impacts that resulted from prior KT activities related to the prior CFN-funded research project and also discuss the relevancy of this KT proposal to the prior research project.  Note that the information you provide may be used publicly for external CFN communications (e.g., CFN website, CFN newsletter, social media).</li>
                    <li>Please clearly describe the overall goal and objectives of the study and provide distinct outputs that support advances in health-related knowledge, health research, health care, health systems, and/or health outcomes for the care of Canadians living with frailty.</li>
                    <li>Please clearly describe the hypothesis and rationale of the study and articulate why this proposal is considered to have the potential to change the care of older Canadians living with frailty.</li>
                    <li>Please clearly describe how you plan on measuring and evaluating the impact of your proposal on the care of older adults living with frailty.</li>
                </ol>
                </i></small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="importance" blobItem="IMPORTANCE" type="Textarea" limit="425" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>3.1.2: Importance of the Idea</h3>
                <p><small><i>Please clearly describe how the study will contribute to advancing health-related knowledge, health research, health care, health systems and/or health outcomes related to the care of Canadians living with frailty.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="approach" blobItem="APPROACH" type="Textarea" limit="3700" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3.2: Feasibility</h2>
                <h3>3.2.1: Approach</h3>
                <small><i>
                <ol type="a">
                    <li>Please describe the approaches and methods used in this study and why they are appropriate to meet the goals and objectives and deliver upon the proposed output(s). The proposal should be developed using an appropriate KT strategy based on a KT framework identified in the April 2012 Knowledge Translation Framework for Ageing and Health from the World Health Organization (<a href='http://www.who.int/ageing/publications/knowledge_translation.pdf' target='_blank'>http://www.who.int/ageing/publications/knowledge_translation.pdf</a>).  In addition to the budget justification you provided in the budget template, please provide any additional budget justification as it relates to the approaches and methods.</li>
                    <li>Please provide timelines showing when goals, objectives and outputs will be reached.  In addition to the budget justification you provided in the budget template, please provide any additional budget justification as it relates to the goals, objectives and outputs.</li>
                    <li>Please describe the potential barriers and challenges related to achieving the proposed goals and objectives and how you intend on overcoming these barriers and challenges.  What is your mitigation strategy?</li>
                </ol>
                </i></small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="expertise" blobItem="EXPERTISE" type="Textarea" limit="825" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>3.2.2: Expertise, Experience and Resources</h3>
                <small><i>
                <ol type="a">
                    <li>Please describe the expertise and experience of each Principal Investigator, Co-investigator, Partner and other critical team member to show that he/she can lead and deliver on the proposed outputs and achieve the goals and objectives of this proposal.</li>
                    <li>Please provide an estimate on the number of hours per week (contribution) for each Principal Investigator, Co-investigator, Partner and other critical team member that will be working on the study and describe why this is an appropriate level of engagement and/or commitment to deliver the proposed outputs and achieve the goals and objectives of this proposal. (Note: All Individuals participating as project team members will also need to be listed in the Project Team List document).</li>
                    <li>For each Principal Investigator, Co-investigator, Partner and other critical team member please describe why the environment (academic institution and/or other organization) is appropriate to enable the conduct and success of the project?</li>
                </ol>
                </i></small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" blobItem="HQP" type="Textarea" limit="425" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3.3: Capacity Building - Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP)</h2>
                <p><small><i>CFN funded proposals must contribute to the development of HQP through their inclusion as fully involved team members. Describe the number of HQP and their level of training/experience and role/activities for the study and the number of hours per week that each will be working on the study.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="networking" blobItem="NETWORKING" type="Textarea" limit="825" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3.4: Project Networking and Engagement</h2>
                <small><i>
                <ol type="a">
                    <li>Describe the networking and engagement planned for this project across disciplines and sectors. Projects must represent a collaborative effort of different Investigators in more than one discipline and at more than one Institution.</li>
                    <li>Describe how knowledge users (e.g. patients/families, decision makers, stakeholders, practitioners) will be involved in the KT study in a meaningful manner.  For clarity, meaningfully involved participation of knowledge users includes assisting in the planning and execution of the study.</li>
                </ol>
                </i></small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="additional" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="CV" name="4 - Additional Information" title="Section 4 - Additional Information">
        <ReportItem id="references" blobItem="REFERENCES" type="Textarea" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>References</h3>
                <p><small><i>Please provide all references referred to in Section 3.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="figures" blobItem="FIGURES" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Tables and Figures</h3>
                <p><small><i>Upload a single PDF document containing all tables and figures.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="partnerships" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="PARTNERSHIPS" name="5 - Partnerships" title="Section 5 - Partnerships &amp; Letters of Support">
        <ReportItem id="partners" blobItem="PARTNERS" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" type="MultiText" class="wikitable" labels="Eligible Partner Organization(s)|Potential Conflict of Interest|Partner’s Role in Study and Specific Use of Contribution in Study|Nature of Contribution|Contribution Amount (CDN$)" types="Text|Radio(Yes,No)|Text|Radio(Cash,In-Kind)|Integer" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small><i>
                <ul>
                    <li>Complete the table below.</li>
                    <li>In a single PDF document please provide letters of support for each partner, collaborator etc. Upload this document below.  Make sure that each letter of support within the PDF is on the organization’s letterhead, detailing the partnership and specifically indicating their cash and/or in-kind contribution. The letter should specifically include reference to CFN, the proposed study, and any conditions placed on funding.  See Application Instructions for guidance on allowable expenses and eligible partners and contributions.</li>
                    <li>Individuals from the partner organizations that will be participating as project team members must be listed in the submitted Project Team Information document.</li>
                    <li>All financial information provided in the table below must also appear in the submitted budget document.</li>
                    <li>Where a researcher has a “financial interest” (as defined by NCE Conflict of Interest Guidelines) in a partner, the potential conflict of interest should be declared in the table.  This does not preclude the partnership in any way, but provides transparency during the review process. Please see CFN Conflict of Interest Policy and Guidelines for additional guidance <a href='http://www.cfn-nce.ca/media/23963/cfn-conflict-of-interest-policy.pdf' target='_blank'>http://www.cfn-nce.ca/media/23963/cfn-conflict-of-interest-policy.pdf</a></li>
                </ul>
                </i></small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="letters" blobItem="LETTERS" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Letters of Support</h3>
                <p><small><i>Upload a single PDF document containing all of the letters of support.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="funding" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="FUNDING" name="6 - Other Funding" title="Section 6 - Other Funding">
        <ReportItem id="funding" type="MultiText" class="wikitable" types="String|String|Integer|Text|Integer|Integer" blobItem="FUNDING" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" labels="Status|Funding Source|Amount|Purpose|% Scientific Overlap|% Financial Overlap" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><small><i>For all Principal Investigators please provide details on grants currently planned, being applied for, pending and awarded, for the entire period covered by this application.</i></small></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="documents" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="DOCUMENTS" name="7 - Supporting Documents" title="Section 7 - Supporting Documents" pagebreak="false">
        <ReportItem id="team" blobItem="TEAM" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Project team Information</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" blobItem="BUDGET" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Budget</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="pi_cvs" blobItem="PI_CVS" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Principal Investigator CV(s)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="team_cvs" blobItem="TEAM_CVS" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Team Member CVs</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="signatures" blobItem="SIGNATURES" blobType="BLOB_RAW" type="Upload" fileSize="20">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Required Signatures</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
