<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Affiliate Program" ajax="true" disabled="false" reportType="RP_HQP_APPLICATION" pdfType="RPTP_HQP_AFFILIATE" pdfFiles="AffiliateApplicationPDF" year="0">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="HQP-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="HQP">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Background Information" name="Information" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>TRAINING AT AGE-WELL</h2>
                <p>At AGE-WELL, we know that our trainees and early career professionals are the catalyst that will drive Canada’s leadership in AgeTech. We are committed to fostering this innovative energy through EPIC, the <a href="https://agewell-nce.ca/epic" target="_blank">Early Professionals, Inspired Careers Program</a>. Aimed at students, postdoctoral fellows, early career researchers, research professionals, clinicians, and recent grads, EPIC provides AGE-WELL members access to exclusive educational programming, experiential opportunities, funding, and mentorship.</p>
                
                <h2>HQP AFFILIATE MEMBERSHIP PROGRAM</h2>
                <p>We offer access to EPIC, entirely free of charge, through our Affiliates Membership Program.</p>

                <h3>Eligibility</h3> 
                <p>To be considered for the AGE-WELL Affiliates Membership you must be engaged in study, research or work aligned with the mission and vision of AGE-WELL.</p>

                <h3>Benefits</h3>

                Membership in AGE-WELL through our Affiliates Program grants access to:
                <ol>
                    <li>membership in a pan-Canadian knowledge community</li>
                    <li>access to our communications and platforms to keep you informed about what’s happening in AgeTech and connect you with 1000+ others in this sector</li>
                    <li>access to AGE-WELL exclusive programming including 60+ webinars and seminars per year</li>
                    <li>access to resources on our members’ intranet, potential communications and participant recruitment support</li>
                    <li>eligibility to apply for internal funding competitions and participate in activities such as our conferences, Summer Institute, video competitions, and hackathons</li>
                    <li>eligibility to participate in AGE-WELL supported experiential learning opportunities including mentorship, internships, and lab exchanges</li>
                    <li>access to AGE-WELL developed online courses including the AGE-WELL Innovators of Tomorrow certificate program.</li>
                </ol>

                <h3>Process</h3>
                <p>Once your application is reviewed, you will be notified via email and asked to sign and return the AGE-WELL Conflict of Interest and Non-Disclosure statements to <a href="mailto:training@agewell-nce.ca">training@agewell-nce.ca</a>.</p>

                <p>Applications are reviewed on a rolling basis throughout the year.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="application" tooltip="Core Research Program Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) Application" name="Application" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_FORM" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="research" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_RESEARCH" limit="300" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Statement of Research Focus</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        Membership in AGE-WELL is aimed at those studying, researching, or working in AgeTech. Recent graduates, clinicians, and those with an active interest in AgeTech that aligns with AGE-WELL’s mission and vision are also encouraged to apply.<br />
                        
                        In this section, applicants should describe their research foci or research interests as they relate to AGE-WELL and our <a href="https://agewell-nce.ca/challenge-areas" target="_blank">identified priorities</a>.<br />
                        
                        Please address the following in your response.
                        <ul>
                            <li>Are you currently engaged in research? If yes, please describe your work and how it connects to AGE-WELL. Why is your project important? Who is your target user population(s)? What is the expected impact of your research?</li>
                            <li>If you are not currently engaged in research, please describe your research interests and how it connects to AGE-WELL.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="training" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_TRAIN" height="200px" limit="300" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Statement of Training or Career Focus</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        In this section, applicants should describe their current academic status or career status.<br />

                        Please address the following in your response.<br />

                        <ol>
                            <li>Are you currently a student, postdoctoral fellow, or recent graduate (within 3 years)? If yes, please describe your current academic status. How does your current research focus relate to AgeTech?</li>
                            <li>If not a student, are you currently working in this sector? Please describe. What is the expected impact of your work?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="biography" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_BIO" limit="300" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Biography and Career Goals</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        AGE-WELL activities are geared towards the needs of our membership. In this section, applicants should describe their goals and why they are seeking membership in the network.<br />
                        Please address the following in your response.
                        <ol>
                            <li>What are your current academic or career goals? Where you see yourself in 5-10 years?</li>
                            <li>How you see AGE-WELL helping you to achieve your goals?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="align" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_ALIGN" limit="300" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Alignment to the Mission and Goals of AGE-WELL</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        AGE-WELL is a unique Canadian network that brings everyone together to develop technologies and services for healthy aging. We’re also training the next generation of innovators in this field, and making Canada a world leader in technologies that help aging populations everywhere.<br />
                        In this section, describe how you and your research or work fits with AGE-WELL’s vision, mission and values.<br />
Please address the following in your response.
                        <ol>
                            <li>How do you see yourself and/or your work making a real-world impact to improve the quality of life for older adults and/or caregivers?</li>
                            <li>AGE-WELL members work outside of disciplinary boundaries. Please describe your comfort level or willingness to engage with methods and disciplines beyond your own. Why is this important?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="documents" type="ReportSection" tooltip="Required Documents" name="Documents" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_DOCS">
        <ReportItem id="cv" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_CV" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Curriculum Vitae</h2>
                <p>Please prepare the document and submit as a PDF.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$user_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
