<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AGE-WELL Catalyst Program Application" reportType="RP_CAT" pdfType="RPTP_CAT" allowIdProjects="true" pdfFiles="CatalystApplicationPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="SD+">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="NI">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="NI-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="AR-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="CI-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="2018 AGE-WELL Catalyst Program" name="Program Description" type="ReportSection" title="2018 AGE-WELL Catalyst Program">
        <ReportItem id="description" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>AGE-WELL is excited to launch its 3rd Catalyst Funding competition to support innovative research projects aimed at generating, promoting or accelerating economic and social benefit in the field of technology and aging.</p> 
                <p>The Catalyst Funding Program represents the first-stage in AGE-WELL’s innovation funding stream. Catalyst grants will support early-stage, scalable research projects including pilot studies, feasibility studies and novel approaches that are aligned with AGE-WELL’s mission and vision. Projects must demonstrate strong potential for real-world impact.</p>
                <p>It is expected that Catalyst projects will lead to new funded research initiatives, either as part of AGE-WELL or through other granting agencies. Projects funded by AGE-WELL Catalyst grants may be suitable for future AGE-WELL investment as they progress along the innovation pipeline. To be eligible for continued funding through AGE-WELL, end-of-term deliverables must provide justification for continued funding either through a renewal of Catalyst funding or transfer to another AGE-WELL funding program (e.g. Core Research Program, Strategic Investment Program). See Project Deliverables and Potential for Continued Funding section below.</p>

                <h3>Award Value and Term</h3>
                <p>Up to $50,000 over 12 months. Can be renewed for one year, pending end-of-term review.</p>
	
                <p><b><u>Deadline:</u></b> March 23rd, 2018, 5:00 pm EST.</p>

                <h3>Eligibility</h3>
                
                <ul>
                    <li>The competition is open to researchers based at Canadian institutions working in the field of technology and aging. AGE-WELL uses the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR) definition of “independent researchers” when defining eligible grant holders (see <a href='http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/34190.html' target='_blank'>http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/34190.html</a>).</li>
                    <li>The applicant’s host institution must be eligible to hold Tri-Council funding. Canadian universities and investigators who are not already members of AGE-WELL will be required to sign onto the Network Agreement prior to receiving funds.</li>
                    <li>Catalyst funds cannot be used for activities funded through other AGE-WELL research competitions (e.g. activities that are part of an AGE-WELL Core Research Project).</li>
                    <li>Investigators will normally be expected to include partner organizations in their projects, including as part of any dissemination or commercialization planning. Such organizations should be described in the application, even where the partnership is at a very early stage of development. For reporting purposes, all partnership activities should be quantified in the application.</li>
                    <li>Proposals will ideally demonstrate some level of additional cash and/or in-kind contributions from industry or community partners or describe a plan to secure such contributions. There is no minimum contribution level required for the Catalyst program.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Application and Review Process:</h3>
                <p>Applications will be accepted through AGE-WELL’s Forum Research Portal.</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Access the Catalyst Program section of the Forum Research Portal.
                        <ul>
                            <li>All current AGE-WELL Network Investigators have Forum accounts and can access the Catalyst Program application materials through the ‘My Applications‘ tab visible when they log into Forum.</li>
                            <li>Applicants who are not already AGE-WELL Network Investigators must first request access to Forum by emailing <a href='mailto:info@agewell-nce.ca'>info@agewell-nce.ca</a> to request an account.  Accounts will be set up within 24 hours (maximum) of receiving the request. Once an account is created, applicants can access application materials through the ‘My Applications‘ tab visible upon login.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Complete the information in each section, uploading attachments as requested. The narrative sections of the application should not exceed 5 pages.</li>
                    <li>It is critical that AGE-WELL research investments support the potential for “real world impact”. A <i>Relevancy Review</i> will be carried out by network stakeholders (older adults and caregivers) to determine the potential for uptake and impact if funded by AGE-WELL. Results of the relevancy review will be taken into consideration by the Research Management Committee during <i>Scientific Review</i> of the proposal.</li>
                </ol>
                
                <h3>Potential for Continued Funding and Project Deliverables</h3>
                <p>To be considered for additional AGE-WELL funding, completed Catalyst projects must demonstrate long-term viability and readiness to advance to the next stage of funding. All teams who anticipate applying for further AGE-WELL funding will be expected to produce specific and measurable deliverables at the conclusion of their project, which may include: </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Problem/solution statement providing evidence of co-creation with key stakeholders over the term of the project. This should emphasize the need/problem/aspiration of stakeholder(s).  "Solutions" could be high level and noncommittal as to technology platform at this stage.</li>
                    <li>Environmental scan and/or literature review to provide an overview of the state of the art with respect to the problem/solution statement and will provide the justification for advancing the project.</li>
                    <li>Research project outline for next steps that would map out approach and likely methods for how a subsequent project would be carried out.</li>
                    <li>Preliminary business case or planning document addressing either knowledge mobilization and/or commercialization plans, e.g. business canvas, basic market analysis, knowledge mobilization plan.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>Key Contact:</h3>
                <p>Questions about the Catalyst Funding Program should be directed to Jeanie Zabukovec, AGE-WELL Research Program Manager (<a href='mailto:Jeanie@agewell-nce.ca'>Jeanie@agewell-nce.ca</a>). If you would like to discuss an idea for a strategic project, please get in touch with J. Zabukovec and one of the Scientific Directors would be happy to talk further.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cover" tooltip="Cover Sheet" name="Cover Sheet" blobSection="COVER_SHEET" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="ia" type="TextReportItem" width="200px" blobItem="LEADERS">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                    <li>
                    <table>
                        <tr>
                            <td align="right"><b>Project&nbsp;lead(s):&nbsp;</b></td>
                            <td>{$item}</td>
                        </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ib" type="TextReportItem" width="200px" blobItem="INSTITUTION">
            <![CDATA[
                        <tr>
                            <td align="right"><b>Institution:&nbsp;</b></td>
                            <td>{$item}</td>
                        </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ic" type="TextReportItem" width="300px" blobItem="PROJECT">
            <![CDATA[
                        <tr>
                            <td align="right"><b>Project&nbsp;Title:&nbsp;</b></td>
                            <td>{$item}</td>
                        </tr>
                     </table>
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iii" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" limit="300" blobItem="SUMMARY">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Provide a 300-word lay summary that includes a problem statement, research purpose and anticipated impact(s) of the project. This summary will be provided to network stakeholders in order to facilitate a Relevancy Review to determine the potential for uptake and impact if funded. This description will also be  used for future communications if the proposal is successful.</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iv" type="IntegerReportItem" min="0" max="50000" width="43px" align="left" blobItem="INVESTMENT">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Total value of AGE-WELL investment requested:</b> ${$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <!--ReportItem id="v" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="PARTNERS" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Collaborators/partners invested in the project (if applicable)</b> {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem-->
        <ReportItem id="via" type="SelectReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" options="WP1 NEEDS-OA|WP2 NEEDS-CG|WP3 TECH-FAI|WP4 TECH-APS|WP5 TECH-DD|WP6 TECH-MCH|WP7 POLICY-TECH|WP8 ETHICS-TECH|Other" blobItem="WP">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>The proposed project is best aligned with AGE-WELL</b>
                    {$item}
                    (WP descriptions are available here: <a href='http://www.agewell-nce.ca' target="_blank">www.agewell-nce.ca</a>)<br />
                    <br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="vib" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" limit="300" blobItem="SUMMARY_OTHER" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <b>If you have selected “Other” and think that the proposed project falls outside of AGE-WELL’s current WP structure, please provide a justification for this:</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="viii" type="Radio" options="Yes|No" blobItem="PREVIOUS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Does this application pertain to a project currently/previously funded through an AGE-WELL Research Program?</b><br />
                    <small>(i.e. are you looking to renew your Catalyst award, or further advance your SIP project to a Catalyst project)?</small>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra1" type="Textarea" rich="true" optional="true" blobItem="EXTRA1">
            <![CDATA[
                <div id="extra" style="display:none;">
                    <h2>APPLICATIONS FOR CONTINUED FUNDING</h2>
                    <p>If you previously received an AGE-WELL SIP, SIP Accelerator or Catalyst award for this project please complete the following questions related to the work already completed (1 page). If objectives from your previous award have not been met and you wish to apply for a no-cost extension, please contact jeanie@agewell-nce.ca.</p>
                    <h3>Were the objectives of the previously funded project met?  Please explain.</h3>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra2" type="Textarea" rich="true" optional="true" blobItem="EXTRA2">
            <![CDATA[
                    <h3>What is/are the main output(s) from your previous award. Please describe the real or potential impact of this work? Consider the real or potential impact on older adults and caregivers, communities, industry and/or policies.</h3>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra2a" type="Upload" rich="true" optional="true" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="EXTRA2A" fileSize="20" mimeType="application/zip,.zip">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><b>Please attach any outputs from your previously funded project (ex. environmental scan, literature review, market analysis, knowledge mobilization plan, ect).</b></p>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra3" type="Textarea" rich="true" optional="true" blobItem="EXTRA3">
            <![CDATA[
                    <h3>What new partnerships or collaboarations were created during the previous award? Will these continue? How did these partnerships/collaborations shape your project?</h3>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra4" type="Textarea" rich="true" optional="true" blobItem="EXTRA4">
            <![CDATA[
                    <h3>Did the project encounter any challenges? What impact did this have on the project? </h3>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extra5" type="Textarea" rich="true" optional="true" blobItem="EXTRA5">
            <![CDATA[
                    <h3>In the narrative application (PART 1), please describe how the new project will build on the activities, findings and partnerships from the previously funded work.</h3>
                    {$item}
                </div>
                <script type="text/javascript">
                    $(document).ready(function(){
                        $("input[name=CoverSheet_viii]").change(function(){
                            var val = $("input[name=CoverSheet_viii]:checked").val();
                            if(val == "Yes"){
                                $("div#extra").slideDown();
                            }
                            else{
                                $("div#extra").slideUp();
                            }
                        });
                        $("input[name=CoverSheet_viii]").change();
                    });
                </script>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="narrative" tooltip="PART 1 - Narrative Application" title="PART 1 - Narrative Application" name="Narrative Application" blobSection="NARRATIVE" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="header1" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Section 1- Overview</h2>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="background" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="BACKGROUND">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Background, Research Question, and/or Objectives -</b>
                    <i>description of problem area and rationale. Cleary state the underlying hypothesis (if applicable) and why this proposal is considered to have the potential to improve the lives of Canadian seniors.  This should provide evidence of co-creation with key stakeholders over the term of the project.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="method" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="METHOD">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Methodological Approach - </b>
                    <i>study design, population, design methodology, data analysis, statistics, etc. Please include whether ethics clearance is required?  If yes, has it already be approved?  If not, when do you expect it to be received?</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="relevance" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="RELEVANCE">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Relevance to AGE-WELL vision and goals - </b>
                    <i>Describe the relevance and the importance of the proposed project to AGE-WELL’s mission and vision and how the project aligns with at least one of <a href='http://agewell-nce.ca/research' target='_blank'>AGE-WELL Workpackages</a>.  Identify how the proposed study meets the specific objectives of the Catalyst Program to foster novel, innovative projects demonstrating potential for significant socio-economic benefits related to the aging population.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="header2" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Section 2 – Innovation and Impact</h2>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="novelty" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="NOVELTY">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Novelty and originality </b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="evaluate" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="EVALUATE">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Potential for Knowledge Mobilization and/or Commercialization - </b>
                    <i>Describe the opportunities for knowledge translation and exchange and/or technology transfer or commercialization of the research proposed. If there are specific companies or organizations that will be involved, list them in section 3 of this application (Partnerships) and ensure that a letter of support is included.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="social" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="SOCIAL">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Social Innovation: Potential implications and practical benefits for the aged population</b>
                    <i>What are practical benefits to the wider community? How will these be achieved?</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="scientific" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="SCIENTIFIC">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Scientific Innovation - </b>
                    <i>What are the key scientific outputs from this research? How will these be communicated to the scientific and/or knowledge-using communities?</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="header3" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Section 3 – Research Plan</h2>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="timeline" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="TIMELINE">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Timeline of Research Deliverables & Milestones - </b>
                    <i>Describe the research milestones and deliverables over the duration of the project. Identify all feasibility issues, challenges and limitations, and what the investigative team will do to overcome them. Include a summary of how this project will be managed and deliverables tracked.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="plans" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="PLANS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Future plans to ensure sustainability of this study - </b>
                    <i>What is the longer term vision of the project within AGE-WELL and/or  other funding sources? Describe any future funding opportunities or collaborations that will help to ensure the project objectives are met following the AGE-WELL funding period.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="header4" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Section 4 – Project team and Networking</h2>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="networking" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="NETWORKING">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Project Networking and Engagement - </b>
                    <i>across disciplines, research sites, and sectors. Projects must represent a collaborative effort of different Investigators in more than one discipline and at more than one Institution and with involvement or partners and stakeholders from other sectors.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="HQP">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Development of HQP - </b>
                    <i>AGE-WELL funded proposals must contribute to the development of Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) through their inclusion as fully involved team members. Briefly summarize the number and level of HQP required and the experience/expertise afforded by involvement in Network-funded research. Specify expected contributions to HQP studies.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="collab" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="COLLAB">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Collaborators/Partners and added value of the collaboration - </b>
                    <i>Part 3 of this application  will include letter(s) of support confirming quantified contributions. Partner contributions should also appear in the Budget spreadsheet.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="funding" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="FUNDING">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Other Funding - </b>
                    <i>Please provide details of other funding applied for that could leverage/support your AGE-WELL Network proposal.  Funding should be described by individual, for the Project Leader, all other Principal Investigators, and all Co-Investigators, for grants currently planned to be applied for, being applied for, pending, about to be submitted, and all grants received, for the entire period covered by this application.</i>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="appendix" tooltip="Budget and Activities" title="Budget and Activities" name="Budget and Activities" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="APPENDIX">
        <ReportItem id="team" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="TEAM" labels="Team Member Name|Role|Institution/Organization|Expertise|Email" types="Text|Select(PL,NI,AR,Collaborator,Partner)|Text|Textarea|Text" sizes="150||150||150" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Team Summary</h2>
                <p class='small'>Use the following code for Role:<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;PL:</b> Project Lead<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;NI:</b> Network Investigator<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;AR:</b> Affiliated Researcher<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;Collaborator</b><br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;Partner</b></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP" labels="Name|Institution|Email|Level of Study/Position" types="Text|Text|Text|Text" sizes="150|150|150|" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="BUDGET" structure="AGEWELL_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="AGE-WELL Budget.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just1" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST1" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <p>Please use the following categories in your budget justification as appropriate. Note that SIP funding includes specific budget caps in some categories.</p>
                <ol>
                <li><b>Salaries to students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just2" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST2" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Salaries to non-students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just3" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST3" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Professional & Tech. Services/contracts</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Consultants and business development services (maximum $5,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just4" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST4" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Equipment</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Purchase of rental</li>
                        <li>Maintenance costs</li>
                        <li>Operating costs</li>
                        <li>Other equipment costs</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just5" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST5" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Computing and Software</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Specialized software licenses and e-communications costs</li>
                        <li>E-business enablement costs, website</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just6" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST6" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Materials, Supplies & Other expenditures</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Materials and Supplies</li>
                        <li>Patent costs (maximum $3,000)</li>
                        <li>Proof of Principle, product validation for market readiness</li>
                        <li>Prototype development (specify)</li>
                        <li>Communications/Marketing/Printing/Production (maximum $5,000)</li>
                        <li>Evaluation costs</li>
                        <li>Management and Networking (maximum $3,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just7" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST7" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Travel</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Field trips</li>
                        <li>Conference, technical shows</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="bio" tooltip="Partnerships and Letters" title="Partnerships and Letters" name="Partnerships and Letters" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="BIO">
        <ReportItem id="bio" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="BIO" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Investigator Bio</h3>
                <p>Please submit a brief bio for each named investigator from the narrative section, highlighting experience and activities relevant to the application (one page per bio maximum).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="PARTNERS" multiple="true" labels="Partner Organization/ Research Receptor|Potential Conflict of Interest|Role in Project and Specific&lt;br /&gt;Use of Contribution in Project|Nature of Contribution|Contribution Amount (CDN$)" types="Text|Select(Yes,No)|Text|Select(Cash,In-Kind)|Integer" sizes="175|75|175|75|75">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>List each organization that will partner in the project, their specific roles (i.e. research receptor, knowledge user, financial/in-kind support), and the cash and in-kind contributions anticipated from the partner(s) to the project. All financial information provided in the budget in the Budget and Activities section should also appear in the pertinent areas of the project budget, and individuals from these organizations that will be participating as project team members should also be listed in the Project Team List.</p>

                <p><u>Please provide a letter of support</u> on the letterhead of each eligible partner detailing the extent of their collaboration and/or cash and in-kind contribution towards the project. The letter should specifically include reference to AGE-WELL, the proposed project, and any conditions placed on funding.</p>

                <p><i>Where a researcher has a “financial interest” (as defined by NCE Conflict of Interest Guidelines) in a partner, the potential conflict of interest should be declared.  This does not preclude the partnership in any way, but provides transparency during the review process. Please see AGE-WELL Conflict of Interest Policy and Guidelines available on AGE-WELL’s website for further information.</i></p>

                <p>Please see Application Instructions for guidance on allowable expenses and eligible partners and contributions.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="letter" type="UploadReportItem" blobItem="LETTER" mimeType="application/zip" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Partner Letters of Support</h3>

                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$user_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
