<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="CC Activity Planning" reportType="RP_CC_PLANNING" pdfType="RPTP_CC_PLANNING" pdfFiles="CCPlanningPDF,CC1PlanningPDF,CC2PlanningPDF,CC3PlanningPDF,CC4PlanningPDF" personId="0" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2015">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="PL">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc1" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc2" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc3" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc4" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="TL">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc1" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc2" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc3" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc4" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="TC">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc1" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc2" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc3" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cc4" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Project start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" deleted="false" />
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions" name="General Instructions" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="instructions" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>CC Activity Planning</h3>
                <p>The Crosscutting activities in the AGE-WELL network are designed to encourage and support research projects within AGE-WELL to achieve our key network goals. As such there are 4 CCs: Knowledge Mobilization (CC1), Commercialization and Technology Transfer (CC2), Transdisciplinary Working (CC3) and Training and Mentorship (CC4). As an initial step in meeting our Network Goals, we are asking all Project Leads to fill in a activity plan for each CC activity. These are designed to put our key network goals to the forefront of projects by:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Ensuring CC activities are fully integrated into projects</li>
    <li>Providing help and support in areas in which researchers may lack skills and expertise</li>
    <li>Building capacity through seminars, resources, mentoring and training</li>
    <li>Monitoring performance of projects in relation to network goals</li>
    <li>Developing new approaches, concepts and directions that require effective team-working</li>
    <li>Allowing us to work efficiently as a group by sharing knowledge, methods, tools, utilizing common resources, such as access to labs, end-users, etc.</li>
    <li>Supporting those areas that researchers typically need extra support with such as knowledge mobilization and commercialization</li>
    <li>Creating a critical mass that will have an impact far beyond what individual projects could achieve.</li>
</ul>
<p>
The activity plans are attached in this package. In addition, these briefing notes give some background ideas about each of the CC activities, which will help Project Leaders to think about and articulate their ideas.</p>
<p>
Each Crosscutting Activity is made up of a team including CC leads, Scientific Director - Andrew Sixsmith, SFU Core Facility Director - Pam Borghardt and appropriate Network Management Office staff as they come on board and of course Network Managing Director – Bridgette Murphy. If you have any queries or would like to get help and guidance, please contact one of the CC leads attached to the particular CC activity area or the supporting team members.
</p><br />
<table cellpadding='3' cellspacing='1' frame='box' rules='all'>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 1 Knowledge Mobilization Co-lead</td>
        <td>Karen Kobayashi</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:kmkobay@uvic.ca'>kmkobay@uvic.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 1 Knowledge Mobilization Co-lead</td>
        <td>Lynn McDonald</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:lynn.mcdonald@utoronto.ca'>lynn.mcdonald@utoronto.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Knowledge Mobilization and Communications Manager</td>
        <td>TBA</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:communications@agewell-nce.ca'>communications@agewell-nce.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 2 Commercialization and Technology Transfer Co-lead</td>
        <td>Geoff Fernie</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:Geoff.Fernie@uhn.ca'>Geoff.Fernie@uhn.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 2 Commercialization and Technology Transfer Co-lead</td>
        <td>Ryan D’Arcy</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:rdarcy@sfu.ca'>rdarcy@sfu.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Business Development and Partnerships Manager</td>
        <td>TBA (starts early July)</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:partnerships@agewell-nce.ca'>partnerships@agewell-nce.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 3 Transdisciplinary Working Co-lead</td>
        <td>Pia Kontos</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:Pia.Kontos@uhn.ca'>Pia.Kontos@uhn.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 3 Transdisciplinary Working Co-lead</td>
        <td>Judith Sixsmith</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:Judith.Sixsmith@northampton.ac.uk'>Judith.Sixsmith@northampton.ac.uk</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Transdisciplinary Staff</td>
        <td>TBA</td>
        <td></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 4 Training and Mentorship Co-lead</td>
        <td>Susan Jaglal</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:susan.jaglal@utoronto.ca'>susan.jaglal@utoronto.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>CC 4 Training and Mentorship Co-lead</td>
        <td>Veselin Jungic</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:vjungic@sfu.ca'>vjungic@sfu.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Education & Training Administrator</td>
        <td>TBA (starts mid-July)</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:training@agewell-nce.ca'>training@agewell-nce.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Scientific Director</td>
        <td>Andrew Sixsmith</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:ajs16@sfu.ca'>ajs16@sfu.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>SFU Core Facility Director</td>
        <td>Pam Borghardt</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:pjborgha@sfu.ca'>pjborgha@sfu.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td>AGE-WELL Managing Director</td>
        <td>Bridgette Murphy</td>
        <td><a href='mailto:Bridgette.Murphy@uhn.ca'>Bridgette.Murphy@uhn.ca</a></td>
    </tr>
</table>

<h3>Overview of Crosscutting (CC) Activities</h3>
<p>CC1. K-MOB - Knowledge Mobilization and Translation: K-MOB will involve researchers and stakeholders in an integrated KT approach to jointly develop research agendas and carry out the research program and encourage innovation. CC1 will identify KT opportunities for the network, participate in research and evaluation of outcomes and will be responsible for the overall KT and mobilization strategy for AGE-WELL. See Section 7.3 of the original proposal for a more detailed overview.</p>
<p>CC2. TECH-TRANS - Commercialization and Technology Transfer: TECH-TRANS will focus on working with our industry partners and project leads to better understand pathways for innovation and to develop novel and innovative approaches to commercialize the outcomes (both technology and services) of AGE-WELL. Activities will include market and policy analyses, service and business modeling, development of ethical guidelines and technical standards. Outcomes will include practical support to commercialization that can be applied across all WPs. See Section 7.4 of the original proposal for a more detailed overview.</p>
<p>CC3. T-WORK - Transdisciplinary Working: T-WORK aims to transcend disciplinary boundaries by developing shared concepts and understandings, goals and working practices in order to work effectively as a single team to tackle the complexity of real-world problem domains. Workshops and other informal and formal communications strategies will ensure that AGE- WELL develops a common frame of reference and shared concepts, while later work will aim to drive and inform different WPs. Outcomes will include the development of a roadmap and priorities for technology and aging research within the team, and a repository and knowledge networking system. See Section 6.2 of the original proposal for a more detailed overview.</p>
<p>CC4. TRAIN - Training and Mentorship: TRAIN will provide a unique training environment that exposes AGE-WELL trainees to multi-disciplinary research environments and to our industry and community partners through collaborations with existing research networks and partner universities. See Section 5.5 of the original proposal for a more detailed overview. As an NCE, we are required to monitor progress and demonstrate that we are achieving our network goals. The general reporting framework for the Core Research Program was outlined in the AGE-WELL Terms and Conditions of Funding document that you received with your Funding Letter. We are asking Project Leads to provide ideas about how their projects should be evaluated. The various activity plans have specific sections in them relating to performance measurement.</p>

<h3>Timeframe for submission of CC Activity Plans</h3>
<ul>
<li>Please fill in the activity plans for the four Crosscutting activities provided in this package</li>
<li>Please complete draft plans for <b>CCs 3&4 by 1st August</b></li>
<li>Please complete draft plans for <b>CCs 1&2 by 1st September</b></li>
<li>These will then be reviewed and feedback provided to Project Leads by CC Leads and NMO Officers (if applicable). Depending on feedback, Project Leads should continue to develop their plans in consultation with CC leads and NMO</li>
<li><b>Final activity plans should be submitted by 1st October for review at the October RMC.</b></li>
</ul>
<p>Support in developing your plans will be available by the CC Leads and their supporting team (NMO staff are expected to be in place during the summer).</p>
<p>Please note, that we see these plans as a starting point and should be seen as living documents that will continue to be developed and changed beyond these deadlines. For example, a project may have to develop capacity in CC2 (e.g. through HQP training or consultation with commercialization consultants at their institutions) and a full commercialization plan would be a deliverable of the project. However, in this scenario, the project will have to demonstrate that they are putting in place the necessary steps towards commercialization, together with a timeline.</p>
<h3>Filling in the activity plans</h3>
<p>The activity plans are designed to help Project Leads to articulate their ideas and provide detailed plans for their activities in the various CC areas. The bullet points are provided as prompts/guides for your plans, but you are not confined to these points however, you should use the sub-headings provided. The activity plans contain instructions indicating maximum pages to be submitted.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cc1" tooltip="Knowledge Mobilization and Translation" name="CC1 K-MOB" blobSection="CC_PLANNING_1" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
            <h3>Briefing Notes</h3>
<p>AGE-WELL is about innovation through research. Traditional technology transfer (TT) approaches often engage end-users and stakeholders in the very late stages of technology development. These approaches have limited applicability in the field of technology and aging, where stakeholder engagement across the entire research and development process is critical to innovation.</p>
<p>Our overarching goal will be to develop a “Knowledge Community” in Technology and Aging to promote knowledge construction, translation, and exchange. We will do this by working collaboratively with various stakeholder groups at all stages of the research process to mobilize findings into policy, practice, and effective business models, products, and services.</p>
<p>There are several key ideas behind AGE-WELL’s vision for knowledge mobilization:</p>
<p>Knowledge mobilization within AGE-WELL will involve researchers and stakeholders in an integrated approach to jointly develop research questions and agendas and carry out the research program and encourage innovation. We are looking for ways to maximize the impact of AGE-WELL locally, nationally, and internationally.</p>
<p>The entire research endeavor within AGE-WELL will be driven through user involvement at all stages of the research process from setting research questions and agendas through to evaluation and knowledge translation and mobilization.</p>
<p>While knowledge mobilization is a continuous process, it is expected that for AGE-WELL projects, the initial few years will focus on the descriptions and benefits of the research and the final year(s) on knowledge mobilization and technology transfer activities from the research.</p>
<p>Highly qualified personnel (HQPs) and trainees are expected to be involved in all aspects of a project, including knowledge mobilization.</p>
<p>Knowledge mobilization (KM) has become shorthand for a wide variety of activities linking the production of academic research to the potential use of such knowledge in non-academic settings. A number of KM definitions have emerged to date, e.g., knowledge transfer, knowledge translation, diffusion of innovation, research utilization, implementation science. Incongruence across these definitions reflects variations in who is targeted as the audience -- an individual, organization or a whole system. KM also occurs in almost every discipline from engineering through to health, education, and agriculture.</p>
<p>Today, ‘knowledge transfer and exchange’ (KTE) has emerged as a result of growing evidence that successful knowledge transfer actually involves two-way communication requiring genuine interactions among all stakeholders. Many experts have come to agree that knowledge use is a not a single discrete event, but rather a process of interaction with multiple flows of knowledge among all stakeholders.</p>
<p>There are many conceptual frameworks for knowledge transfer and exchange: recent reviews of the literature in this area have recognized as many as 63 theories and models. Most of these, however, are unrefined and untested in practice despite their focus on health.</p>
<p>The two dominant frameworks (and their many adaptations) in the health field are from CIHR and PARiHs. CIHR has also developed an innovation and commercialization strategy for health research that is aligned with AGE-WELL. The strategy for innovation and commercialization can be found at <a target='_blank' href='http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/29418.html'>http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/29418.html</a>.</p>
<p>An exchange model of knowledge mobilization represents an approach to conducting research that applies the principles of knowledge translation to the entire research process. The central premise is that involving knowledge users as equal partners alongside researchers will lead to research that is more likely to be useful to the knowledge users, and which has increased potential for commercialization.</p>
<p>Each stage in the research process is an opportunity for significant collaboration with knowledge users, including the refinement of the research questions, selection of the methodology, data collection and tool development, selection of outcome measures, interpretation of the findings, the crafting of the message and dissemination of the results.</p>
<p>As CIHR has constructed the best models for knowledge mobilization, including a focus on commercialization, we have modified their approach for AGE-WELL. The framework for knowledge mobilization is built on the Knowledge to Action model developed by CIHR. It is a framework that demonstrates the role of knowledge and the pathways for knowledge mobilization.</p>
<p>Involvement of Knowledge Users and Partners in Research is crucial: "a dynamic and iterative process that includes synthesis, dissemination, exchange and ethically sound application of knowledge to improve the health of Canadians, provide more effective health services and products and strengthen the health care system." <a target='_blank' href='http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/45321.html'>http://www.cihr-irsc.gc.ca/e/45321.html</a></p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="objectives_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_OBJECTIVES,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Objectives</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="objectives" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_OBJECTIVES" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are your goals for knowledge mobilization? (these could be to inform/change: knowledge/awareness, future research, attitudes, behavior(s), policy, practice(s), technology, new products)</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="mobilize_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_MOBILIZE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What knowledge will you mobilize?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="mobilize" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_MOBILIZE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are your goals for knowledge mobilization?</li>
                        <li>What are the main messages?</li>
                        <li>Why are these meaningful?</li>
                        <li>What is the potential impact?</li>
                        <li>How will your knowledge be used?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_PARTNERS,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Who are your knowledge partners?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_PARTNERS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Who is involved in mobilizing this knowledge? (these may be stakeholders from different groups: caregivers, families, government, industry, etc.)</li>
                        <li>Are these partners involved in developing your research and/or knowledge (knowledge mobilization is often a 2-way process)?</li>
                        <li>Describe their role in your project</li>
                        <li>Who are the champions/key mobilizers?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="engage_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_ENGAGE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Who are you trying to reach and engage?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="engage" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_ENGAGE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <small>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Who is your target audience? (e.g. community-based and not-for profit organizations, general public, health care professionals/service providers, health system administrators/managers, industry/venture capital groups, media (print, TV, etc.), patients/residents/consumers, policy makers/legislators, private sector, research funders, researchers)</li>
                            <li>Define your target audience in terms of their sector, roles, responsibilities and decision-making needs/opportunities</li>
                            <li>What are their knowledge needs in the research area and their preferences for using knowledge?</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="achieve_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_ACHIEVE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How will you achieve your knowledge mobilization objectives?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="achieve" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_ACHIEVE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <small>
                        <ul>
                            <li>How will you get your messages across?</li>
                            <li>How will your reach your intended knowledge users?</li>
                            <li>When do you intend to implement your plan? (provide a brief timeline)</li>
                            <li>How are knowledge mobilization activities integrated with other project activities?</li>
                            <li>Do you need to adapt the knowledge to specific audiences?</li>
                            <li>Have any contextual or mitigating factors been considered that might affect the planned KM activities?</li>
                            <li>What are the barriers and facilitators to knowledge use?</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="expertise_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_EXPERTISE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What expertise do you need?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="expertise" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_EXPERTISE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[<small>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Are all necessary knowledge users involved to achieve the stated goals?</li>
                            <li>Describe the team's ability to execute the proposed strategies</li>
                            <li>How will the teams collaborate meaningfully with members of its target audiences?</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="expertise_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_RESOURCES,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What resources do you need for your knowledge mobilization plan?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="resources" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_RESOURCES" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <small>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Financial resources?</li>
                            <li>Personnel?</li>
                            <li>Consumables?</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_MEASURE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How will you measure the impact of your knowledge?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_MEASURE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <small>
                        The idea of innovation is to change things (practice, services, policy, attitudes, use of technologies, etc.)
                        <ul>
                            <li>How will you know you have achieved your goals?</li>
                            <li>How should the impact of your knowledge be evaluated?</li>
                            <li>Note any useful measures/indicators of reach and outcome</li>
                            <li>How should this information be collected and analyzed?</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER,CC_PLANNING_1,CC_1_SUPPORT,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How do you think AGE-WELL as an organization could help or support your knowledge mobilization efforts?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_1_SUPPORT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <small>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Provide any ideas about support at the network level</li>
                        </ul>
                    </small>
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attach" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CC_1_ATTACH" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Additional Materials</h3>
                <small>If you have any additional materials, you can upload a pdf attachement</small><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cc2" tooltip="Commercialization and Technology Transfer" name="CC2 TECH-TRANS" blobSection="CC_PLANNING_2" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Briefing Notes</h3>
<p>The prime aim of AGE-WELL is to establish and promote Canada’s international leadership in the design, development and commercialization of technology that supports the health and well-being of older adults.</p>
<p>AGE-WELL is designed to expressly tackle challenges in commercialization, with a key first step involving the initial development of a translational plan at the earliest possible stage.</p>
<p>AGE-WELL will have a major emphasis on supporting entrepreneurship through the funding of new start-ups, supporting Network Investigators and HQP to be entrepreneurial, and through partnerships with industry and service providers.</p>
<b>Creating an enterprise culture</b>
<p>Our proposal stated that AGE-WELL would produce 12 products ready to transfer to market by the end of its first 5 years. The shift in expectations of research across Canada toward commercialization of the results will likely increase the emphasis placed on our success in this aspect when the time comes to judge the achievements of our network.</p>
<p>While AGE-WELL has been tasked to create commercial outputs, currently there is a need to build capacity across the Network to achieve this. AGE-WELL needs to foster an “enterprise culture” within the whole network. This is about creating the right environment for commercialization, where all participants are engaged in meeting our key network objective of generating commercial products and services.</p>
<p>Not every project is expected to be directly responsible for a commercial outcome, but all projects should be actively contributing to this goal. For example technology projects (WPs-3-6), will be supported by projects WP1, WP2, WP7 and WP8 as part of their contribution to achieving our commercialization goals.</p>
<p>Individual researchers and research projects will have to take ownership of their own commercialization needs and work proactively to develop capacity and opportunities for commercialization. AGE-WELL will not directly be doing the commercialization, but will be providing advice and assistance.</p>
<p>All projects will need an industry partner to provide opportunities for commercial development. This could be a technology company local to the research institute or from the AGE-WELL network or a startup company formed from within or outside AGE-WELL.</p>
<p>All project plans should include defined activities, milestones and resources allocated to commercialization, including business plan development including HQP training plans that should include taking courses, accessing mentorship spending time within commercial operations.</p>
<p>Key performance indicators will include commercialization outcomes.</p>
<p>The objective of commercializing at least 12 products and services implies that each of the ‘technology’ work packages must commercialize at least 3 products/services during the first 5 years. The ‘technology’ work packages will need the support of the ‘research’ packages to achieve this ambitious goal as well as the support of the CC’s.</p>
<p>There are various ways that this support might be provided and some specific ideas are provided below:</p>
<ol>
    <li>Providing commercially-focused information to technology projects:
        <ul>
            <li>Align their research activities so that they provide a “service” to the technology development projects</li>
            <li>Market analyses- anticipating the barriers and facilitators to the adoption of proposed products/services</li>
            <li>Stakeholder research (not just older people/caregivers) to map out the whole context of use within which a technology might exist. This may involve developing new business process models for service providers to utilize AGE-WELL products.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li>Contributing knowledge that will generate new products/services:
        <ul>
            <li>Mapping new technology solutions- e.g. project workshops to develop new ideas for products and services</li>
            <li>Networking with teams within AGE-WELL to develop ideas for new products and business opportunities informally and via activities within CC3</li>
            <li>Identifying, evaluating and highlighting near-to-market technologies that could be “quick-wins” for AGE-WELL through its commercialization funding.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li>Creating new businesses:
        <ul>
            <li>Market research services to industrial partners</li>
            <li>Develop a service (using technology) either directly or partnering with existing service providers</li>
            <li>Some research WPs are intervention based and include tech development. If this is the case, there should be a strong business case for long-term sustainability</li>
            <li>Researchers and HQPs partnering with product developers to create spin-off companies.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
</ol>
<b>Concluding ideas about Commercialization and Technology Transfer</b>
<p>Together, we will develop an enterprise culture. All of our researchers and developers will need to demonstrate a commitment to this in order to continue to be funded (i.e. evaluation metrics for commercialization activities need to be built in).</p>
<p>Social and clinical researchers do not typically see themselves as contributors to developing commercial ideas and solutions and working with people in the commercial sector (except in terms of general information and data from their discipline, clinically-oriented studies or providing specific consultancy). AGE-WELL will be aiming to change this research culture and this will be a key task for CC3.</p>
<p>All of the CC leads and relevant NMO personnel will provide the support to research projects to achieve the above- through support/advice and training.</p>
<p>We especially would like to see HQPs involved in commercialization activities and, indeed, HQPs may be the major catalyst for commercialization in some projects. Consider providing training opportunities and release time for HQPs beyond their typical disciplinary training to attend for example courses on technology commercialization.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="products_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_PRODUCTS,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What products or services do you intend to commercialize? (please refer to briefing notes for detailed explanation)</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="products" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_PRODUCTS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="commercialize_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_COMMERCIALIZE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>If your project is planning to directly commercialize a product(s):</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="commercialize" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_COMMERCIALIZE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are the products or services you intend to bring to market?</li>
                        <li>What is new or unique about your product?</li>
                        <li>What is your competitive advantage or value proposition to the customer?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="provide_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_PROVIDE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>If your project is providing support to commercialization within AGE-WELL:</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="provide" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_PROVIDE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What kind of commercially focused information will you provide to technology projects?</li>
                        <li>What knowledge will you provide that will generate new products/services?</li>
                        <li>What are your plans for creating new businesses based on your research knowledge or experience?</li>
                        <li>Do you have any other commercially oriented contributions?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_PARTNERS,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Who are your partners?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_PARTNERS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Which (if any) partners are involved in the commercialization process?
                            <ul>
                                <li>For each partner describe their role</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="stage_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_STAGE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What stage is your product at?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="stage" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_STAGE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Is it at the preliminary design process?</li>
                        <li>Does a working prototype exist?</li>
                        <li>Does a pre-production prototype exist?</li>
                        <li>What testing and technical analysis has been completed?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="market_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_MARKET,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What is your market?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="market" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_MARKET" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Who are you targeting?</li>
                        <li>How big is this market?</li>
                        <li>What proportion of this market do you think you could capture and over what timeframe?</li>
                        <li>What is your revenue forecast? (companies often discover that the market for their product is too small)</li>
                        <li>What are the barriers in this market?</li>
                        <li>What/who are your competition?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ip_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_IP,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Intellectual property</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ip" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_IP" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Have you done any patent searching to see if you have (or expect to have) any protectable IP?</li>
                        <li>What are your plans to protect your IP?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="achieve_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_ACHIEVE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How will you achieve your commercialization objectives?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="achieve" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_ACHIEVE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Will your product require Health Canada, CE or FDA approval? If so, what class will it belong to?</li>
                        <li>How do you intend to take your products to market? (Typically, this is through i. licensing of IP or ii. start-up company)</li>
                        <li>How will your reach your intended market?</li>
                        <li>Describe the capabilities of your team, specifically as it relates to commercialization of your technology. (i.e. not technical or research capability)</li>
                        <li>What financial and human resources will you need?</li>
                        <li>How is your commercialization process integrated with other project activities?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_MEASURE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How will you measure the effectiveness of your commercialization activities?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_MEASURE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Define a clear list of milestones for the project with deliverables due on specific dates</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_2,CC_2_SUPPORT,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How do you think AGE-WELL as an organization could help or support commercialization within the network?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_2_SUPPORT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Provide any ideas about support you would like to get from AGE-WELL to commercialize your product.</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attach" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CC_2_ATTACH" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Additional Materials</h3>
                <small>If you have any additional materials, you can upload a pdf attachement</small><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cc3" tooltip="Transdisciplinary Working" name="CC3 T-WORK" blobSection="CC_PLANNING_3" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Briefing Notes</h3>
<p>Given the scale and complexity of the AGE-WELL Network and its goals, transdisciplinarity is a promising way research teams can work towards creating shared ideas, aims, objectives and goals. This involves team members creating a shared culture that integrates and transcends each member’s separate disciplinary perspective.</p>
<p>In our proposal we stated that AGE-WELL will foster transdisciplinarity by bringing together researchers, industry partners, service providers, and older Canadians and their families and caregivers in a series of research and development projects to create an integrated network.</p>
<p>While transdisciplinarity is a recognised strength of our NCE, working within such complex teams and large scale networks can be challenging and many research and development projects are compromised by poor communication and team work resulting from conflicting perspectives on how to achieve success, divergent conceptual models, methodological stances and forms of analysis. To achieve the promise of transdisciplinarity, we will need to foster collaborative processes of working within the whole network. This is about creating the right environment for transdisciplinarity, where all participants are engaged in meeting this key network objective.</p>
<p>A key first step to achieving this is to develop a transdisciplinary plan at the earliest possible stage. To begin this process, we need to get a good sense of the following from each network member. The activity planning is aimed at eliciting:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Understandings about transdisciplinarity</li>
    <li>Experience with a transdisciplinary approach</li>
    <li>Experiences working on large complex projects with team members from different disciplines</li>
    <li>Implementation of transdisciplinarity across the network</li>
    <li>Contributions to the network: Perceived value of transdisciplinary working</li>
</ul>
<p>In addition we need to map the opportunities we have in AGE-WELL to work in transdisciplinary ways and how this can be best supported within the AGE-WELL Network. The activity plan is designed to help with the mapping exercise and the development of the support mechanisms needed to facilitate transdisciplinary working within AGE-WELL.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="trans_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_TRANS,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>SECTION 1: KNOWLEDGE</h2>
                <h3>What do you know about transdisciplinarity?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="trans" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_TRANS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Purpose, key characteristics and features</li>
                        <li>How do you see transdisciplinarity differing from other approaches (multi, inter-cross-disciplinary)?</li>
                        <li>What are the benefits of a transdisciplinary approach?</li>
                        <li>What kinds of projects would benefit most from a transdisciplinary approach?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="adopt_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_ADOPT,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>SECTION 2: EXPERIENCE</h2>
                <h3>Have you previously worked on projects that adopted a transdisciplinary approach?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="adopt" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_ADOPT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>In what ways was it transdisciplinary?</li>
                        <li>What problems were encountered in working in transdisciplinary ways?</li>
                        <li>What were the rewards/benefits of working in transdisciplinary ways?</li>
                        <li>What key lessons did you draw from these experiences to help make transdisciplinary working more effective in future research?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="teamwork_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_TEAMWORK,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Please outline your experience of teamwork within large, complex projects</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="teamwork" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_TEAMWORK" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What were the challenges to effective teamwork and how were these met?</li>
                        <li>What were the benefits of working in large teams?</li>
                        <li>What key lessons did you draw from these experiences to help make teamwork more effective in future research?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="network_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_NETWORK,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>SECTION 3: IMPLEMENTATION</h2>
                <h3>What are your plans to contribute to the wider network?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="network" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_NETWORK" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>How will you contribute to the development of the network goals?</li>
                        <li>How will you support technology development across the network?</li>
                        <li>How will HQPs be involved in TD working?</li>
                        <li>How might different stakeholder groups (e.g. older adults, family care partners, health and social care providers, etc.) be engaged as team members of the project?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="synergy_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_SYNERGY,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Synergies between projects</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="synergy" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_SYNERGY" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are you plans for linking in with other projects in AGE-WELL?</li>
                        <li>How might your project benefit from working with other projects?
                            <ul>
                                <li>Sharing conceptual frameworks</li>
                                <li>Sharing methodologies</li>
                                <li>Sharing data</li>
                                <li>Sharing resources</li>
                                <li>Dissemination of findings/analyses (seminars and conferences)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="accept_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_ACCEPT,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How can we encourage acceptance of different theoretical and methodological approaches to research and team working practices?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="accept" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_ACCEPT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Consider:
                            <ul>
                                <li>Epistemologies, Concepts, Methods, Interpretational Frameworks</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>What opportunities do you see in AGE-WELL to develop transdisciplinary working practices?</li>
                        <li>What techniques do you feel could promote transdisciplinarity?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_SUPPORT,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>SECTION 4: SUPPORT AND EVALUATION</h2>
                <h3>How do you think CC3 (transdisciplinary working) can support the AGE-WELL network to achieve its goals?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="support" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_SUPPORT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Provide any ideas about support at the project, work package, crosscutting theme and
network level.
                            <ul>
                                <li>What kind of training would be most helpful?</li>
                                <li>What sorts of resources would be most helpful?</li>
                                <li>What communication strategies should be developed?</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="eval_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_3,CC_3_EVAL,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How can transdisiplinarity be evaluated within AGE-WELL so that we can establish what works well and what doesn’t?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="eval" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_3_EVAL" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are important outcomes related to transdisciplinarity?</li>
                        <li>How do we measure these outcomes?</li>
                        <li>What milestones and targets should be developed?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attach" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CC_3_ATTACH" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Additional Materials</h3>
                <small>If you have any additional materials, you can upload a pdf attachement</small><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cc4" tooltip="Training and Mentorship" name="CC4 TRAIN" blobSection="CC_PLANNING_4" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Briefing Notes</h3>
<p>Successfully developing and commercializing new technologies is a highly demanding process that requires well-rounded Highly Qualified Persons (HQPs) that are able to work effectively within a transdisciplinary environment. To achieve this we need to attract and retain world-class HQP in areas essential to Canadian economic and social development.</p>
<p>CC4 will support HQP training within the AGE-WELL Network through the development and implementation of novel training initiatives, events, and programs. AGE-WELL will provide a unique training environment that exposes trainees to multi-disciplinary research environments and to our industry and community partners through collaborations with existing research networks and partner universities. An important immediate outcome for the AGE-WELL Network is to establish training that promotes and encourages trainees to consider the economic, social, environmental, and ethical implications of their work.</p>
<p>HQPs include all students and trainees (Masters, PhD, Post-docs) within AGE-WELL projects, research associates and technicians, but may also include early-stage researchers and any faculty who might benefit from our training environment. We may also want to include personnel from partner organizations if training is required here- e.g. to build receptor capacity.</p>
<p>As well as scientific excellence, HQPs will need to demonstrate that their research has potential for real world impact and their research is aligned with AGE-WELL’s vision and strategic goals.</p>
<p>We also need to recognize that the majority of HQPs will not pursue academic careers. Indeed,
our trainees moving into receptor industries and government agencies represent a major component of building capacity within the Canadian economy.</p>
<p>CC4 will work closely with CCs1-3 to develop HQP with robust, transferrable skills. The training program will emphasize the knowledge and skills required for successful knowledge mobilization and commercialization and provide experiential learning in transdisciplinary work that will serve the HQPs throughout their careers. Mechanisms for enrichment include multi regional teams, co-supervision across disciplines, summer institutes, conferences, journal clubs, student exchanges and courses and workshops.</p>
<p>As a strategic first step we would like to identify the current strengths and weaknesses in training across the projects to enable the development of new initiatives and partnerships to equip HQPs with the right skills and knowledge.</p>
<p><b>Expectations for HQPs supported by AGE-WELL funds</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Attend AGE-WELL events (workshops, knowledge café’s, annual conference)</li>
    <li>Participate in AGE-WELL summer institute</li>
    <li>Take at least one course on knowledge mobilization, commercialization, project management</li>
    <li>Spend time with industry, public sector or community partners</li>
    <li>Acquire soft skills such as communication and team skills</li>
    <li>Acquire a deeper understanding of end user needs and ethical, economic and social implications of their work.</li>
</ul>
<b>Expectations of AGE-WELL Project Leads</b>
<p>To accomplish our training goals it is important for Project Leads to recognize that HQPs who are supported by AGE-WELL funds will need release time to participate in network activities outside of their research projects.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="train_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_TRAIN,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Description of type of HQP training activities will be conducted within your research project.</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="train" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_TRAIN" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What are your project objectives for HQP training?</li>
                        <li>What HQPs are likely to be involved?</li>
                        <li>How will you engage HQPs in your project activities?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="know_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_KNOW,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>The AGE-WELL training program needs to emphasize the knowledge and skills for successful knowledge mobilization, commercialization and transdisciplinary working.</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="know" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_KNOW" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Do members of your research team have any particular training expertise that could be relevant? If yes please state name of team member and describe expertise</li>
                        <li>Are there any courses or training initiatives that you are aware of that might be relevant for your HQP locally, provincially, or nationally? If yes please list</li>
                        <li>What resources or initiatives should CC4 develop for HQP training in:
                            <ul>
                                <li>Knowledge mobilization</li>
                                <li>Commercialization</li>
                                <li>Transdisciplinary work</li>
                                <li>Other (specify)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="outcome_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_OUTCOME,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>An important outcome for AGE-WELL is to create training initiatives that encourage HQPs to consider the economic, social, environmental and ethical implications of their work.</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="outcome" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_OUTCOME" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    List any suggestions you have for training that would address these considerations.
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="industry_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_INDUSTRY,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>The majority of our HQPs will not pursue academic careers but will be employed by industry or government or start their own business.</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="industry" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_INDUSTRY" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>What skills will these trainees need to be successful?</li>
                        <li>Are you aware of any initiatives or programs that could provide these skills? If yes, please list below.</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="other_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_OTHER,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What other knowledge, skills or training should AGE-WELL as an organization be providing to HQPs within the network?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="other" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_OTHER" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure_head" type="StaticReportItem" text="{getText(RP_CC_LEADER, CC_PLANNING_4,CC_4_MEASURE,0,0,{$project_id})}" title="Feedback">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>How should we measure the effectiveness of the HQP training program?</h3>
                {$item}<br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="measure" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="CC_4_MEASURE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <small>
                    <ul>
                        <li>How should HQP training be evaluated? List any potential measures/indicators.</li>
                        <li>How should this information be collected?</li>
                    </ul>
                </small>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="attach" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="CC_4_ATTACH" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Additional Materials</h3>
                <small>If you have any additional materials, you can upload a pdf attachement</small><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The following is a preview of the combined version of the CC Activity plans.  When the PDF is generated, five different PDFs will be created:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>A combined PDF of all four CC Activities.</li>
                    <li>CC1 K-MOB Activities</li>
                    <li>CC2 TECH-TRANS Activities</li>
                    <li>CC3 T-WORK Activities</li>
                    <li>CC4 TRAIN Activities</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>When the PDF is generated, five different PDFs will be created:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>A combined PDF of all four CC Activities.</li>
                    <li>CC1 K-MOB Activities</li>
                    <li>CC2 TECH-TRANS Activities</li>
                    <li>CC3 T-WORK Activities</li>
                    <li>CC4 TRAIN Activities</li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
