<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AGE-WELL Collaborative Impact Program Application" reportType="RP_CIP" pdfType="RPTP_CIP" pdfFiles="CIPApplicationPDF" ajax="true" disabled="true">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="NI">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="NI-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="2016 AGE-WELL Collaborative Impact Program" name="Program Description" type="ReportSection" title="2016 AGE-WELL Collaborative Impact Program">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Program Description</h3>
                
                <p>AGE-WELL’s Collaborative Impact Program is a matched funding program that is designed to leverage partnerships between academic researchers and industry, government (provincial) and community organizations in order to accelerate Canadian innovation and economic competitiveness, and improve the quality of life for older adults and/or caregivers.</p>
                
                <p>CIP funds will support <u>post-discovery</u> commercialization, business development, knowledge mobilization, or translation activities that align with the vision and mission of AGE-WELL. AGE-WELL will consider proposals for commercialization and/or knowledge mobilization, including:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>commercialization of technologies, products, and/or services, including but not limited to, business development, prototype development, market readiness and start-up activities</li>
                    <li>knowledge mobilization (KM), translation (KT) or exchange activities, including but not limited to, the implementation of KM/KT products or the introduction of new products/services into practice or policy settings</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>Award Value</h3>
                <p>Up to $75,000 investment from AGE-WELL with additional matched funds from partnering organizations. The overall project budget must include 25% cash contribution and 25% in-kind contribution from partners.</p>
                
                <p><i>(For example: to receive $75,000 from AGE-WELL, an application must include $37,500 cash and a further $37,500 measurable in-kind contributions from a partner(s) for a total project budget of $150,000)</i></p>
                
                <h3>Timeframe</h3>
                <p>12 month, non-renewable awards.</p>

                <p>Application Deadline: <b>Wednesday, March 30 by 5:00 pm EST</b></p>

                <h3>Eligibility Criteria</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>The competition is open to investigators working in the field of technology and aging based at Canadian institutions that are eligible to hold Tri-Council funds. Canadian universities and investigators who are not already members of the AGE-WELL network will be required to sign onto the Network Agreement prior to receiving funds.</li>
                    <li>Funded projects must be aligned with AGE-WELL’s overall mission and vision and at least one of AGE-WELL’s 8 Workpackages: <a target='_blank' href='http://agewell-nce.ca/research'>http://agewell-nce.ca/research.</a>.</li>
                    <li>Preference will be given to projects with the potential to achieve real-world impact within 12 months.</li>
                    <li>CIP funds cannot be used for activities funded through other AGE-WELL competitions (e.g. Core Research Program).</li>
                    <li>Researchers can hold only one of either AGE-WELL CIP or SIP (Strategic Investment Program) awards in the same fiscal year.</li> 
                    <li>Matching funds may come from provincial, private or public sector partners. Funds from federal research funding programs (e.g. CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC, Industry or Health Canada, other NCEs etc.) are <u>ineligible</u> as matching funds for the Collaborative Impact Program.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h3>Partnerships</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL is dedicated to identifying and developing collaborations with other organizations and stakeholders to leverage AGE-WELL funding through cash or in-kind contributions, and to create opportunities for commercialization, knowledge exchange or mobilization.</p>
                <p>CIP is a matched funding program. Cash and in-kind contributions are required from provincial, industry and/or community partners for this funding program. Projects will normally be expected to include partner organizations in dissemination or commercialization planning and should detail these in the application. For reporting purposes, all partnership activities should be quantified in the budget module and supported by a Letter of Support from each partnering organization.</p>
                
                <h3>Application Instructions</h3>
                <p><b>PART 1 - Narrative Application</b> (8 page max, minimum 12 pt font excluding Cover Sheet)</p>
                <p>Complete sections directly in Forum using the spaces provided. Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>
                <br />
                <p><b>PART 2 – Team, Budget & Milestones</b> (Team Summary, Budget and Budget Justification, Partner Contributions, Other Funds, Milestones)</p>
                <p>Complete Team Summary, HQP, Budget Justification and Other Funds directly in Forum using the sections and drop down menus provided.</p> 
                <p>Budget Template and Milestone Templates (Excel) are available in Forum (links in each section).  Download, complete and upload filled documents.  Any partner contributions should be added to the Budget Template and supported by a letter signed by the partner.</p>
                <p>Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>
                <br />
                <p><b>PART 3 - Investigator Bio</b> (2 page max, highlighting relevant experience) and <b>Partner Letter(s) of Support</b> (if applicable)</p>
                <p>Upload a brief bio (2 page max., PDF) for the principal investigator.  No specific format/template is required.</p>
                <p>Upload any letters of support from partners described in Part 2. Submit as PDF(s).</p>
                <p>Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cover" tooltip="Cover Sheet" name="Cover Sheet" blobSection="COVER_SHEET" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="i" type="TextReportItem" width="300px" blobItem="PROJECT">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li>
                    <b>Investigator Name: </b>{$user_name}&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>Institution: </b>{$user_uni}<br />
                    <b>Project Title:&nbsp;</b>{$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ii" type="TextReportItem" width="200px" blobItem="PARTNER">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Project Partner(s)</b>: {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iii" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" limit="150" blobItem="SUMMARY">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Provide a 150-word plain language summary of the purpose, rationale and anticipated impact(s) of the project.</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iv" type="IntegerReportItem" min="0" max="75000" width="43px" align="left" blobItem="INVESTMENT">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Total value of AGE-WELL investment requested:</b> ${$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="v_cash" type="IntegerReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="CASH" optional="true" min="0" max="75000" width="43px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Total value of current partner investment: Cash </b>${$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="v_inki" type="IntegerReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="INKI" optional="true" min="0" max="75000" width="43px">
            <![CDATA[
                    &nbsp;&nbsp;<b>In-kind </b>${$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="vi" type="SelectReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" options="WP1 NEEDS-OA|WP2 NEEDS-CG|WP3 TECH-FAI|WP4 TECH-APS|WP5 TECH-DD|WP6 TECH-MCH|WP7 POLICY-TECH|WP8 ETHICS-TECH" blobItem="WP">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>The proposed project is best aligned with AGE-WELL</b>
                    {$item}
                    (WP descriptions are available here: <a href='http://www.agewell-nce.ca' target="_blank">www.agewell-nce.ca</a>) 
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="narrative" tooltip="PART 1 - Narrative Application" title="PART 1 - Narrative Application" name="Narrative Application" blobSection="NARRATIVE" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>1) RATIONALE AND APPROACH</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="rational" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="RATIONAL">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Summarize the rationale for the project</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Why this project at this time?</li>
                        <li>What is the benefit/value-added of the proposed impact(s)?</li>
                        <li>What is unique about this project / how does it improve on previous work?</li>
                        <li>Describe any scientific validation, pilot work, prototype, or proof of concept activity related to this project that has been completed to date.</li>
                        <li>What is the strength of the evidence forming the basis for the planned dissemination and/or commercialization development activity?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="GOALS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>State the project goals and objectives</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>What is the ultimate goal(s) of the proposed initiative?</li>
                        <li>State the objectives that need to be achieved to realize the ultimate goal(s). (specific goals, objectives and milestones will be listed in an appendix)</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kt" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="KT">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Describe the commercialization, business strategy, or knowledge mobilization approach to be used</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>How will your proposed activities address target audience/market needs? (e.g., product development and distribution efforts, market gap/societal need/demand)</li>
                        <li>Describe how user sector contexts and needs have been accounted for </li>
                        <li>Describe your IP strategy</li>
                        <li>To whom will the evidence/knowledge/information/product be disseminated? Provide a sense of the size/scale of the target audience/market</li>
                        <li>Describe the competitive advantage of your product/business/start-up, your main competitors, and business model, if applicable)</li>
                        <li>For commercialization focused projects, describe how you anticipate taking the product/service to market. How will customers/end-users gain access to the product/service?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2) IMPACT AND EVALUTION</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="impact" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="IMPACT">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Describe the anticipated impacts and associated benefits and beneficiaries of this project</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Describe how your proposed project contributes to and/or facilitates the commercialization, translation, mobilization and/or policy use of research to accelerate Canadian innovation, and economic competitiveness, and to improve the lives of older adults and/or caregivers.</li>
                        <li>Identify the anticipated impacts of this project–what will change, who will benefit and how?</li>
                        <li>Describe any benefits to productivity, cost reductions or savings to the health system, tangible economic and/or social benefits</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="evaluate" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="EVALUATE">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>How and when will you evaluate this initiative?</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>How will you measure success of this project?</li>
                        <li>How will the results of the evaluation process provide feedback to future initiatives related to this initiative?</li>
                        <li>What are your plans for generating future investments in this project?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3) PROJECT TEAM AND PARTNERSHIPS</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="expertise" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="EXPERTISE">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Describe how the expertise of your team will contribute to the success of the proposed initiative</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="PARTNERS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Outline the partnerships involved and partner roles/responsibilities (e.g. dissemination, product development, testing and evaluation etc.).</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Identify all partners/partnership arrangements (contributions will be itemized in an appendix)</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="appendix" tooltip="PART 3 - Team, Budget &amp; Milestones" title="PART 2 - Team, Budget &amp; Milestones" name="Budget and Activities" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="APPENDIX">
        <ReportItem id="team" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="TEAM" labels="Team Member Name|Role|Institution/Organization|Expertise|Email" types="Text|Select(PL,NI,Partner)|Text|Textarea|Text" sizes="150||150||150" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Team Summary</h2>
                <p class='small'>Use the following code for Role:<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;PL:</b> Project Lead<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;NI:</b> Network Investigator<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;Partner</b></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP" labels="Name|Institution|Email|Level of Study/Position" types="Text|Text|Text|Text" sizes="150|150|150|" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="BUDGET" structure="AGEWELL_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="AGE-WELL Budget.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just1" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST1" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <p>Please use the following categories in your budget justification as appropriate. Note that CIP funding includes specific budget caps in some categories.</p>
                <ol>
                <li><b>Salaries to students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just2" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST2" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Salaries to non-students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just3" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST3" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Professional & Tech. Services/contracts</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Consultants and business development services (maximum $5,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just4" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST4" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Equipment</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Purchase of rental</li>
                        <li>Maintenance costs</li>
                        <li>Operating costs</li>
                        <li>Other equipment costs</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just5" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST5" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Computing and Software</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Specialized software licenses and e-communications costs</li>
                        <li>E-business enablement costs, website</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just6" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST6" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Materials, Supplies & Other expenditures</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Materials and Supplies</li>
                        <li>Patent costs (maximum $4,000)</li>
                        <li>Proof of Principle, product validation for market readiness</li>
                        <li>Prototype development (specify)</li>
                        <li>Communications/Marketing/Printing/Production (maximum $5,000)</li>
                        <li>Evaluation costs</li>
                        <li>Management and Networking (maximum $3,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just7" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST7" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Travel</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Field trips</li>
                        <li>Conference, technical shows</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="milestones" type="Upload" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="MILESTONES" mimeType="application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Milestones</h2>
                <a href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/AGE-WELL Milestones.xls'>Download Spreadsheet Template</a>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="bio" tooltip="PART 3 - Investigator Bios &amp; Partner Letter(s) of Support" title="PART 3 - Investigator Bios &amp; Partner Letter(s) of Support" name="Bio &amp; Letter of Support" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="BIO">
        <ReportItem id="bio" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="BIO" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Investigator Bio</h3>
                <p>Please submit a brief bio (2 page maximum) for each named investigator from Part 2, highlighting experience and activities relevant to the application.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="letter" type="UploadReportItem" blobItem="LETTER" mimeType="application/zip">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Partner Letter of Support</h3>
                <p>All cash and in-kind contributions must be supported by letters of support from the contributing partner. Please attach a letter of support signed by the partner organization as a zip archive.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
