<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AGE-WELL Core Research Program / Platform Project Program 2020-2024 End-of-Term Project Report" reportType="RP_CRP_REPORT" pdfType="RPTP_CRP_REPORT" pdfFiles="CRPReportPDF" personId="0" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="SD+">
        
        </Role>
        <Role role="PL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="PS">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPC">

        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="part1" tooltip="Impact Case Study" name="Impact Case Study" title="Part 1: Impact Case Study" blobSection="PART1" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="SUMMARY" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Please provide a short case study of outstanding work or achievement in any of the evaluation impact areas (Scientific Excellence, Networking and Partnerships, Knowledge Mobilization, Commercialization, and HQP Training). Case studies provide a concrete example of how a research project and its findings have contributed to real-world impact. These stories are a great opportunity to promote the amazing work accomplished within AGE-WELL. We will draw on these case studies as we promote the work accomplished over the past nine years. We encourage teams to insert, attach or provide links to any relevant images connected to this work.</p>
                <u>Language</u>
                <p>The case study is aimed at a very wide audience:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>avoid jargon and overly “academic” style of writing</li>
                    <li>assume the reader is not familiar with your disciplinary concepts and language</li>
                    <li>assume the reader is educated to a reasonable level</li>
                    <li>the tone should be less formal than usual academic writing, and be engaging and easy-to-read but still “serious”.</li>
                </ul>
                <b>i. Summary of the impact (indicative maximum 250 words/half page)</b>
                <p>This section should briefly summarise the specific impact or novel contribution that is being described in the case study.  This should be written in engaging way that will communicate clearly to a lay audience- it may be useful to contact someone in your Institutions Communications department to craft this section.</p>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="research" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="RESEARCH" rich="true" limit="500">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>ii. Underpinning research (indicative maximum 500 words/1 page)</b>
                <p>This section should outline the key research insights or project activities that underpinned the impact, and provide details of what, when, and by whom. References to specific research outputs that embody the research described in this section, and evidence of its quality, should be provided in the last two sections of this case study. Details of the following should be provided in this section:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Description of specific product/outcome</li>
                    <li>Summary of problem/challenge area</li>
                    <li>Brief description of the project- what, why, who, etc.</li>
                    <li>What was done in this project (research insights or other activities and outcomes- link to PRL stage) in respect to achieving impact</li>
                    <li>Brief description of outputs, products, etc. that contributed to impact</li>
                    <li>How did this contribute to successful outcomes and impact?</li>
                    <li>Illustrative materials- photographs, quotes, links to videos and recordings (not included in word count)</li>
                    <li>Dates of when it was carried out.</li>
                    <li>Names of the key researchers and what positions they held at the institution at the time of the research.</li>
                    <li>Any relevant key contextual information about this area of research.</li>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="details" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="DETAILS" rich="true" limit="500">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>iii. Details of the impact (indicative maximum 500 words)</b>
                <p>This section should provide a narrative to explain how this case study has made an impact and the nature and extent of the impact. The following should be provided:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>A clear explanation of the process or means through which the research led to, underpinned or made a contribution to the impact (for example, how it was disseminated, how it came to influence users or beneficiaries, or how it came to be exploited, taken up or applied).</li> 
                    <li>Where the case study was part of a wider body of research that contributed to the impact (for example, where there has been research collaboration with other institutions or grants), the case study should specify the particular contribution of the case study and acknowledge other key research contributions.</li>
                    <li>Beneficiaries – who or what community, constituency or organisation has benefitted, been affected or impacted on.</li>
                    <li>Nature of the impact – how they have benefitted, been affected or impacted on.</li>
                    <li>Evidence or indicators of the extent of the impact described, as appropriate to the case being made.</li>
                    <li>Dates of when these impacts occurred.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="references" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="REFERENCES" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>iv. References to the research (indicative maximum of six references)</b>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="other" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="OTHER" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>v. Other sources to corroborate the impact (indicative maximum of 5)</b>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="part2" tooltip="Future Impact" name="Future Impact" title="Part 2: Future Impact" blobSection="PART2" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="future_impact" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="FUTURE_IMPACT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The long-term impact of AGE-WELL’s Core Research Program / Platform Project Program will likely only be realized after the award term end date. Please list any anticipated outputs and outcomes beyond the award term.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="part3" tooltip="Leveraged Funding" name="Leveraged Funding" title="Part 3: Leveraged Funding" blobSection="PART3" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="funding" type="MultiText" blobItem="FUNDING" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" labels="Granting Organization|Award Program|Fiscal Year / Term|Amount ($)" sizes="100|150|100|100" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It is important that we understand and report on how the AGE-WELL investment has been leveraged to secure additional grant funding connected to this program of research.</p>

                <p>Please provide a list below of the following: 1)  grants obtained directly related to this program of research (including all provincial and federal sources) over the past five years, and 2) any proposed grant applications that have been/will be submitted based on the work developed in your AGE-WELL project.</p>
                
                <b>Do not include cash and in-kind contributions from partner organizations as these will have been reported previously to AGE-WELL.</b>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="part4" tooltip="Key Outputs" name="Key Outputs" title="Part 4: Key Outputs" blobSection="PART4" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="outputs" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="OUTPUTS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>An important part of AGE-WELL’s mandate is to promote and put into action key outputs from our federal funding. To achieve this, we are developing a knowledge repository of ‘shareable’ outputs to support and educate other project teams or trainees within the network, or make available outside the network, if appropriate and with permission. Note that we are not looking for academic journal publications, but rather guidelines, manuals, scoping reviews, white papers, policy briefs, educational materials, data sets, frameworks, toolkits, video/films and/or websites etc.</p>
                
                <p>Since your team has been reporting outputs on Forum for four years now, we expect that these key outputs have already been reported—we are looking for you to help us understand which ones you consider appropriate and relevant to share in order to support continued growth of AGE-WELL and development of the sector as a whole.</p>
                
                <p>Please list what you consider the top 5 ‘shareable’ outputs of this project. Please indicate whether each output should remain internal to AGE-WELL or whether you think it is ripe for broader dissemination (external). Please provide links and/or attachments of materials below.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Upload Attachments</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="jennifer@agewell-nce.ca,info@agewell-nce.ca" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
