<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Annual Report - EPIC Survey" reportType="RP_EPIC_REPORT" pdfType="RPTP_EPIC_REPORT" pdfFiles="EPICReportPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="0">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="HQP+">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="survey" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="Instructions" name="Instructions" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="instructions" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Key objectives:</b><br />
                <ul>
                    <li>To determine program graduates’ perspectives on the EPIC program Core Competencies and the extent to which these competencies were achieved</li>
                    <li>To determine the extent to which the EPIC program encouraged participants to consider the economic, social, environmental, and ethical implications of their work</li>
                    <li>To determine program graduates’ intentions for employment or continued education after completing the EPIC program</li>
                </ul>
                <b>Narrative and instructions to respondents:</b><br />
                <p>Thank you for agreeing to complete the Early Professionals, Inspired Careers (EPIC) exit survey.  This survey comprises the final report listed on your EPIC tab.  This survey should only take 10-15 minutes to complete.  As a graduate of the EPIC program, we value your opinions on the program’s strengths and areas for potential growth.</p>
                <p>As a reminder, the AGE-WELL EPIC Program intends to expose Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) to multi-disciplinary research environments, industry, and community partners. Through funding opportunities and experiential learning opportunities - including courses, workshops, collaboration opportunities, and mentorship - the program emphasizes the development of skills, ideas, teamwork, and relationship-building that are the building blocks of a successful career.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="survey" tooltip="Survey" name="Survey" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="SURVEY">
        <ReportItem id="info" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <table>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>Name:</b></td><td>{$user_name}</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>HQP Type:</b></td><td>{$user_sub_roles}</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>Institution:</b></td><td>{$user_uni}</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>Department:</b></td><td>{$user_dept}</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>Title:</b></td><td>{$user_level}</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td align="right"><b>Supervisor(s):</b></td><td>{$user_supervisors}</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1a" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1A" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Survey</h2>
                <p>Please respond to the following questions by selecting the most appropriate response:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li><b>EPIC Core Competencies - this section pertains to the 4 core competencies</b>
                        <p>When answering questions in this section, recall that the 4 Core Competencies of the AGE-WELL EPIC program are defined as follows:</p>

                        <p><b>Knowledge and Technology Exchange & Exploitation: A</b>ccelerate innovation and commercialization. Join our Knowledge Community and help establish Canada as a global leader in the development of technologies for healthy aging. Learn more about business planning, project management, “soft” skills training, post-discovery commercialization, knowledge dissemination and mobilization.</p>

                        <p><b>Transdisciplinary Research Skills: B</b>uild research capacity and expertise to achieve excellence in research. Transcend disciplinary boundaries to think and problem-solve creatively. Explore experiential design, co-production, and the importance of user research.</p>

                        <p><b>Ethics: C</b>lose the gap between innovative technologies and practice. Understand the ethical, privacy, and security factors that obstruct market access and success. How does big data affect your research?</p>

                        <p><b>Understanding Impact: D</b>rive practical solutions. Know the market, end user, and the relationship between technology and the built environment. Learn more about health technology assessment, technology evaluation, and the social, economic, environmental, and commercial implications of your work.</p>
                        
                        <ol type="a">
                            <li>The EPIC Core Competencies are clearly defined
                            {$item}<br />
                            </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1b" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1B" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC Core Competencies are sufficiently comprehensive
                {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1c" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1C" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC Core Competencies are relevant to my work and/or research
                {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1d" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1D" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program helped increase my knowledge and awareness in “Knowledge and Technology Exchange & Exploitation”
                {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1e" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1E" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program helped increase my knowledge and awareness in “Transdisciplinary research skills”
                {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1f" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1F" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program helped increase my knowledge and awareness in “Ethics”
                {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="1g" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="1G" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program helped increase my knowledge and awareness in “Understanding Impact”
                {$item}<br />
                </li></ol></li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2a" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2A" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>This section pertains to the EPIC program elements
                <ol type="a">
                    <li>Participation in the EPIC program has helped me define or redefine my career goals
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2a_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2A_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples of how: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2b" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2B" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>Participation in the EPIC program has afforded me additional insights into career opportunities.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2b_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2B_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples of how: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2c" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2C" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>Participation in the EPIC program has afforded me additional insights into my own work and/or research.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2c_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2C_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples of how: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2d" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2D" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program requirements afforded me the flexibility and autonomy to direct my own learning and development
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2d_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2D_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples of how: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2e" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2E" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program added value to the formal training initiatives already available through my academic community or institution.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2e_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2E_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please specify: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2f" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2F" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>Participation in the EPIC program will help me secure future employment with industries capable of exploiting technology for healthy aging.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2f_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2F_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please specify which activities were particularly helpful in this regard: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2g" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2G" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The multidisciplinary and multi-sectoral nature of the EPIC program provided me unique mentorship opportunities. 
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2g_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2G_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2h" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2H" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The multidisciplinary and multi-sectoral nature of the EPIC program provided me unique training opportunities.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2h_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2H_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2i" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2I" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program exposed me to economic, social, and ethical implications of my research.
                        {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2j" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2J" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The EPIC program provided me opportunities to become involved in the initial stages of research discovery and its practical application for social and economic benefits.
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2j_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2J_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please provide examples: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2k" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2K" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The format of the EPIC program activities fostered networking and collaboration amongst researchers.
                        {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2l" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2L" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The format of the EPIC program activities fostered networking and collaboration amongst industry partners.
                        {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2m" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2M" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>The format of the EPIC program activities fostered networking and collaboration amongst other stakeholders (policy makers, end-users etc.).
                        {$item}<br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2n" type="RadioReportItem" blobItem="2N" options="Strongly Disagree|Disagree|Neutral|Agree|Strongly Agree" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>Continued access to EPIC program activities will help me remain engaged with AGE-WELL upon completion of the EPIC program
                        {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2n_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2N_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                    Please comment: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="2o_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="2O_EX" height="75px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Please describe other activities that could be offered by AGE-WELL to encourage the development of the Core Competencies: {$item}<br /><br />
                </li></ol></li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="3a_ex" type="Textarea" blobItem="3A_EX">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Now that you have completed the EPIC program, what work and/or research you are currently engaged in.? {$item}<br /><br />
                </li></ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="documents" type="UploadReportItem" blobItem="DOCUMENTS" fileSize="10">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Supporting Documents</h3>
                <p>Please collate and upload here your evidence of EPIC activity completion if not already emailed to <a href='mailto:samantha@agewell-nce.ca'>samantha@agewell-nce.ca</a>.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="appendix" tooltip="Appendix" name="Appendix" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="appendix" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Relevant performance indicators from <a href='http://www.nce-rce.gc.ca/ReportsPublications-RapportsPublications/NCE-RCE/ProgramGuide-GuideProgramme_eng.asp' target='_blank'>NCE Website</a></p>
                <h3>Expected results and outcomes</h3>
                <p>The NCE Program has the responsibility of delivering on short, medium and long-term commitments. These are categorized as immediate, intermediate and long-term outcomes of the NCE Program. These outcomes are achieved through the selection and funding of NCE networks who collectively, and through collaboration with the NCE Secretariat, deliver on these outcomes. The program outcomes include:</p>
                <p>Immediate outcomes:
                <ul>
                    <li>increase networking and collaboration among researchers from Canada and abroad;</li>
                    <li>develop leading-edge research findings that are relevant to the needs of the user sector (e.g. private and public sectors, non-governmental organizations, and others) and Canada’s socio-economic development;</li>
                    <li>create nation-wide, multidisciplinary and multisectoral research partnerships between universities and the user sector (e.g. private and public sectors, non-governmental organizations, and others); and</li>
                    <li>establish training that promotes multidisciplinary and multisectoral research approaches and encourages trainees to consider the economic, social, environmental, and ethical implications of their work.</li>
                </ul></p>
                <p>Intermediate/long-term outcomes: 
                <ul>
                    <li>accelerate the exchange of research results within the Network and the use of this knowledge within Canada by organizations that can harness it for Canadian economic and social development;</li>
                    <li>attract and retain world-class researchers and highly qualified personnel (HQP) in areas essential to Canadian economic and social development;</li>
                    <li>create functional, multi-regional, and interdisciplinary research teams;</li>
                    <li>develop a pool of HQP in areas essential to Canadian economic and social development; and</li>
                    <li>increase Canada’s international visibility and reputation.</li>
                </ul></p>
                <h3>Development of Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP)</h3>
                <p>The training and retention of HQP is imperative to maximize the effectiveness of the Networks’ contribution to the wealth, wellness and well-being of Canadians.  The Training Program proposed by the Network is expected to add value to the formal training initiatives already available through the academic community and should aim at helping HQP find employment in the Canadian economy (i.e., private sector partners, government, etc.). The multidisciplinary and multisectoral nature of a network should be utilized to provide unique mentorship and training opportunities to maximize HQP retention and integration in all facets of the workforce.<br />
                Elements being considered are:
                    <ul>
                        <li>the ability to attract, develop and retain outstanding researchers in research areas and technologies critical to Canadian productivity, economic growth, public policy and quality of life; and</li>
                        <li>training strategies that expose HQP to the full range of economic, social, and ethical implications of the Network’s research by involving them in activities from the initial research discovery to its application through to practical social and economic benefits.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
