<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="EPIC-AT Award 2023" reportType="RP_EPIC_REVIEW" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2023">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="Evaluator">
            <SectionPermission id="instructions" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="materials" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="instructions" tooltip="General Instructions" name="General Instructions" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>EPIC-AT is pleased offer Black, Indigenous, and racialized early career researchers funding to support patient-oriented research and patient engagement. Funding for these awards was made available through the Strategy for Patient-Oriented Research (SPOR) Supplement to CIHR Health Research Training Platforms.</p>

                <p>EPIC-AT is built on a foundation of equity, diversity, inclusion, and accessibility. Racialized people comprise over one-fifth of the Canadian population, yet are significantly underrepresented as both faculty members and senior university leaders (Cukier, 2021). Moreover, as found by an Innovation, Science, and Economic Development Canada sponsored survey, tenured faculty tend to be less racially diverse and more likely to be male.</p>

                <p>These awards are meant to increase financial support for Black, Indigenous, and other racialized early career researchers to pursue patient-oriented research and patient engagement activities and help build their independent research programs as they pertain to digital health solutions for older adults with complex health needs.</p>
                
                <h3>Review Form and Instructions</h3>
                <p>Prior to undertaking the reviews, please familiarize yourself with the EPIC-AT Application Form and Information Package provided to all applicants.</p>

                <p>These Fellowships are, first and foremost, a training grant and you will see this reflected in the adjudication criteria and weighting below. Through these Fellowships we are hoping to support candidates with strong potential for future impact both within and outside of academia.</p>

                Our ideal Fellows demonstrate:
                <ul>
                    <li>Vision for their research that goes beyond traditional disciplines and silos</li>
                    <li>New ideas and approaches to old problems</li>
                    <li>Keen willingness to learn new skills</li>
                    <li>Awareness of the importance of non-traditional KT including commercial and social impact</li>
                    <li>Strong identification with EPIC-AT vision</li>
                </ul>

                <p>Emphasis here could and should be on potential rather than solely on the technicalities of the research proposal itself – particularly for those at the Master’s or early PhD level. Consider the value the applicant will gain from being part of the EPIC-AT training environment.</p>

                <p>A key aspect of EPIC-AT’s training philosophy is that we have the ability to fund Fellows who may not be funded through traditional funding sources (e.g. CIHR, NSERC, SSHRC) or may not have significant numbers of peer-reviewed publications and presentations.</p>

                <p>We are looking to fund individuals who are thinking “outside of the box”, and who are interested in pursuing non-traditional roles within their training program.</p>

                <p>Please use the following adjudication criteria when reviewing applications. You will note that the criteria weighs quite heavily applicant potential and desire to participate in the training program:</p>
                <table class="wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Objectives & Rationale</td>
                        <td valign="top">30%</td>
                        <td valign="top">
                            <ul style='margin-top:0;'>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>the activity or project’s relevance to EPIC-AT values and mission</li>
                                <li>originality or novelty of proposed activity or project</li>
                                <li>proposal demonstrates how EDI principles and best practices inform activities</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Deliverables & Feasibility</td>
                        <td valign="top">40%</td>
                        <td valign="top">
                            <ul style='margin-top:0;'>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>appropriateness of the methods and theoretical approach</li>
                                <li>probability that the objectives will be met within the timeline proposed</li>
                                <li>involvement of partners or stakeholders in the design and conduct of proposed activities</li>
                                <li>appropriateness of requested budget and justification of proposed costs</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Potential Impact</td>
                        <td valign="top">30%</td>
                        <td valign="top">
                            <ul style='margin-top:0;'>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>potential positive impact on the lives of older adults and caregivers</li>
                                <li>the associated benefits to older adults and caregivers is feasibly described</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>

                <h3>Numerical Scoring</h3>
                
                <p>EPIC-AT Fellowship applications will be assigned a score for each of the three criteria above, based on the following scoring table. The appropriate weighting is then applied to arrive at a final score. Applications must receive an average score of 6 or higher and receive at least a 5 in each of the three criteria to be recommended for funding.</p>
                
                <p>To make the review process as simple as possible, provide a single overall score for each criterion using the following scale:</p>

                <table class="wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left" style="width:6em;">Score</th>
                        <th align="left">Descriptor</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>8-9</td>
                        <td>Very good to excellent</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>6-7</td>
                        <td>Good to very good</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>4-5</td>
                        <td>Satisfactory to good</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Below 4</td>
                        <td>Unsatisfactory</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>

                <h3>Comments</h3>

                <p>Please use the comment boxes to justify your score. We have provided some questions to guide scoring on each criterion. Please bear these in mind, but use your own judgment if you think other factors are relevant. There is also an overall comments box where you can highlight the key attributes of the applicant.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="materials" tooltip="Download HQP Application PDFs" name="Materials" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
            <table align="left">
                <tr>
                    <th style="min-width:110px;">HQP Name</th>
                    <th style="min-width:125px;">Application PDF</th>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItemSet id="hqp_materials" type="MaterialsReportItemSet" subType="EPIC-2023">
            <ReportItem id="hqp_pdf" type="PDFReportItem" reportType="EPIC-AT2023" width="100%" project="true">
                <![CDATA[<tr><td>{$user_name}</td><td>{$item}</td>]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItem id="letters" arrayId="letters" type="EliteUploadedLetters" blobReport="RP_EPIC_AT2" blobSection="2" blobItem="LETTERS" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" personId="{$user_id}" showStatus="false" optional="true">
                <![CDATA[
                    <td>{$item}</td></tr>
                ]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="HQP Review" name="HQP Review" blobSection="HQP_REVIEW" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItemSet id="hqp_materials" type="MaterialsReportItemSet" subType="EPIC-2023">
            <ReportItemSet id="toggle" type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" title="{$user_name}">
                <ReportItem id="overall" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_OVERALL_COMM" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <h2>1. Overall comments</h2>
                        <small>
                            <ul>
                                <li>What are key strengths of the proposal/applicant?</li>
                                <li>What are the weaknesses?</li>
                                <li>Is this applicant representative of AGE-WELL’s vision for a new type of HQP?</li>
                                <li>Any other comments?</li>
                            </ul>
                        </small>
                        {$item}
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                
                <ReportItem id="goals" type="RadioReportItem" orientation="horizontal" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_GOALS" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" options="1|2|3|4|5|6|7|8|9">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <h2>2. Objectives & Rationale (30%)</h2>
                        <small>
                            <ul>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>the activity or project’s relevance to EPIC-AT values and mission</li>
                                <li>originality or novelty of proposed activity or project</li>
                                <li>proposal demonstrates how EDI principles and best practices inform activities</li>
                            </ul>
                        </small>
                        <b>Overall Score:</b>&nbsp;{$item}<br />
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                <ReportItem id="goals_comm" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_GOALS_COMM" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <b>Comments:</b>
                        {$item}
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                
                <ReportItem id="deliv" type="RadioReportItem" orientation="horizontal" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_DELIV" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" options="1|2|3|4|5|6|7|8|9">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <h2>3. Deliverables & Feasibility (40%)</h2>
                        <small>
                            <ul>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>appropriateness of the methods and theoretical approach</li>
                                <li>probability that the objectives will be met within the timeline proposed</li>
                                <li>involvement of partners or stakeholders in the design and conduct of proposed activities</li>
                                <li>appropriateness of requested budget and justification of proposed costs</li>
                            </ul>
                        </small>
                        <b>Overall Score:</b>&nbsp;{$item}<br />
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                <ReportItem id="deliv_comm" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_DELIV_COMM" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <b>Comments:</b>
                        {$item}
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                
                <ReportItem id="impact" type="RadioReportItem" orientation="horizontal" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_IMPACT" blobSubItem="{$user_id}" options="1|2|3|4|5|6|7|8|9">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <h2>4. Potential Impact (30%)</h2>
                        <small>
                            <ul>
                                <li style='margin-top:0;'>potential positive impact on the lives of older adults and caregivers</li>
                                <li>the associated benefits to older adults and caregivers is feasibly described</li>
                            </ul>
                        </small>
                        <b>Overall Score:</b>&nbsp;{$item}<br />
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
                <ReportItem id="impact_comm" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_REVIEW_IMPACT_COMM" blobSubItem="{$user_id}">
                    <![CDATA[
                        <b>Comments:</b>
                        {$item}
                    ]]>
                </ReportItem>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
