<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="EPIC-AT Health Research Training Platform Fellowships (2022)" headerName="{$user_name}: {$hqp_application_uni} / {$hqp_application_program}" reportType="RP_EPIC_AT" pdfType="RPTP_EPIC_AT" pdfFiles="EPIC-AT" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2022">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="HQP" subRole="EPIC-AT">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Information" name="Information" title="EPIC-AT Health Research Training Platform Fellowships (2022)" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Information Package</h2>
                <h3>Instructions</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>The application is comprised of an online application form and supporting documents detailed below. Late or incomplete applications will not be reviewed. Please note that this includes letters of reference.</li>
                    <li>Applicants are strongly recommended to complete the EPIC-AT HRTP Fellowship application (Section C of this package in either English or French) using preferred word processing software. The online application portal will open on 23 May, 2022.</li>
                    <li>Once you are ready to submit your application online, if you have not already done so, you must register with the AGE-WELL Forum Research Portal at https://forum.agewell-nce.ca/index.php/Special:HQPRegister (the form will ask for your name and email). After you submit the registration form, the system will create an account and send your credentials to the email address you provided. Once you login, you will have to reset your temporary password.</li>
                    <li>The “My Applications” link is in the top right of the page you will reach after resetting your password. Please select “EPIC-AT Award 2022.” Copy your application material and upload supporting documents to the AGE-WELL Forum Research Portal website by 5pm ET on 13 June, 2022.</li>
                    <li>Letters of support must be sent directly to training@agewell-nce.ca (details in Section B of this package).</li>
                    <li>Notice of Admissions will be received by August, 2022. Expected start date of fellowship is 1 September, 2022</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Contact Information:<br />
                <a href='mailto:training@agewell-nce.ca'>training@agewell-nce.ca</a></p>
                
                <h3>Background Information</h3>
                <p><b>About EPIC-AT HRTP</b></p>
                <p>The Early Professionals, Inspired Careers in AgeTech Health Research Training Platform (EPIC-AT HRTP) is a national training platform that will prepare graduate students, postdoctoral fellows and early career researchers to be future leaders in digital health solutions for older adults with complex health needs.</p>

                <p>Powered by AGE-WELL, EPIC-AT is led by researchers from 11 universities and research hospitals across 6 Canadian provinces. It is hosted at the University of Toronto. This unique platform is funded by the Canadian Institutes of Health Research (CIHR) with additional support provided by 41 collaborating organizations from across Canada.</p>

                <p>The competency-based, experiential learning platform is an extension of AGE-WELL’s globally-leading EPIC training program and will provide one-year fellowships to graduate students, postdoctoral fellows and early career researchers at Canadian institutions.</p>
                
                <p><b>FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM</b></p>
                <p>EPIC-AT Fellowships provide a minimum of $8000 to trainees and $10,000 to Early Career Researchers. Fellowships are intended to enable promising new scholars to participate fully in an exclusive 1 year training program. The program will focus on developing new skills and providing a breadth of experience in transdisciplinary working, stakeholder engagement and co-creation, the research-policy dynamic and the innovation and implementation process. The program will equip fellows to develop, implement and evaluate digital technologies that help older Canadians with complex health needs age safely, independently and with dignity in the setting of their choice.</p>

                <p>EPIC-AT is built on a foundation of equity, diversity, inclusion, and accessibility. We welcome and strongly encourage applications from all individuals including women, Indigenous peoples, visible minorities, persons with disabilities, members of the LGBTQ2S+ communities, mature students and all others who can contribute to the diversification of ideas to better support an increasingly diverse older Canadian population. You are encouraged to self-identify if you wish to do so.</p>

                <p>Indigenous older adults are one of the most rapidly growing group of seniors in Canada. Due to the continued effects of colonization and systemic biases, Indigenous older adults face a higher and rising prevalence of complex health needs including multimorbidity. It is imperative to swiftly develop and implement culturally safe and appropriate solutions. As such, EPIC-AT welcomes applications from those who explicitly use Indigenous Ways of Knowing and will award a minimum of 2 Fellowships to self-identified Indigenous trainees or ECRs.</p>

                We expect to offer the following 1 year fellowships in this 2022 call:
                <ul>
                    <li>20 Master’s, PhD, and Postdoctoral Fellowships at minimum $8,000</li>
                    <li>3 Early Career Researcher Fellowships at minimum $10,000</li>
                </ul>

                <p>This represents the minimum value of fellowships. A number of postsecondary institutions and research institutes have agreed provide top up funding and/or travel funds to successful applicants from their institutions. Eligible applicants will automatically be considered for these additional funds; no additional application is required.</p>
                
                <p><b>Benefits</b></p>
                These fellowships are an opportunity for trainees and early career researchers to:
                <ul>
                    <li>gain in-depth, specialized expertise in developing, implementing and evaluating digital health solutions for seniors with complex health needs</li>
                    <li>access to multi-sectoral mentors and sponsors</li>
                    <li>participate in value-added professional development training, internship and lab exchange opportunities</li>
                    <li>network with a community of AgeTech researchers and professionals</li>
                    <li>receive support to identify and attain career goals</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p><b>Eligibility</b></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Domestic and international graduate students or postdoctoral fellows must participate full-time in their respective program at a Canadian post-secondary institution or research institute.</li>
                    <li>Early career researcher applicants must be within the first 5 years (60 months) of a full-time academic appointment at a Canadian post-secondary institution or research institute.</li>
                    <li>All applicants must be engaged in academic study/research aligned with the mission and vision of EPIC-AT and willing to participate fully in the training platform program.</li>
                    <li>Applicants may not hold an AGE-WELL Annual Graduate and Postdoctoral Award concurrently with an EPIC-AT Fellowship.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p><b>Program Requirements</b></p>
                <p><i>Training</i></p>
                <p>Fellowship holders will be automatically enrolled in the 1-year EPIC-AT training and mentorship program and are expected to participate actively in online courses, seminar series, professional development activities, a capstone project and annual meeting. The expected time commitment of the training and mentorship program is approximately 50-60 hours over the course of 1 year.</p>
                
                <p><i>Reporting</i></p>
                <p>Fellowship holders are required to complete Individual Development Plans and report on their publications, presentations, and progress made towards goals.</p>

                <p>Fellow institutions will report on expenditures of EPIC-AT funds by submitting a Form 300 to training@agewell-nce.ca no later than April 30 of each year for the duration of the fellowship.</p>
                
                <p><i>Acknowledging EPIC-AT</i></p>
                <p>EPIC-AT fellows will acknowledge the fellowship program in their presentations, publications, and other knowledge translation activities related to research conducted during their fellowship period.</p>
                
                <p><b>Adjudication Criteria</b></p>
                <p>All applications will undergo an administrative round of review to confirm eligibility and relevance of the applicant’s research to stakeholders’ lived experiences.</p>
                
                <p>Eligible applications will then be reviewed by a team of field experts using the following criteria:</p>
                <table class="wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Alignment with EPIC-AT Program Goals</td>
                        <td valign="top">25%</td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>the applicant’s research is relevant to EPIC-AT values and mission</li>
                                <li>the applicant seeks to go beyond traditional disciplinary boundaries</li>
                                <li>the applicant is interested in creating real-world solutions</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Personal Statement</td>
                        <td valign="top">25%</td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>achievements of the applicant relative to other researchers at the same career stage</li>
                                <li>the applicant demonstrates a vested interest in their research and career development</li>
                                <li>the applicant has clearly identified the benefits of participating in EPIC-AT</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Scholarly Merit</td>
                        <td valign="top">25%</td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>the applicant’s research is original or novel</li>
                                <li>the appropriateness of the methods and theoretical approach</li>
                                <li>probability that the objectives will be met within the timeline proposed</li>
                                <li>involvement of partners or stakeholders in the design and conduct of proposed activities</li>
                                <li>the applicant has or will consider EDI in research</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign="top">Potential Impact and Feasibility</td>
                        <td valign="top">25%</td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>the applicant’s research has potential positive impact on the lives of older adults and caregivers</li>
                                <li>the associated benefits to older adults and caregivers feasibly described</li>
                                <li>the applicant’s letters of reference indicate that the applicant and their work have excellent potential positive impact</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                
                <p><b>Required Documents Checklist</b></p>
                <p>Award applicants must submit the following:</p> 
                <ul>
                    <li>Online application form in Forum</li>
                    <li>Two confidential letters of support (one must be from your current or proposed supervisor; in the case of ECRs one letter must be from a department head or equivalent)</li>
                    <li>Trainee applicants must provide formal evidence of enrolment in a Master’s or Doctoral program or Post-Doctoral position</li>
                    <li>Curriculum Vitae (no specified format)</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p><b>Important Dates</b></p>
                Forum Application Opens: 23 May, 2022<br />
                Completed Applications Due: 13 June, 2022<br />
                Results Available: August, 2022<br />
                Fellowship Term: 1 September 2022 - 31 August 2022<br />
                Funding Disbursement Schedule: 1 September 2022, 1 March 2022
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="application" tooltip="Application Form" name="Application Form" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_FORM" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table style='width: 100%;'>
                    <tr>
                        <td colspan='2'><h3>1. ADMINISTRATIVE INFORMATION<br /><small>Please note that the information provided here is not used to adjudicate applications and will not affect your ranking.</small></h3></td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Applicant Name:</b></td><td>{$user_name}</td></tr>
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Email Address:</b></td><td>{$user_email}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="status" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_STAT" width="425px" placeholder="e.g., PhD Year 1, Occupational therapy or Assistant Professor, Year 3">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Academic Status and Department:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="supervisor" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUP" width="325px" placeholder="If you are an ECR, please leave this blank">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Supervisor Name:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="uni" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UNI" width="325px" placeholder="Please list the institution where funds will be held">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Institution/University:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="level" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_LVL" orientation="vertical" options="Master's (8,000)|PhD ($8,000)|Postdoctoral ($8,000)|Early Career Researcher ($10,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Fellowship Category</b><br /><small>(please note that this represents the minimum value; eligible applicants will be automatically considered for institutional supplements and matching funds)</small></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="level" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_LVL" orientation="vertical" options="AGE-WELL NCE|Centre de recherche Institut universitaire de gériatrie de Montréal (CRIUGM)|Reseau provincial de recherche en adaptation-réadaptation (REPAR)|Réseau Québécois de recherche sur le viellissement (RQRV)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Memberships</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="project_title" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="PROJECT_TITLE" width="400px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Research Project Title:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_KEYWORDS" multiple="true" max="6" sizes="180">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Keywords (maximum 6):</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="lay_summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="LAY_SUMMARY" rich="true" limit="200">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Lay Summary</b><br />
                        <p>Please note that the lay summary of your application will be reviewed and scored by stakeholder for relevance. Please write the summary in English.</p>

                        The lay summary should address each of the following questions:
                        <ol>
                            <li>Background: What do we already know about the problem?</li>
                            <li>Objective: What question does your study address?</li>
                            <li>Method: How will the research be carried out? How is this different from previous studies?</li>
                            <li>Implications: How will the anticipated results improve the lives of older adults with complex health needs and/or their caregivers?</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="age" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="AGE" orientation="vertical" options="18-24 years old|25-34 years old|35-44 years old|45-54 years old|55-64 years old|65-74 years old|75+ years old|I prefer not to answer" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'><h3>2. Self-Identification Form</h3>
                        <p>Please note that the information provided here will not be shared. It will not be used to adjudicate applications and will not affect your ranking. This information is solely collected so the platform can monitor the equity performance of programs and design new measures that achieve greater equity, diversity and inclusion in the research enterprise.</p>
                        
                        <p>All applications for fellowships require you to complete a self-identification form; however, if you would prefer not to self-identify and/or provide the requested information, you may select “I prefer not to answer" for any or all of the questions.</p>
                        
                        <p>Any self-identification statistics shared will always be reported in aggregate form to ensure protection of the identity of any individual.</p>
                        
                        <p>The collection of this information is an essential part of efforts to improve EDI in science and research. For further information, please see the Tri-Agency's policy on Self-Identification Data Collection in Support of EDI and Canada's 50-30 Challenge.</p>
                        
                        <p>See the Tri-Agency's policy on Self-Identification Data Collection in Support of EDI here: <a href='https://science.gc.ca/eic/site/063.nsf/eng/h_97615.html' target='_blank'>https://science.gc.ca/eic/site/063.nsf/eng/h_97615.html</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Age:</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="gender" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="GENDER" orientation="vertical" options="Woman|Man|Gender fluid, nonbinary and/or Two Spirit|LGBTQ2IA+|My gender identity and/or sexual orientation is not listed above.|I prefer not to answer" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Self-Identified Gender Identity and Sexual Orientation:</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="gender_other" type="Text" width="300px" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="GENDER_OTHER" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    If your gender identity or sexual orientation were not listed, and you would like to specify, please do so here:<br />
                    {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="indigenous" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="INDIGENOUS" orientation="vertical" options="First Nations (Includes status, treaty or registered Indians, as well as non-status and non-registered Indians)|Métis|Inuit/Inuk|I prefer not to answer|Not applicable" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Do you identify as a member of any of the following Indigenous populations:</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="ethnicities" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="ETHNICITIES" orientation="vertical" options="Black|Persons of mixed origin (with one parent in one of the Visible Minority communities listed)|Japanese|Filipino|Non-white West Asian, North African/Arab (includes Egyptian; Libyan; Lebanese; Iranian; etc.)|Non-white Latin American (includes Indigenous peoples from Central and South America, etc.)|Chinese|Korean|South Asian/East Indian (includes Indian from India; Bangladeshi; Pakistani; East Indian from Guyana, Trinidad, East Africa; etc.)|Southeast Asian (includes Burmese, Cambodian, Laotian; Thai; Vietnamese; etc.)|White|My ethnicity is not listed here|I prefer not to answer|Not applicable" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Do you identify with any of the following ethnicities:</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="ethnicities_other" type="Text" width="300px" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="ETHNICITIES_OTHER" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    If your ethnicity was not listed above, and you would like to specify, please do so here:<br />
                    {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="disability" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="DISABILITY" orientation="vertical" options="Yes|No|I prefer not to answer" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Are you a person living with a disability?</b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="postsecondary" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="POSTSECONDARY" orientation="vertical" options="Yes|No|I prefer not to answer" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>Are you a first generation postsecondary student?<br />
This is defined as an individual whose parents did not complete postsecondary education. </b></td><td valign="top" style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="GOALS" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'><h3>3. ALIGNMENT WITH EPIC-AT PROGRAM</h3>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Statement of alignment with EPIC-AT Program Goals</b><br />
                        <p>EPIC-AT is inviting fellowship applications from those trainees and ECRs researching in AgeTech, specifically related to digital health solutions for older adults with complex health needs and their caregivers.</p>

                        In this section, applicants should describe: 
                        <ol>
                            <li>How does your research connect to research foci of EPIC-AT? How does your work align with its mission?</li>
                            <li>Why is this work important to you?</li>
                            <li>How does your project transcend typical disciplinary boundaries?</li>
                            <li>Will this work result in real-world solutions? Why or why not? If yes, how?</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="bio" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="BIO" rich="true" limit="200">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'><h3>4. PERSONAL STATEMENT</h3>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Biography</b><br />
                        <p>EPIC-AT Fellows will be the catalyst that drives forward the Canadian innovation landscape in AgeTech in the digital health solutions for older adults with complex health needs and their caregivers.</p>

                        In this section, applicants should describe:
                        <ol>
                            <li>What past experiences and achievements make you an ideal EPIC-AT Fellow?</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="career" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="CAREER" rich="true" limit="350">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Career Path</b><br />
                        In this section applicants should describe:
                        <ol>
                            <li>What are your career goals?</li>
                            <li>Where do you see yourself in 5-10 years?</li>
                            <li>What skills gaps have you identified for yourself that you would like to fill over the next year?</li>
                            <li>How do you see EPIC-AT helping you achieve your goals?</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="focus" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="FOCUS" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'><h3>5. SCHOLARLY MERIT AND QUALITY OF PROPOSED RESEARCH</h3>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Research focus and objectives</b><br />
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>What is the overall aim of your research?</li>
                            <li>What are your specific research questions (if appropriate)</li>
                            <li>List your specific objectives - these should include both the research objectives AND the ”non-academic” objectives, such as knowledge transfer etc. (these objectives should be related to the specific project activities that will be mapped out in “tasks/activities” in the next section)</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="achieve" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="ACHIEVE" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>How will you achieve your project goals?</b><br />
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Brief overview of the approach (design/methods) you will use to meet your project objectives</li>
                            <li>Describe the type of research being undertaken e.g. technology development, review, feasibility study, pilot study, requirements analysis, prototype development, intervention study, evaluation study, etc.</li>
                            <li>Describe the tasks and activities planned (provide detail on specific tasks to be carried out to meet the project objectives you identified above). “Activities” may include research activities, KT, innovation, commercialization, team-building and training, etc.</li>
                            <li>Provide specific timing of the various tasks, activities and milestones, where milestones are critical points in the project (e.g., completion of a task)</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="engagement" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="ENGAGEMENT" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Stakeholder Engagement</b><br />
                        <p>Stakeholder engagement is a foundational aspect of EPIC-AT’s approach to research excellence. In this section, describe:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>How have, or how will, the principles of EDI be incorporated into your research plan?</li>
                            <li>Are partners and/or stakeholders involved in the design and conduct of proposed activities? If yes, how? If no, why not?</li>
                        </ol>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="impact" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="IMPACT" rich="true" limit="200">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'><h3>6. POTENTIAL IMPACT AND FEASIBILITY</h3>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Potential Impact</b><br />
                        <p>In this section, please provide a brief statement of the potential positive impact your work will have on the lives of older adults with complex health needs and their caregivers.</p>

                        <p>As applicable, address the following:</p>

                        <p><b>Social innovation</b><br />
                        What are practical benefits of your research to the wider community?</p>

                        <p><b>Technological innovation</b><br />
                        What are the novel aspects and contributions of your research from a technical point of view?</p>

                        <p><b>Policy and practice innovation</b><br />
                        How might policies, services and care be transformed by your research?</p>

                        <p><b>Scientific innovation</b><br />
                        What are the key scientific outputs from this research?</p>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="impact_plan" type="Textarea" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="IMPACT_PLAN" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2'>
                        <b>Impact Plan</b><br />
                        <p>EPIC-AT seeks to equip trainees and ECRs with the skills to translate their work into real-world impact.</p>

                        <p>While the success ultimately depends on the rate of uptake and meaningful application of knowledge or products by end users, non-traditional academic knowledge mobilization, commercialization and effective implementation of solutions are a platform goal.</p>  

                        <p>Not every Fellow is expected to be directly responsible for a commercial outcome or uptake of knowledge, but all projects should be actively contributing to these overall goals.</p>

                        <p>Please address your plan to ensure your work achieves the impact described in the previous section.</p>
                        {$item}
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>

        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$user_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
