<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Award 2022" headerName="{$user_name}: {$hqp_application_uni} / {$hqp_application_program}" reportType="RP_HQP_APPLICATION" pdfType="RPTP_HQP_APPLICATION" pdfFiles="HQPApplicationPDF" ajax="true" disabled="false" year="2022">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="HQP-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="HQP">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="STAFF+">
            <SectionPermission id="background" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="application" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="documents" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="background" tooltip="Background Information" name="Information" title="AGE-WELL Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards in Technology and Aging (2022)" type="ReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>About AGE-WELL</h3> 
                <p>AGE-WELL Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards in Technology and Aging provide partial funding to highly qualified master’s, doctoral and postdoctoral candidates and provide them with access to training and mentorship opportunities through the AGE-WELL Network of Centres of Excellence. AGE-WELL aims to provide a unique training environment that exposes trainees to multi-disciplinary research environments and to its industry and community partners. AGE-WELL is committed to attracting, developing, and retaining outstanding Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) in Canada.</p>

                <p>AGE-WELL is a pan-Canadian network of industry, non-profit organizations, government, care providers, caregivers, end-users, and academic partners working together to drive innovation and create technologies and services that benefit older adults and caregivers. Our vision is to harness and build upon the potential of emerging and advanced technologies in areas such as artificial intelligence (AI), e-health, information communication technologies (ICTs), and mobile technologies to stimulate technological, social, and policy innovation.</p>

                <h3>Eligibility</h3>
                <p>In order to be considered for AGE-WELL Awards, funding applicants must:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Receive at least some financial support from additional sources: home department, supervisor research grants, and/or through government and agency scholarships or awards.</li>
                    <li>Participate full‐time in their respective program at a Canadian post-secondary institution.</li>
                    <li>Be engaged in academic study/research aligned with the mission and vision of AGE-WELL.</li>
                    <li>Applicants for doctoral awards are restricted to those entering the first, second, or third year of their program with the exception of the AGE-WELL-NBHRF Awards and the AGE-WELL-UW Faculty of Health Awards.</li>
                </ol>

                <p>Applicants who will receive AGE-WELL project funds concurrently with this award period are ineligible to apply to this competition.  For example, a trainee who will be funded through AGE-WELL Core Research Projects, Platform Projects, Cross-Cutting themes, or the Strategic Investment, Collaborative Impact, Catalyst or AIR programs would be ineligible.</p>

                <h3>The Awards</h3>
                <p>Awards are intended to enhance existing funding support awarded to promising new scholars. Trainees must demonstrate that they receive funding from a source other than AGE-WELL.</p>

                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level awards at $10,000</li>
                    <li>PhD level awards at $15,000</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral level awards at $20,000</li>
                </ul>

                <p>If successful, trainee funding will be held and disbursed by the trainee’s supervisor in a new account that must be established at the supervisor’s home institution. Awards are not renewable.</p>

                <h3>Program Requirements</h3>

                <i>Training</i>
                <p>Funded trainees will be automatically enrolled in our EPIC training program (Early Professionals, Inspired Careers) and are expected to participate actively in AGE-WELL seminar series and professional development activities (e.g. workshops in commercialization or entrepreneurship). Trainees will be required to earn the Innovators of Tomorrow certificate by completing 4 online courses (estimated 25-30 hours total) within 1 year of receiving AGE-WELL funds.</p>

                <i>Reporting</i>
                <p>As per NCE rules, funds must flow from AGE-WELL to the trainee’s primary supervisor at their institution.  Academic institutions receiving AGE-WELL funds in trust are expected to:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Set up a new account for AGE-WELL funds disbursed during the current AGE-WELL funding cycle.</li>
                    <li>Report on expenditures of AGE-WELL funds by submitting a Form 300 to the Network Management Office no later than April 30 of each year for the duration of this funding award.</li>
                </ol>

                <i>Acknowledging AGE-WELL</i>
                <p>AGE-WELL funded trainees will acknowledge the AGE-WELL Award program in their presentations, publications, and other knowledge translation activities related to research conducted during their funding period.  Funded trainees are required to use the AGE-WELL logo on their posters and other materials related to research conducted during their funding period.</p>

                <h3>Admission Criteria</h3>
                <p>All applications will be reviewed by a team of field experts using the following criteria:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Scholarly Merit & Quality of Proposed Research (40%)</li>
                    <li>Fit with AGE-WELL Goals and Priorities (40%)</li>
                    <li>Quality of training environment (20%)</li>
                </ol>

                <h3>Required Documents</h3>
                <p>Award applicants must submit the following:</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>Online Application Form;</li>
                    <li>Two Confidential Letters of Support (one must be from your proposed supervisor)</li>
                    <li>Formal evidence of enrolment in a Master’s or Doctoral program or Post‐Doctoral position;</li>
                    <li>Formal evidence of awarded funding for 2022-2023;</li>
                    <li>Curriculum Vitae.</li>
                </ol>

                <h3>Important Dates</h3> 
                Applications Open: 29 April, 2022<br />
                Completed Applications Due: 31 May, 2022<br />
                Results Available: 5 August, 2022<br />
                Funding Commences: 1 September 2022<br />
                Award term: 1 September 2022 - 31 August 2022<br />

                <h3>1. Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship</h3> 
                <p><b>Michael F. Harcourt O.C., LL.B.</b> is the Founding Chair of the Board for the AGE-WELL Network of Centres of Excellence (NCE). Previously he served as the 30th Premier of British Columbia from 1991-96 and Mayor of Vancouver 1980-1986. He is a passionate believer in the power of communities to improve the human condition and has played a significant role in promoting quality of life for those in Canada and abroad. A devastating spinal cord injury in 2002 only strengthened his resolve to contribute to the transformation of communities, particularly in relation to social inclusion. Since 2011, he has demonstrated his commitment to capacity building in the public sector as the lead faculty of the United Way's Public Policy Institute. As Chair of AGE-WELL, Mr. Harcourt has championed the next generation of leaders in the field of technology and aging and believes passionately in their ability to create real-world impact. The <b>Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship</b> recognizes his long service and dedication to public policy as a means to effect social change, and his commitment to supporting emerging leaders across disciplines.</p>

                <p>AGE-WELL NCE is dedicated to the creation of technologies, services, policies, and practices that benefit older adults and caregivers. We are committed to engaging and nurturing outstanding emerging scientific, industry and community leaders from across disciplines. We aim to provide a unique training environment based on scientific excellence and real-world applicability that exposes trainees to multidisciplinary research environments within a truly collaborative setting in the field of technology and aging.</p>

                <p>The successful recipient of the <b>Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship</b> will be supported and mentored by AGE-WELL’s knowledge mobilization, policy and governmental relations team; at least four meetings over the course of the award term are expected.</p>

                <p>The recipient may be profiled at AGE-WELL’s Annual Conference and/or in the network’s Annual Report. The $20,000 fellowship will be awarded to one <b>doctoral student (any year) or postdoctoral fellow</b>. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards. Award term: 1 September 2022-31 August 2023.</p>

                <p><i>Note that applicants to the Michael F Harcourt Policy Fellowship do not need to have completed a policy-focused degree program or be employed in a policy-focused role. The fellowship is meant to encourage trainees from any discipline and training program to explore the policy dimensions of their work in the field of technology and aging.</i></p>

                <p><b>APPLICATION AND SUBMISSION INFORMATION</b></p>

                <p>Complete an application to the AGE-WELL Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards program as per established requirements. Applicants wishing to be considered for the Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship will be required to submit a maximum ½ page statement that outlines their interest in policy and the potential policy implications of their work.</p>

                <h3>2. AGE-WELL Indigenous Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL is pleased to once again offer the Indigenous Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards to provide salary support to self-identified Indigenous trainees researching in AgeTech-related fields.</p>

                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level awards at $15,000</li> 
                    <li>PhD level awards at $25,000 </li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral level awards at $30,000</li>
                </ul>

                <p>If successful, trainee funding will be held and disbursed by the trainee’s supervisor in a new account that must be established at the supervisor’s home institution. Awards are not renewable. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <p>The recipient may be profiled at AGE-WELL’s Annual Conference and/or in the network’s Annual Report. Award term: 1 September 2022-31 August 2023.</p>


                <p><b>APPLICATION AND SUBMISSION INFORMATION</b></p>

                <p>Complete an application to the AGE-WELL Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards program as per established requirements. Applicants wishing to be considered for the Indigenous Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards are asked to indicate their interest and eligibility on the application form.</p>

                <h3>3. AGE-WELL Co-funded Awards</h3>

                <p>AGE-WELL has partnered with a number of community, industry, and post-secondary groups to further expand our collective impact and to build capacity among Canada’s young researchers. Applicants are asked to review eligibility and program information for each of the co-funded awards below and to indicate their interest in having their application also considered for a specific co-funded award. Unless otherwise indicated, eligibility, admission criteria, and required documents for AGE-WELL Co-funded Awards align with that of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <h3>AGE-WELL-MIRA Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL and the <a href="http://mira.mcmaster.ca/" target="_blank">McMaster Institute for Research on Aging</a> aim to support a greater number of salary awards to outstanding graduate students enrolled at McMaster University who wish to commence, pursue or sustain their research training in technology and aging.</p>
 
                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level award at $15,000</li>
                    <li>PhD level award at $20,000 (eligible applicants will be entering years 1-3)</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral award at $50,000</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>Funding for this award runs from September 1, 2022 – August 31, 2023 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and MIRA will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <h3>AGE-WELL-NBHRF Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL NCE and the <a href="https://www.nbhrf.com/" target="_blank">New Brunswick Health Research Foundation</a> (NBHRF) are pleased to open the call for the 2022 AGE-WELL-NBHRF Funding Program.  Applicants must be based at a New Brunswick institution.</p>

                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level award at $17,500</li>
                    <li>PhD level award at $25,000</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral level award (PhD) at $40,000</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral level award (MD or Pharm. D) at $56,500</li>
                </ul>

                <p>Funding will commence on 1 September 2022 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and NBHRF will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <h3>AGE-WELL-SHRF Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL and the <a href="https://www.shrf.ca/" target="_blank">Saskatchewan Health Research Foundation</a> are pleased to open the call for the 2022 AGE-WELL-SHRF Postdoctoral Fellowship. The successful recipient must be based at a Saskatchewan institution.</p>

                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Postdoctoral award at $45,000</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Funding for this award runs from September 1, 2022 – August 31, 2023 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and SHRF will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <h3>AGE-WELL-UBC Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL and the <a href="https://ihlcdp.ok.ubc.ca/" target="_blank">Institute for Healthy Living and Chronic Disease Prevention</a>, University of British Columbia-Okanagan aim to support a greater number of salary awards to outstanding graduate students enrolled at UBC-O who wish to commence, pursue or sustain their research training in technology and aging.</p>
 
                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level award at $10,000</li>
                    <li>PhD level award at $20,000 (eligible applicants will be entering years 1-3)</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral award at $25,000</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>Funding for this award runs from September 1, 2022 – August 31, 2023 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and UBC will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

                <h3>AGE-WELL-UofT FASE Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL and the <a href="https://www.engineering.utoronto.ca/" target="_blank">Faculty of Applied Science and Engineering</a>, University of Toronto aim to support a greater number of salary awards to outstanding graduate students enrolled in FASE who wish to commence, pursue or sustain their research training in technology and aging.</p>
 
                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level award at $10,000</li>
                    <li>PhD level award at $15,000 (eligible applicants will be entering years 1-3)</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral award at $20,000</li>
                </ul>

                <p>Funding for this award runs from September 1, 2022 – August 31, 2023 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and UofT FASE will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p> 

                <h3>AGE-WELL-UW Faculty of Health Awards</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL and the <a href="https://uwaterloo.ca/health/" target="_blank">Faculty of Health</a>, University of Waterloo aim to support a greater number of salary awards to outstanding graduate students enrolled in the Faculty of Health who wish to commence, pursue or sustain their research training in technology and aging.</p>

                <p>We expect to offer the following awards in this 2022 call:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Master’s level award at $10,000</li>
                    <li>PhD level award at $20,000</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral award at $25,000</li>
                </ul>

                <p>Funding for this award runs from September 1, 2022 – August 31, 2023 and is non-renewable. AGE-WELL and UW Faculty of Health will individually administer their portion of the award funds. This award is subject to the training and reporting requirements of the AGE-WELL Awards.</p>

        ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="application" tooltip="Core Research Program Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP) Application" name="Application" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_FORM" type="EditableReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table style='width: 100%;'>
                    <tr>
                        <td colspan='2'><h3>BACKGROUND INFORMATION</h3></td>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Applicant Name:</b></td><td>{$user_name}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="status" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_STAT" width="180px" placeholder="e.g. PhD Year 1, Occupational therapy">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Academic Status and Department:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="supervisor" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUP" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Supervisor Name:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="uni" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UNI" width="180px" placeholder="Please list the institution where funds will be held">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Institution/University:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="level" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_LVL" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($10,000)|PhD ($15,000)|Postdoctoral ($20,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;width:210px;'><b>AGE-WELL Awards - <br />Funding Category</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="MICHAEL" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_MICHAEL" orientation="vertical" options="PhD ($20,000)|Postdoctoral ($20,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship</b><br /><i>Please indicate your eligibility and desire to be considered for these awards</i></td><td id='micheal' style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="MICHAEL_DESC" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_MICHAEL_DESC" rich="true" limit="750" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr id='michael_desc'>
                    <td></td>
                    <td align='left' valign='top'>
                        <div style='display:none;'>
                            The purpose of this fellowship is to encourage candidates from any disciplinary background to explore the policy dimensions of their work in the field of technology and aging. To be considered for the Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship, please submit a policy engagement plan related to the work described in your award application (750 words maximum). The policy engagement plan must include at a minimum: the policy relevant question(s) that you think your work could answer, the potential impact of your work on stakeholders, and key audiences who would benefit from hearing about your work.{$item}
                        </div>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="INDIGENOUS" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_INDIGENOUS" orientation="vertical" options="Master’s ($15,000)|PhD ($25,000)|Postdoctoral ($30,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Indigenous Graduate Student and Postdoctoral Awards</b><br /><i>Please indicate your eligibility and desire to be considered for these awards and confirm that you self-identify as an Indigenous trainee.</i></td><td id='indigenous' style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="INDIGENOUS_DESC" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_INDIGENOUS_DESC" rich="true" limit="750" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr id='indigenous_desc'>
                    <td></td>
                    <td align='left' valign='top'>
                        <div style='display:none;'>
                            {$item}
                        </div>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <tr>
                    <td colspan='2' style='padding-top:15px;'><b>AGE-WELL Co-Funded Awards: Please indicate your eligibility and interest in being considered for the awards below by checking the appropriate boxes.</b></td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        
        <ReportItem id="MIRA" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_MIRA" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($15,000)|PhD ($20,000)|Postdoctoral ($50,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-MIRA Awards</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="NBHRF" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_NBHRF" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($17,500)|PhD ($25,000)|Postdoctoral, PhD ($40,000)|Postdoctoral, MD or Pharm. D ($56,500)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-NBHRF Awards</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="SHRF" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SHRF" orientation="vertical" options="Postdoctoral ($45,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-SHRF</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="UBC" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UBC" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($10,000)|PhD ($20,000)|Postdoctoral ($25,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-UBC Award</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="UOFT" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UOFT" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($10,000)|PhD ($15,000)|Postdoctoral ($20,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-UofT FASE Award</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="UW" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UW" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($10,000)|PhD ($20,000)|Postdoctoral ($25,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-UW Faculty of Health</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="UOFC" type="CheckboxReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_UOFC" orientation="vertical" options="Master's ($15,000)|PhD ($20,000)|Postdoctoral ($50,000)" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>AGE-WELL-UCalgary Awards</b></td><td style='padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px;'>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        
        <ReportItem id="project" type="TextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_PROJ" width="180px">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right'><b>Project Title:</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="keywords" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_KEYWORDS" multiple="true" max="6" sizes="180">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr><td align='right' valign='top' style='padding-top:5px;'><b>Keywords (maximum 6):</b></td><td>{$item}</td></tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
                <script type='text/javascript'>
                    $('#micheal input').change(function(){
                        var value = $('#micheal input').is(":checked");
                        if(value){
                            $('#michael_desc td > div').slideDown();
                        }
                        else{
                            $('#michael_desc td > div').slideUp();
                        }
                    });
                    $('#micheal input').change();
                    $('#indigenous input').change(function(){
                        var value = $('#indigenous input').is(":checked");
                        if(value){
                            $('#indigenous_desc td > div').slideDown();
                        }
                        else{
                            $('#indigenous_desc td > div').slideUp();
                        }
                    });
                    $('#indigenous input').change();
                </script>
                <p>N.B.: If successful, funding will be disbursed to the named primary supervisor at the institution listed.</p>
                <h3>SCHOLARLY MERIT AND QUALITY OF PROPOSED RESEARCH</h3>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="research" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_RESEARCH" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Statement of research focus (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>AGE-WELL is inviting proposals in the broad area of technology and aging. The research project may be linked to one of AGE-WELL's eight <a href='https://agewell-nce.ca/challenge-areas' target='_blank'>Challenge Areas</a>, but does not need to limited to these. Research should address at least one of our key research questions:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>What are the needs of older adults and caregivers?</li>
                            <li>What technology-based systems and services should be used to meet those needs?</li>
                            <li>How can we foster innovation in the technology and aging sector? </li>
                        </ol>
                        <p>In this section, applicants should describe:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>How does your research connect to research foci of the AGE-WELL NCE?</li>
                            <li>Why is your project important?</li>
                            <li>Who is your target user population(s)?</li>
                            <li>What is the expected impact of your research?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="objectives" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_OBJ" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Research objectives/aims (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research: </p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Overall aim of the research</li>
                            <li>Specific objectives - these should include both the research objectives AND the ”non-academic” objectives, such as knowledge transfer etc. (these objectives should be related to the specific project activities that will be mapped out in “tasks/activities” in the next section)</li>
                            <li>Specific research question(s) (if appropriate)</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_GOALS" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>How will you achieve your project goals? (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section describe the following aspects of your research: </p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Brief overview of the approach (design/methods) you will use to meet your project objectives</li>
                            <li>Describe the type of research being undertaken e.g. technology development, review, feasibility study, pilot study, requirements analysis, prototype development, intervention study, evaluation study, etc.</li>
                            <li>Describe the tasks and activities planned (provide detail on specific tasks to be carried out to meet the project objectives you identified above). “Activities” may include research activities, KT, innovation, commercialization, team-building and training, etc.</li>
                            <li>Provide specific timing of the various tasks, activities and milestones, where milestones are critical points in the project (e.g. completion of a task)</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="biography" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_BIO" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>FIT WITH AGE-WELL GOALS AND PRIORITIES</h3>
                <b>Biography and career goals (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>In this section briefly describe:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Your current goals</li>
                            <li>Where you see yourself in 5-10 years</li>
                            <li>How you see AGE-WELL helping you to achieve your goals</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="align" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_ALIGN" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Alignment to the mission and goals of AGE-WELL (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Successful applications will need to be aligned with the key strategic goals of AGE-WELL. Applicants are strongly encouraged to familiarize themselves with the <a href='https://agewell-nce.ca/about-age-well' target='_blank'>network</a>. As well as scientific excellence, applicants will need to demonstrate that their research has potential for real world impact. In this section, describe how  your research fits with AGE-WELL’s vision and strategic goals.</p>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="commercialization" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_COMM" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Potential for commercialization and/or knowledge mobilization (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>AGE-WELL research is designed to produce social and economic impact. Success in either ultimately depends on the rate of uptake and meaningful application of knowledge or products by end users. Commercialization and knowledge mobilization are vital activities of AGE-WELL.</p>
                        <p>Not every project is expected to be directly responsible for a commercial outcome or uptake of knowledge, but all projects should be actively contributing to these overall goals.  In this section address the following:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Are there new products/systems and services that may result from this research?</li>
                            <li>How could your research support the commercialization of other products and services (e.g. user-based research)?</li>
                            <li>What audiences/user groups might benefit from the knowledge produced by your research?</li>
                            <li>How will these user groups be engaged in your research?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="innovation" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_INN" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Potential for innovation (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Innovation is a critical outcome of the AGE-WELL Network.  Innovation may come in various forms, including social innovation, scientific innovation, technological innovation, and policy-based innovation.  In this section, as applicable, address the following:</p>
                        <p><i>Social innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are practical benefits of your research to the wider community?</li>
                            <li>How will these benefits be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Technological innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are the novel aspects and contributions of your research from a technical point of view?</li>
                            <li>How will these be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Policy and practice innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>How might policies, services and care be transformed by your research?</li>
                            <li>How will these changes be achieved?</li>
                        </ol>
                        <p><i>Scientific innovation</i></p>
                        <ol type="i">
                            <li>What are the key scientific outputs from this research?</li>
                            <li>How will these be communicated to the scientific and/or knowledge-using communities?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="industry" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_IND" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>QUALITY OF TRAINING ENVIRONMENT</h3>
                <b>Industry and/or community partners (if applicable) (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>The AGE-WELL Network unites leading Canadian private and public companies, government bodies, care providers, end-users and academic partners to develop cohesive critical mass in the technology and aging sector. All AGE-WELL researchers and trainees have access to the AGE-WELL partner network. We expect that the majority of AGE-WELL research projects will be carried out in conjunction with a community or industrial partner, for example: a technology company, a service provider, or a government department or agency.</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Specify how your project is aligned with partner goals, their role and contribution in the project and how you will work directly with this partner(s).</li>
                            <li>If your research does not currently involve working with a partner organization, identify the type of partner that would be appropriate for your research and how your research might benefit from partner engagement (e.g. Co-.development of technology, knowledge mobilization, experiential learning). Where possible, AGE-WELL will attempt to link trainee projects with appropriate AGE-WELL partners.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="boundary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_BOUNDARY" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>In what ways will your project go beyond conventional disciplinary boundaries? (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Transdisciplinary working - that is working across and with other disciplines than your own – is an important aspect of AGE-WELL. In this section please address the following:</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Describe networking that may occur across disciplines and sites within AGE-WELL</li>
                            <li>How does the project link with other projects/activities in the AGE-WELL Network?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="training" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_TRAIN" height="200px" limit="2200" recommended="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Training context (1/2 page)</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Describe resources available through your proposed supervisor and department/institute.</p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Is this project part of a bigger program of research? </li>
                            <li>How will these link to and support your specific project?</li>
                        </ol>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="funding" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_FUND" height="200px">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>Other funding obtained/applied for</b>
                    <div style="font-size:smaller;">
                        <p>Provide the total amount of matching funds and support already received or applied for (including stipends from supervisor), and source of funding. See "Background Information"</p>
                    </div>
                {$item}<br /><br />
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="documents" type="ReportSection" tooltip="Required Documents" name="Documents" blobSection="HQP_APPLICATION_DOCS">
        <Static blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_SUPPORT2" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Two Confidential Letters of Support (one must be from your proposed supervisor)</h2>
                <p>Letters must be sent via email (<a href='mailto:training@agewell-nce.ca'>training@agewell-nce.ca</a>) directly by the referee using their department letterhead. Electronic signature or scanned signed documents are accepted. </p> 

<p>You need two confidential letters of support:</p>
<ul>
    <li>a letter from an individuals familiar with your research, academic background, and aptitude; and</li>
    <li>a letter from your proposed academic supervisor.</li>
</ul>{$item}
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="admission" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_ADMISSION" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Formal evidence of admission to a Master's or Doctoral program or Postdoctoral position</h2>
                <p>Master’s and Doctoral students can submit their acceptance letters as formal evidence of admission to a graduate program. Applicants can also submit their transcripts as evidence of registration to a graduate program.</p>

                <p>Postdoctoral fellows can submit a copy of their engagement letters as formal evidence of admission to a post‐doctoral position. In the event that engagement letters are not available, a letter from the applicant’s supervisor is sufficient. Please ensure to include the Award period and funding amount in the letter.</p>
                <b>The uploaded file must be a PDF Document</b>.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="evidence" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_EVIDENCE" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Formal evidence of application or awarded funding for 2022-2023</h2>
                <p>AGE-WELL Awards are intended to enhance existing funding support to promising new scholars. Applicants must receive financial support from additional sources; AGE-WELL project funds are an ineligible source of matching funds for this competition.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Award Offer Letter</li>
                    <li>Email confirmation on submitted application for an award</li>
                    <li>Email confirmation from your supervisor of committed funds</li>
                    <li>Letter from funding agency</li>
                    <li>Postdoctoral Award/Engagement Letters</li>
                    <li>Letter from Postdoctoral supervisor which outlines the Award period & funding amount</li>
                </ul>
                <b>The uploaded file must be a PDF Document</b>.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="cv" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_CV" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Curriculum Vitae</h2>
                <p>Please prepare the document and submit as a PDF.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="michael" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="HQP_APPLICATION_MICHAEL" mimeType="application/pdf" fileSize="2" optional="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Michael F. Harcourt Policy Fellowship - Personal Statement (maximum 1/2 page, for Harcourt applicants only)</h2>
                <p>Please outline your interest in policy and the potential policy implications of your work.<br />
                Please prepare the document and submit as a PDF.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="{$user_email}" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
