<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AGE-WELL National Innovation Hub (AWNIH) Report" pdfFiles="IHReportPDF" extends="WPReport">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="NI+">
            <SectionPermission id="summary" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="nce" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="additional" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Project />
        <Person id="1567" />
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="summary">
        <ReportItem id="summary" limit="4000">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Report Description</h3>
                <p>This report is designed to capture activity and impact over the past year to inform AGE-WELL’s federal reporting requirements. Importantly, we will also use the content to help position Innovation Hubs within new AGE-WELL initiatives such as envisAGE and Strategic Science Fund programs and in new funding applications (e.g. forward-looking plans in 2.c are important for the latter).</p>
                
                <p>It is understood and expected that Innovation Hubs receive funding from a variety of sources and engage in activities in support of organizational goals that may diverge, in some cases, from those of AGE-WELL. <b>Please answer the questions to the best of your ability.</b></p>
                
                <h3>Executive Summary (4000 characters / 1 pg)</h3>
                <p>Describe the top three achievements, contributions and/or success stories from your Innovation Hub as they relate to the realization of your Hub’s overarching goals and to AGE-WELL’s <a href="http://agewell-nce.ca/about-us" target="_blank">mission and vision</a></p>
                
                Highlight key achievements or progress in the following areas:
                <ul>
                    <li>Research Excellence</li>
                    <li>Development of highly Qualified HQP</li>
                    <li>Networking and Partnerships</li>
                    <li>Knowledge Mobilization and Technology Transfer</li>
                </ul>
                
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="nce" delete="true" />
    <ReportSection id="additional" name="Additional Information" title="2. Additional Information">
        <ReportItem id="outcomes">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>a) Other Outcomes</h3>
                <p>While it is important that we demonstrate achievement across key network areas in the previous section, we realize that there are other ways to define success and achievement relevant to AGE-WELL’s mission and vision. In this section, please describe any success or achievements that you would like to highlight that have not been covered in the sections above.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="benefits">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>b) Benefits of Network Involvement</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL strives to provide its members with benefits and opportunities that are only realizable through a multisectoral networked approach. Please describe any benefits accrued by your team(s) resulting from your specific involvement in AGE-WELL (e.g. team cohesion, access to new partners, working with other Innovation Hubs etc.)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="priorities" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="PRIORITIES">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>c) Innovation Hub Objectives and Priorities</h3>
                <p>Please provide an update on Hub priorities and projects planned for 2024-25 and beyond. Note that AGE-WELL expects to have opportunities to match industry / partner funding in the upcoming year for mature projects positioned for impact within 18 months. </p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="initiatives" delete="true" />
    <ReportSection id="review">
        
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit">
        
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
