<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Project Plan Update 2020-21" reportType="RP_PROJ_PLAN_UPDATE" pdfType="RPTP_PROJ_PLAN_UPDATE" pdfFiles="ProjectPlanUpdatePDF" personId="0" ajax="true" year="2020" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="SD+">

        </Role>
        <Role role="PL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="PS">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPC">

        </Role>
        <Project />
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="overview" type="ReportSection" tooltip="Overview" name="Overview" title="Project Plan Update 2020-21">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>In May 2020 the AGE-WELL Network Management Office surveyed Project Leads to better understand the current and anticipated impact of COVID-19 on funded projects. Teams were told at that time that they will have an opportunity to submit a revised project plan and budget at a later date.</p>
                
                <p>In light of research disruptions and delays due to COVID-19, AGE-WELL will not undertake an Annual Project Progress Evaluation (APPE) of its multi-year projects this fall as planned. Instead, projects funded through the AGE-WELL Core Research Program and Platform Project Program will complete the project update process outlined in this document consisting of updates to project status, project plans and project outputs by <u><b>January 15</b></u>, 2021 via the Forum research portal.</p>
                
                <p>The Forum portal is the primary mechanism for preparing and submitting progress reports and funding requests, and serves as a central repository for information about people, projects, and activities within AGE-WELL. The project update process requires Project Leads to ensure that their Forum project profiles are up to date and that all project HQP have been added to the portal. How-to guides for Forum reporting and adding HQP are included in this document. A separate Budget Update process will proceed as usual in February 2021. Project Leads will prepare and submit a revised project budget at that time including an estimate of unspent funds at year-end.</p>
                
                <p>The intent of the revised 2020-21 process is to ensure that RMC is able to assess how newly funded AGE-WELL projects and programs are faring in light of COVID-19 and to understand how projects have changed or will change their approaches in this new environment.  Project teams will have the opportunity to meet with network Scientific Directors and Network Management Office team members following the project update process to ensure the appropriate network supports are available to their teams.</p>
                
                <p>Projects will <u>not</u> be evaluated against specific performance metrics as part of the update process; therefore the second instalments of funding that are usually tied to mid-term reviews will be released in November as planned prior to receipt of updated project plans. Any adjustments required to term lengths, budgets, and project plans will be in place for April 1, 2021.</p>
                
                <h3>Important Dates:</h3>
                <table class="wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <td><b>January 15, 2021</b></td>
                        <td>Completion of Project Status, Plan Update and Project Output Reporting in Forum</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td><b>February 19, 2021</b></td>
                        <td>Completion of Budget Update module in Forum<br /><i>Instructions will circulate in January. This is the standard Forum budget module for AGE-WELL funded projects.</i></td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td><b>April 1, 2021</b></td>
                        <td>Release of 2021-22 Funding Letters</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="status" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="STATUS" tooltip="A. Project Status" name="Project Status" title="A. Project Status">
        <ReportItem id="active" type="Checkbox" blobItem="ACTIVE" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" options="Active">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>1. What is the current status of the AGE-WELL funded project?</h3>
                <ol type="i">
                    <li>{$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="active_1" type="Radio" blobItem="ACTIVE_1" options="Yes|No" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                        <ul>
                            <li>Was project start delayed by COVID-19? {$item}</li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="active_2" type="Calendar" blobItem="ACTIVE_2">
            <![CDATA[
                            <li>If Yes, what was the project restart date? {$item}</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="inactive" type="Checkbox" blobItem="INACTIVE" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" options="Inactive">
            <![CDATA[
                    <li>{$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="inactive_1" type="Radio" blobItem="INACTIVE_1" options="Yes|No" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                        <ul>
                            <li>If inactive, was it delayed by COVID-19? {$item}</li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="inactive_2" type="Calendar" blobItem="INACTIVE_2">
            <![CDATA[
                            <li>Anticipated start date: {$item}</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="information" type="Textarea" blobItem="INFORMATION" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                    <li>
                        Additional information to clarify the status of your project (optional):
                        {$item}
                    </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="impact" type="Textarea" blobItem="IMPACT" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
               <h3>2. Please describe how you think the COVID-19 situation will impact your project in the longer-term.</h3>
               {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="pivots" type="Textarea" blobItem="PIVOTS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
               <h3>3. Please summarize any solutions or pivots that have been or will be implemented (e.g. switching to online or virtual stakeholder meetings, alternative recruitment methods, etc.). You will be asked to detail specific changes to your project plan in the next section.</h3>
               {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="update" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="UPDATE" tooltip="B. Project Plan Update" name="Project Plan Update" title="B. Project Plan Update">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The majority of AGE-WELL funded projects reported in May that their project plans would require adjustment in light of COVID-19. In this section, teams are asked to describe in detail those specific challenges, changes or adjustments. Materials from your last Project Plan Update (Jan 2020) are accessible in this section for reference.  If helpful for project planning, Project Leads have the option to request a one-year no-cost extension to their current three-year award at this time, with justification. Note that a no-cost extension may be requested in the final year of the project as per usual process.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="timeline" type="Textarea" blobItem="TIMELINE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>1. Describe the specific challenges, changes or adjustments to project plans in the context of COVID-19 related to:</h3>
                <ol type="a">
                <li>Project timeline:<br />
                    {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="extension" type="Radio" blobItem="EXTENSION" options="Yes|No" orientation="horizontal">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p>Project Leads have the option to request a no-cost extension now to the current award term (Apr 1, 2020- Mar 31, 2023) to assist with project planning. This would change your award term end to Mar 31, 2024. If choose <u>not</u> to extend your award term now, you will be able to choose to extend in 2023 as per usual process.</p>
                    <b>Would you like to request an extension now?</b>
                    {$item}
                    <br />
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="Textarea" blobItem="GOALS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Research goals and objectives, including whether COVID-19 considerations or research questions that have been incorporated into your project:
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="methods" type="Textarea" blobItem="METHODS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Research methods (e.g. participant recruitment and data collection, community outreach activities, etc.)
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partnerships" type="Textarea" blobItem="PARTNERSHIPS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Networking and partnerships (e.g. changes in partner organization’s ability to contribute cash or in-kind contributions to your project, including access to participants, need to identify new partners, etc.)
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ktee" type="Textarea" blobItem="KTEE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Knowledge mobilization and commercialization:
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="Textarea" blobItem="HQP" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    Recruitment and/or training of HQP:
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="platform_pdf" type="PDFReportItem" buttonName="Platform Report" project="true" reportType="PlatformReport" year="2019">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Previous Project Report</h3>
                <small>If a report was previously filled out, it will be listed below</small><br />
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="catalyst_pdf" type="PDFReportItem" buttonName="Catalyst Report" project="true" reportType="CatalystReport" year="2019">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Additional Project Materials</h3>
                <p>If you have additional documents to submit at this time (e.g. new letters of support, revised project summary or project plan etc.) you may attach them here.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <For from="1" to="20">
            <ReportItem id="file{$index}" type="Upload" blobItem="FILES{$index}" blobType="BLOB_RAW" fileSize="5">
                <![CDATA[
                    <div class='files' id='file{$index}' style='display:none;'>
                        {$item}
                    </div>
                    <script type='text/javascript'>
                        if('{getBlobMD5()}' != '' || '{$index}' == 1){
                            $('#file{$index}').show();
                        }
                    </script>
                ]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </For>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <button id='addFile' type='button'>Add another file</button>
                <script type='text/javascript'>
                    $('#addFile').click(function(){
                        $('.files:not(:visible)').first().show();
                        $('iframe', $('.files:visible').last())[0].src = $('iframe', $('.files:visible').last())[0].src;
                        if($('.files:not(:visible)').length == 0){
                            $('#addFile').prop('disabled', true);
                        }
                    });
                </script>
                <br /><br />
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="reporting" type="ReportSection" tooltip="C. Project Reporting 2020-21" name="Project Reporting" title="C. Project Reporting 2020-21">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>AGE-WELL’s performance management framework typically combines a balanced scorecard approach with output reporting via the Forum research portal. For fiscal year 2020-21, the network will defer use of the balanced scorecard as part of a mid-year evaluation process but will retain project output reporting via Forum as part of its annual reporting process. Project Leads as are asked to report project outputs, achievements and partner contributions via Forum by <b>January 15, 2021</b>.</p>
                
                <p>As mentioned above, projects will not be evaluated against specific performance metrics; project output reporting through Forum is also used by the Network Management Office to support network annual reporting and to understand network performance. Project teams will be asked to update Forum again at the end of fiscal year.</p>
                
                <p>Forum reporting updates can be made to Forum at any time and it is expected that Project Leads keep project information up to date in Forum throughout the life of the project. Information about AGE-WELL reporting is maintained on the <a href="http://members.agewell-nce.ca/annual-reporting">network intranet</a>: A “How-To” reporting guide has been prepared and can be found here: <a href="http://members.agewell-nce.ca/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Annual-Reporting-on-Forum-How-To-Guide_Jan-2019.pdf">Annual Reporting on Forum – How-To Guide</a>. (<a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/APPENDIX A - Project Plan Update 2020-21.pdf">See also Appendix A</a>)</p>
                
                Key links are included below:
                <ul>
                    <li>All project outputs and outcomes that have been produced in this last fiscal year (publications, presentations, patents etc.), partially funded by AGE-WELL and/or related to their AGE-WELL research agenda, must be entered in the Forum: <a href="https://forum.agewell-nce.ca/index.php/Special:ManageProducts">https://forum.agewellnce.ca/index.php/Special:ManageProducts</a></li>
                    <li>All financial contributions (cash and in-kind)  from partners and other sources enhancing AGE-WELL funded activities must be entered in the system: <a href="https://forum.agewell-nce.ca/index.php/Special:Contributions">https://forum.agewell-nce.ca/index.php/Special:Contributions</a></li>
                    <li>Forum profiles must be complete for all Network Investigators and HQP, including university affiliations, bio tab in full, associated projects, supervisory relations. It is the supervisor’s responsibility to ensure project HQP are set up in Forum. Project Leads may designate a team member to create Forum accounts for HQP using the Project Support role in Forum. (<a href="{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/APPENDIX B - Project Plan Update 2020-21.pdf">See also Appendix B</a>)</li>
                    <li>EPIC tabs must be up-to-date for HQP</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="jennifer@agewell-nce.ca,info@agewell-nce.ca" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
