<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="2021-22 Annual Project Progress Evaluation Report" reportType="RP_PROJ_PLAN_UPDATE" pdfType="RPTP_PROJ_PLAN_UPDATE" pdfFiles="ProjectPlanUpdatePDF" personId="0" ajax="true" year="2021" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="SD+">

        </Role>
        <Role role="PL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="PS">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPL">

        </Role>
        <Role role="WPC">

        </Role>
        <Project />
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="overview" type="ReportSection" tooltip="Overview" name="Overview" title="2021-22 Annual Project Progress Evaluation Report: {$project_name}">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The aim of this form is to allow AGE-WELL’s Research Management Committee (RMC) to assess project progress and performance against key impact objectives of the network. Given the disruption of COVID-19 to network research programs, this form also provides Project Leads with an opportunity to demonstrate project evolution following the January 2021 Project Update process.</p> 

                <h2>Completing the Report</h2>
                The report consists of four sections:
                <ol type="A">
                    <li><b>Project Status:</b> description of overall project status in light of disruptions of the past year.</li>
                    <li><b>Product Development / Product Readiness:</b> assignment of current and projected product readiness levels associated with “products” of the research (i.e. technologies, services, practices, policies). Additional information on determining product readiness below.</li>
                    <li><b>Impact Statement and Case Study:</b> projected impact of the research against timelines—that is, within and beyond the funding period, and a short case study of project achievement.</li>
                    <li><b>Progress Update / Planning Scorecards:</b> project progress and planning across the following network program criteria: scientific excellence, development of HQP, knowledge mobilization and commercialization, and networking and partnerships. Additional information below.</li>
                </ol>

                <h2>Product Readiness Levels</h2>
                <p>AGE-WELL produces a broad range of products or solutions (e.g. technologies, services and policies). Progress towards achieving impact can be defined and measured across all projects in a consistent fashion. The Product Readiness Levels (PRL) is a method of estimating maturity and progress across 5 stages that overlay the Technology Readiness Levels (TRL). The five stage progression is based on the funding continuum of the innovation pipeline developed for CIHR’s eHealth innovations Partnership Program.</p>

                <p>AGE-WELL has adapted both scales to be inclusive of the types of technology-based solutions that are part of the network. Please refer to the <a href="http://members.agewell-nce.ca/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/AGE-WELL-PRL-Guidelines_final.docx">Product Readiness Levels Guideline</a> for definitions of the PRL levels, as well as example outputs at each level across product type.</p>

                <p>Projects are required to justify the current PRL stage of each product and projected PRL stage one year later. It is expected that projects will progress through these stages at an appropriate pace. However it should be noted that it is expected that some products may remain at a specific PRL longer than others.</p>

                <h2>Progress Report and Balanced Scorecard</h2>
                <p>Each project is required to provide project detail in the form of a Progress Report and Planning Scorecard in the following areas: Scientific Excellence, Networking and Partnerships, Knowledge Mobilization and Commercialization, and HQP Training. The Progress Report should capture activity to date; the planning scorecard should capture proposed activity for 2022-23. All projects are asked to complete the sections of the tables that are relevant to their project; for example, not all projects may be able to complete both the knowledge mobilization and commercialization sections of the tables.  The tables were developed based on the <i>Balanced Scorecard</i> approach and will be used by the RMC to review projects progress from year to year.</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="status" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="STATUS" tooltip="A. Project Status" name="Project Status" title="A. Project Status">
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="Textarea" blobItem="SUMMARY" rich="true" height="400px">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Provide a brief summary of the status of this project in light of disruptions over the past 18 months. Please include 1) adaptations to challenges outlined in your January 2021 Project Progress Update (e.g. changes to partnerships, access to participants, HQP retention etc.) and 2) ongoing challenges and plans to address them.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="prl" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="PRL" tooltip="B. Product Development / Product Readiness" name="Product Development" title="B. Product Development / Product Readiness">
        <ReportItem id="product_type" type="Checkbox" blobItem="PRODUCT_TYPE" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" options="Technology product - a device or system that someone will buy or adopt|Policy/practice product - information that will be used by stakeholder or end-user, including others in the network|Service product - a service or information product that will be used by another entity">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>AGE-WELL recognizes different types of products: Technologies, Services, Policies/Practices. Projects can be at different stages of product readiness, from concept to deployment and adoption.  Please refer to the guidelines in order to define which stage best characterises your project.</p>
                
                <h2>1. What kind of product(s) are you developing (check all that apply):</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="nProducts" blobItem="N_PRODUCTS" type="Integer" min="0" max="100" size="3">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2. Use the attached supporting documents (AGE-WELL PRL Guidelines) to determine the “Product Readiness Level” (PRL) your product(s) are currently at.</h2>
                <p><b>How many products has your project developed?</b></p> {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prl" type="MultiText" multiple="true" blobItem="PRL_LEVEL" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" indices="Product|Product Type|Stage|PRL Level|Future PRL" labels="Product|Product Type|Stage|PRL Level|&lt;div style='max-width:200px;display:inline-block;'>Which PRL level do you expect to be at one year from now?&lt;div class='small' style='float:left;white-space:wrap;'>Provide a brief justification and key steps you will be taking if you project a different (higher) PRL level from what was indicated above. (500 words max)&lt;/div>&lt;/div>" types="Text|Select(Technology,Policy/Practice,Service)|Select(INNOVATION RESEARCH,INCUBATOR,PROTOTYPE,EXPERIMENTAL IMPLEMENTATION,OUTCOMES)|Select(1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9)|Textarea" sizes="||||600" heights="||||200" orientation="vertical">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Use the attached supporting documents (<a style='color:inherit;text-decoration:underline;' href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/AGE-WELL PRL Guidelines.docx'>AGE-WELL PRL Guidelines</a>), determine the “Product Readiness Level” (PRL) your product(s) currently at:</h3>
                    <b>PRL Levels</b>
                    <ul>
                        <li><b>INNOVATION RESEARCH</b> (PRL 1) basic principles observed</li>
                        <li><b>INCUBATOR</b> (PRL 2-3) technology concept formulated; experimental proof of concept</li>
                        <li><b>PROTOTYPE</b> (PRL 4-5) technology validated in lab; technology validated in relevant environment (industrially relevant environment in the case of key enabling technologies)</li>
                        <li><b>EXPERIMENTAL IMPLEMENTATION</b> (PRL 6-7) technology demonstrated in relevant environment (industrially relevant environment in the case of key enabling technologies); system prototype demonstration in operational environment</li>
                        <li><b>OUTCOMES</b> (PRL 8-9) system complete and qualified; actual system proven in operational environment (competitive manufacturing in the case of key enabling technologies; or in space)</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>
                {$item}
                <script type='text/javascript'>
                    setInterval(function(){
                        $('#table_ProductDevelopment_prl tr.obj').each(function(i, el){
                            var selects = $('select', $(el));
                            var spans = $('span.recommended', $(el));
                            var type  = $(selects[0]);
                            var stage = $(selects[1]);
                            var level = $(selects[2]);
                            var val = stage.val();
                            var recommended = "1";
                            
                            if(spans.length > 0){
                                spans.remove();
                            }
                            
                            switch(val){
                                case "INNOVATION":
                                    recommended = "1";
                                    break;
                                case "INCUBATOR":
                                    recommended = "2-3"
                                    break;
                                case "PROTOTYPE":
                                    recommended = "4-5";
                                    break;
                                case "EXPERIMENTAL IMPLEMENTATION":
                                    recommended = "6-7"
                                    break;
                                case "OUTCOMES":
                                    recommended = "8-9";
                                    break;
                            }
                            
                            level.after("<span class='recommended' style='width:50px;display:inline-block;font-weight:bold;vertical-align:middle;line-height:25px;'>(" + recommended + ")</span>");
                        });
                    }, 100);
                </script>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="impact" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="IMPACT" tooltip="C. Impact Statement and Case Study" name="Impact Statement" title="C. Impact Statement and Case Study">
        <ReportItem id="value" type="Textarea" blobItem="VALUE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>1. Impact Statement</h2>
                <p>AGE-WELL is expected to deliver social and economic benefits to Canadians, including but not limited to improved health or quality of life; improved policy, practice and services; new products or enterprises; job creation; value-added training etc. To fulfill our mandate we invest in a variety of projects and programs ranging from multi-year research funding to policy engagement and startup support programs. Keeping the broader mandate of AGE-WELL in mind:</p>
                <h3>What is the expected value and impact of this research within the timeframe of the funding term?</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="longterm" type="Textarea" blobItem="LONGTERM" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What are the anticipated longer-term outcomes and impact for partners, older adults and/or caregivers?</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="case_study" type="Textarea" blobItem="case_studty" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2. Case Study</h2>
                <p>Please provide a short <b>case study</b> of outstanding work or achievement in any of the above evaluation areas (Scientific Excellence, Networking and Partnerships, Knowledge Mobilization and Commercialization, and HQP Training). Case studies provide an opportunity for a better understanding of the work being completed and its impact in the real world. These stories are a great opportunity to promote the amazing work being accomplished within AGE-WELL. The following should be provided for the case study (500 words max):</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>A clear explanation of the process or means through which the research led to, underpinned or made a contribution to the impact (for example, how it was disseminated, how it came to influence users or beneficiaries, or how it came to be exploited, taken up or applied).</li>
                    <li>Where the case study was part of a wider body of research that contributed to the impact (for example, where there has been research collaboration with other institutions or grants), the case study should specify the particular contribution of the case study and acknowledge other key research contributions.</li>
                    <li>Details of the beneficiaries – who or what community, constituency or organisation has benefitted or been affected.</li>
                    <li>Details of the nature of the impact – how they have benefitted or been affected.</li>
                    <li>Evidence or indicators of the extent of the impact described, as appropriate to the case being made.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="progress" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="PROGRESS" tooltip="D. Progress Report and Planning Scorecards" name="Progress / Plans" title="D. Progress Report and Planning Scorecards">
        <!-- Scientific Excellence - Progress Report -->
        <ReportItem id="progress" type="Textarea" blobItem="PROGRESS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>1. Scientific Excellence - Progress Report</h2>
                <p>The AGE-WELL Core Research Program (CRP) must address Canadian needs and problems and demonstrate world-class scientific achievements. AGE-WELL is committed to a transdisciplinary approach and the involvement of stakeholders in all aspects of the project. In this section we ask that you document completed objectives, deliverables and project activities related to scientific excellence of this program of research. Include highlights from the project team with respect to national/international leadership (e.g. international collaborations, leadership positions held of relevance to the project), advancing knowledge (e.g. scientific and other publications and presentations etc.) and the project’s stakeholder-driven approach, including detail about the involvement of older adults, caregivers, policy makers, or partners in the project. Please specify the roles of stakeholders in this project) (e.g. advisory committee members, affiliated researchers, co-authors etc.). In addition, project Leads should include any other updates and metrics relevant to their specific projects.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="progress_narrative" type="Textarea" blobItem="PROGRESS_NARRATIVE" rich="true" limit="250">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Scientific Excellence - Planning Scorecard</h3>
                <p>In this section we ask you to complete the planning table below to outline objectives, outputs and activities for the next year in the same categories as above. Room is provided for Project Leads to include project-specific activities and metrics beyond those required in the planning template.</p>
                
                <p><b>Narrative:</b> Please provide any additional details needed to support the information in the table below (250 words max).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table rules="all" frame="box" class="small wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left" width="5%">Category</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Objectives – Main objectives for the upcoming year</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Outputs – Deliverables required to meet project objectives</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Project Activities – Activities required to generate outputs</th>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="prog_1_1" blobItem="PROG_1_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>National & International leadership</b> (e.g. developing international collaborations, being invited to international meetings, workshops, etc)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_1_2" blobItem="PROG_1_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_1_3" blobItem="PROG_1_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_2_1" blobItem="PROG_2_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Advancing knowledge</b> (e.g. publishing in journals and other publications, presenting at conferences and other meetings)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_2_2" blobItem="PROG_2_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_2_3" blobItem="PROG_2_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_3_1" blobItem="PROG_3_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Stakeholder driven research</b> (e.g. partner/organization driven research or older adult & caregiver involvement)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_3_2" blobItem="PROG_3_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_3_3" blobItem="PROG_3_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_4_1" blobItem="PROG_4_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Other</b> (TBD by the Project Lead)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_4_2" blobItem="PROG_4_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="prog_4_3" blobItem="PROG_4_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        
        <!-- Networking and Partnerships – Progress Report -->
        <ReportItem id="networking" type="Textarea" blobItem="NETWORKING" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2. Networking and Partnerships – Progress Report</h2>
                <p>The project must demonstrate that it has brought together the key individuals and organizations needed to generate and implement multifaceted solutions to the complex challenges it is designed to address. It must be built on relationships with partners and the receptor community that will accelerate the activities, outcomes and impact of the project. In this section we ask that you document completed objectives, deliverables and project activities related to networking and partnerships of this program of research, including examples of effective collaboration with the private, public and not-for-profit sectors in technology, market development, and public policy development, as well as national and international partnerships that are integral to this project’s success. Please specify <b>national or international partners by sector</b> (e.g. Industry, community, federal, provincial. Activity noted here must also be updated in Forum via the <i>Manage Outputs and Manage Contributions</i> modules. In addition, project Leads should include any other updates and metrics relevant to their specific projects.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="networking_narrative" type="Textarea" blobItem="NETWORKING_NARRATIVE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Networking and Partnerships - Planning Scorecard</h3>
                <p>In this section we ask you to complete the planning table below to outline objectives, outputs and activities for the next year in the same categories as above. Room is provided for Project Leads to include project-specific activities and metrics beyond those required in the planning template.</p>
                <p><b>Narrative:</b> Please provide any additional details needed to support the information in the table below (250 words max).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table rules="all" frame="box" class="small wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left" width="5%">Category</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Objectives – Main objectives for the upcoming year</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Outputs – Deliverables required to meet project objectives</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Project Activities – Activities required to generate outputs</th>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="net_1_1" blobItem="NET_1_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>National/international partnerships</b> (e.g. partners involved at a national and international level across sectors)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="net_1_2" blobItem="NET_1_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="net_1_3" blobItem="NET_1_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="net_2_1" blobItem="NET_2_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Other</b> (TBD by the Project Lead)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="net_2_2" blobItem="NET_2_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="net_2_3" blobItem="NET_2_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        
        <!-- Knowledge Mobilization & Commercialization – Progress Report -->
        <ReportItem id="kmc" type="Textarea" blobItem="KMC" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3. Knowledge Mobilization & Commercialization – Progress Report</h2>
                <p>NCE Networks are expected to generate social and economic benefits by ensuring the rapid flow of knowledge, ideas and innovations from researchers to Canadian receptors. Projects are expected to demonstrate that the appropriate activities will be undertaken and the appropriate resources allocated to maximize those benefits through effective stakeholder engagement and communication. In this section we ask that you document completed objectives, deliverables and project activities related to <b>knowledge mobilization</b> and/or commercialization, including examples of knowledge dissemination (e.g. academic and non-academic knowledge dissemination activities; media interviews; policy briefs etc.), <b>product development or management of intellectual property (IP)</b> (e.g. patents, provisional patents, IP disclosures, startup company development etc.). Activity noted here must also be updated in Forum via the <i>Manage Outputs</i> module. In addition, project Leads should include any other updates and metrics relevant to their specific projects.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_narrative" type="Textarea" blobItem="KMC_NARRATIVE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Knowledge Mobilization and Commercialization - Planning Scorecard</h3>
                <p>In this section we ask you to complete the planning table below to outline objectives, outputs and activities for the next year in the same categories as above. Room is provided for Project Leads to include project-specific activities and metrics beyond those required in the planning template.</p>
                <p><b>Narrative:</b> Please provide any additional details needed to support the information in the table below (250 words max).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table rules="all" frame="box" class="small wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left" width="5%">Category</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Objectives – Main objectives for the upcoming year</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Outputs – Deliverables required to meet project objectives</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Project Activities – Activities required to generate outputs</th>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_1_1" blobItem="KMC_1_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Knowledge Dissemination</b> (e.g. academic and non-academic dissemination activities, communications)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_1_2" blobItem="KMC_1_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_1_3" blobItem="KMC_1_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_2_1" blobItem="KMC_2_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Product Development & IP Management</b> (e.g. patents, licensing agreements, copyrights, startup development etc.)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_2_2" blobItem="KMC_2_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_2_3" blobItem="KMC_2_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_3_1" blobItem="KMC_3_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Other</b> (TBD by the Project Lead)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_3_2" blobItem="KMC_3_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kmc_3_3" blobItem="KMC_3_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        
        <!-- Training of HQP – Progress Report -->
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="Textarea" blobItem="HQP" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>4. Training of HQP – Progress Report</h2>
                <p>AGE-WELL’s EPIC training program is designed to add value to the formal training initiatives already available through the academic community and should aim at helping HQP find employment in the Canadian economy, particularly in sectors related to technology and aging.  HQP should be directly involved in the range of activities in a multi-disciplinary team research project and should have opportunities to collaborate with project partners and network members. In this section we ask that you document completed objectives, deliverables and project activities related to the development of HQP for this program of research, including a summary of the project’s training portfolio (e.g. recruitment and retention metrics, HQP-led publications, internships completed etc.) and engagement of HQP in network training opportunities (e.g. enrolment in EPIC training program).Activity noted here must also be updated in Forum via the Manage Outputs and EPIC modules. In addition, project Leads should include any other updates and metrics relevant to their specific projects.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_narrative" type="Textarea" blobItem="HQP_NARRATIVE" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>HQP Training - Planning Scorecard</h3>
                <p>In this section we ask you to complete the planning table below to outline objectives, outputs and activities for the next year in the same categories as above. Room is provided for Project Leads to include project-specific activities and metrics beyond those required in the planning template.</p>
                <p><b>Narrative:</b> Please provide any additional details needed to support the information in the table below (250 words max).</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <table rules="all" frame="box" class="small wikitable">
                    <tr>
                        <th align="left" width="5%">Category</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Objectives – Main objectives for the upcoming year</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Outputs – Deliverables required to meet project objectives</th>
                        <th align="left" width="25%">Planned Project Activities – Activities required to generate outputs</th>
                    </tr>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_1_1" blobItem="HQP_1_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Development of HQP</b> (e.g. involvement of HQP in the project and Network; HQP-led publications, internships, enrolment in EPIC)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_1_2" blobItem="HQP_1_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_1_3" blobItem="HQP_1_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_2_1" blobItem="HQP_2_1" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <tr style='height:100%;'>
                <td><b>Other</b> (TBD by the Project Lead)</td>
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_2_2" blobItem="HQP_2_2" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp_2_3" blobItem="HQP_2_3" type="Textarea" height="100%">
            <![CDATA[
                <td style='height:100%;'>{$item}</td>
                </tr>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                </table>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="jennifer@agewell-nce.ca,info@agewell-nce.ca" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
