<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="AGE-WELL Strategic Investment Program Application" reportType="RP_SIP_10_2016" pdfType="RPTP_SIP_10_2016" allowIdProjects="true" pdfFiles="SIPApplication102016PDF" ajax="true">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="NI">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="NI-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="External-Candidate">
            <SectionPermission id="description" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="cover" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="narrative" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="appendix" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="description" tooltip="2016 AGE-WELL Strategic Investment Program (SIP) Program Description and Application Instructions" name="Program Description" type="ReportSection" title="2016 AGE-WELL Strategic Investment Program (SIP) Program Description and Application Instructions">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Program Description</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL’s Strategic Investment Program supports opportunities that require a rapid response in order to generate, promote or accelerate economic and social benefits aligned with AGE-WELL’s mission and vision. These funds will support post-discovery commercialization, business development and knowledge dissemination, mobilization, or translation activities.</p>

                <p>Successful projects should accelerate Canadian innovation and economic competitiveness, and improve the quality of life for older adults or caregivers.</p>

                <p>AGE-WELL will consider proposals for knowledge mobilization and/or commercialization, including:
                    <ul>
                        <li>knowledge mobilization (KM), translation (KT) or exchange activities, including but not limited to, the development or implementation of KM/KT products or tools</li>
                        <li>commercialization of technologies, products, and/or services, including but not limited to, business development, market readiness and prototype development activities</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                
                <h3>Maximum Investment</h3>
                <p>$25,000</p>
                
                <h3>Timeframe</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL will provide investment for up to 12 months per application.  These investments are non-renewable.The project goals must be achievable within a one-year timeframe.</p>

                <h3>Eligibility</h3>

                <p>The competition is open to Canadian-based investigators working in the field of technology and aging. Canadian universities and investigators who are not already members of the AGE-WELL network will be required to sign onto the Network Agreement prior to receiving funds.</p>

                <p>SIP funds cannot be used for activities funded through other AGE-WELL competitions (e.g. Core Research Program); however, new commercialization focused activities such as start-ups developed from prior AGE-WELL investments are eligible for SIP funding.</p>

                <p>Funded projects must be aligned with AGE-WELL’s overall mission and vision and at least one of AGE-WELL’s 8 Workpackages: <a href='http://agewell-nce.ca/research' target='_blank'>http://agewell-nce.ca/research</a>. Preference will be given to projects with the potential to achieve real-world impact within 12 months.</p>

                <h3>Partnerships</h3>
                <p>AGE-WELL is dedicated to identifying and developing collaborations with other organizations and stakeholders to leverage AGE-WELL funding through cash or in-kind contributions, and to create opportunities for commercialization, knowledge exchange or mobilization.</p>

                <p>Although cash and in-kind contributions from commercial or community partners are not strictly required for this funding program, projects will normally be expected to include partner organizations in dissemination or commercialization planning and should detail these in the application. For reporting purposes, all partnership activities should be quantified in Part II – Appendix of the application package and supported by a Letter of Support from the partnering organization included in Part III of this application.</p>

                <h3>Application Instructions</h3>
                The SIP application consists of three sections:<br />
                <b>PART 1 - Narrative Application</b> (5 page max, minimum 12 pt font excluding Cover Sheet)<br />
                <p>Complete sections directly in Forum using the spaces provided. Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>
                <b>PART 2 - Appendix</b> (Team Summary, Budget and Budget Justification, Partner Contributions)<br />
                <p>Complete Team Summary, HQP and Budget Justification directly in Forum using the sections and drop down menus provided.</p>
                <p>Budget Template (Excel) are available in Forum (links in each section).  Download, complete and upload filled documents.  Any partner contributions should be added to the Budget Template and supported by a letter signed by the partner.</p>
                <p>Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>
                <b>PART 3 - Investigator Bio</b> (2 page max, highlighting relevant experience) and Partner Letter of Support (if applicable)</p>
                <p>Complete bio directly in Forum using the textbox provided.  Provide a brief bio (2 page max) for the principle investigator.  No specific format/template is required.</p>
                <p>Upload any letters of support from partners described in Part 2. Submit as PDF(s).</p>
                <p>Use the Save button at the bottom of the page after each section entry or before moving between sections.</p>

                <h3>Submission Deadlines:</h3>
                <p>Proposals will be accepted quarterly. Deadlines for 2016 are:
                    <ul>
                        <li>January 15, 2016</li>
                        <li>April 15, 2016</li>
                        <li>July 15, 2016</li>
                        <li><b>October 21, 2016</b></li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>SIP aims to provide rapid and responsive funding for commercialization and knowledge mobilization activities.  We expect to communicate decisions within 4 weeks of the deadline.</p>

                <h3>Review Process</h3>
                <ol>
                    <li>Applications will be screened for completeness by Network Management Office staff. Additional information may be requested if the information provided is deemed to be insufficient or unclear.</li>
                    <li>The KTEE Advisory Group (Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation) to the AGE-WELL Research Management Committee will review all complete applications and determine their eligibility for support, the appropriate level of investment, and any associated terms and conditions that must be met prior to the commitment of AGE-WELL resources. </li>
                    <li>Funding decisions will be communicated to the corresponding Network Investigator in writing by the Network Management Office. </li>
                </ol>

                <h3>Contact</h3>
                <p>Questions about this funding program can be directed to Jeanie Zabukovec, AGE-WELL Research and Partnerships Administrator (<a href='mailto:jeanie@agewell-nce.ca'>jeanie@agewell-nce.ca</a>).</p>
            ]]>
        </Static>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="cover" tooltip="Cover Sheet" name="Cover Sheet" blobSection="COVER_SHEET" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="i" type="TextReportItem" blobItem="PROJECT">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li>
                    <b>Investigator Name: </b>{$user_name}&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>Institution: </b>{$user_uni}<br />
                    <b>Project Title:&nbsp;</b>{$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ii" type="RadioReportItem" options="Knowledge Mobilization|Commercialization" blobItem="TYPE">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Project Type</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iii" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" limit="150" blobItem="SUMMARY">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Provide a 150-word plain language summary of the purpose, rationale and anticipated impact(s) of the project.</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="iv" type="IntegerReportItem" min="0" max="25000" width="43px" align="left" blobItem="INVESTMENT">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>Total value of AGE-WELL investment requested:</b> ${$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="v" type="SelectReportItem" options="WP1 NEEDS-OA|WP2 NEEDS-CG|WP3 TECH-FAI|WP4 TECH-APS|WP5 TECH-DD|WP6 TECH-MCH|WP7 POLICY-TECH|WP8 ETHICS-TECH" blobItem="WP">
            <![CDATA[
                <li>
                    <b>The proposed project is best aligned with AGE-WELL</b>
                    {$item}
                    (WP descriptions are available here: <a href='http://agewell-nce.ca/research/research-themes-and-projects' target="_blank">http://agewell-nce.ca/research/research-themes-and-projects</a>) 
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="narrative" tooltip="PART 1 - Narrative Application" title="PART 1 - Narrative Application" name="Narrative Application" blobSection="NARRATIVE" type="EditableReportSection">
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>1) RATIONALE AND APPROACH</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="rational" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="RATIONAL">
            <![CDATA[
                <style>
                    ol#list > li {
                        margin-bottom:15px;
                    }
                </style>
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Summarize the rationale for the project</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Why this project at this time?</li>
                        <li>What is the benefit/value-added of the proposed impact(s)?</li>
                        <li>What is unique about this project / how does it improve on previous work?</li>
                        <li>What is the strength of the evidence forming the basis for the planned dissemination and/or commercialization development activity?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="goals" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="GOALS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>State the project goals and objectives</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>What is the ultimate goal(s) of the proposed initiative?</li>
                        <li>State the objectives that need to be achieved to realize the ultimate goal(s).</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="kt" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="KT">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Describe the KM/KT, commercialization, business strategy, or approach to be used</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>To whom will the evidence/knowledge/information/product be disseminated? Provide a sense of the size/scale of the target audience/market</li>
                        <li>How will your proposed activities address target audience/market needs? (e.g., product development and distribution efforts, market gap/societal need/demand)</li>
                        <li>Describe how user sector contexts and needs have been accounted for</li>
                        <li>Describe your IP strategy, if applicable</li>
                        <li>Describe the competitive advantage of your product/business/start-up, your main competitors, and business model, if applicable</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>2) IMPACT AND EVALUTION</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="impact" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="IMPACT">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Describe the anticipated impacts and associated benefits and beneficiaries of this project</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Describe how your proposed project contributes to and/or facilitates the commercialization, translation, mobilization and/or policy use of research to accelerate Canadian innovation, and economic competitiveness, and to improve the lives of older adults and/or caregivers.</li>
                        <li>Identify the anticipated impacts of this project–what will change, who will benefit and how?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="evaluate" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="EVALUATE">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>How and when will you evaluate this initiative?</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>How will you measure success of this project?</li>
                        <li>How will the results of the evaluation process provide feedback to future initiatives related to this initiative?</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <Static>
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>3) PROJECT TEAM AND PARTNERSHIPS</h2>
            ]]>
        </Static>
        <ReportItem id="expertise" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="EXPERTISE">
            <![CDATA[
                <ol id='list' type="i">
                <li><b>Describe how the expertise of your team will contribute to the success of the proposed initiative</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Identify additional skills needed to fill expertise gaps on your team, if any, and how you plan to address them (note that team members and expertise will be listed in the appendix)</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="partners" type="TextareaReportItem" rich="true" blobItem="PARTNERS">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Outline the partnerships involved and partner roles/responsibilities (e.g. dissemination, product development, testing and evaluation etc.).</b>
                    <ul class='small'>
                        <li>Identify all partners/partnership arrangements (contributions will be itemized in an appendix)</li>
                    </ul>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="appendix" tooltip="PART 2 - Appendix" title="PART 2 - Appendix" name="Appendix" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="APPENDIX">
        <ReportItem id="team" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="TEAM" labels="Team Member Name|Role|Institution/Organization|Expertise|Email" types="Text|Select(PL,NI,Partner)|Text|Textarea|Text" sizes="150||150||150" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Team Summary</h2>
                <p class='small'>Use the following code for Role:<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;PL:</b> Project Lead<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;NI:</b> Network Investigator<br />
                <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;Partner</b></p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="HQP" labels="Name|Institution|Email|Level of Study/Position" types="Text|Text|Text|Text" sizes="150|150|150|" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Highly Qualified Personnel (HQP)</h2>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" type="BudgetReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="BUDGET" structure="AGEWELL_BUDGET_STRUCTURE" template="AGE-WELL Budget.xlsx">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just1" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST1" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <p>Please use the following categories in your budget justification as appropriate. Note that SIP funding includes specific budget caps in some categories.</p>
                <ol>
                <li><b>Salaries to students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just2" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST2" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Salaries to non-students</b>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just3" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST3" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Professional & Tech. Services/contracts</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Consultants and business development services (maximum $5,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just4" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST4" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Equipment</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Purchase of rental</li>
                        <li>Maintenance costs</li>
                        <li>Operating costs</li>
                        <li>Other equipment costs</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just5" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST5" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Computing and Software</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Specialized software licenses and e-communications costs</li>
                        <li>E-business enablement costs, website</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just6" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST6" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Materials, Supplies & Other expenditures</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Materials and Supplies</li>
                        <li>Patent costs (maximum $3,000)</li>
                        <li>Proof of Principle, product validation for market readiness</li>
                        <li>Prototype development (specify)</li>
                        <li>Communications/Marketing/Printing/Production (maximum $5,000)</li>
                        <li>Evaluation costs</li>
                        <li>Management and Networking (maximum $3,000)</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="just7" type="TextareaReportItem" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="JUST7" height="100px">
            <![CDATA[
                <li><b>Travel</b>
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>Field trips</li>
                        <li>Conference, technical shows</li>
                    </ol>
                    {$item}
                </li>
                </ol>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <!--ReportItem id="other_funds" type="MultiTextReportItem" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" labels="Funding Agency|Type of Grant|Program|Status|Value" types="Text|Select(1,2,3,4,5,6,7)|Text|Select(PA,GH,E/C)|Integer" sizes="||||75" blobItem="OTHER_FUNDS" multiple="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Other Funds</h3>
                <table class='small'>
                    <tr>
                        <th style='width:200px;' align='left'>Type of Grant</th>
                        <th align='left'>Status</th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td valign='top'>
                            1. Provincial<br />
                            2. CIHR/NSERC/SSHRC<br />
                            3. Other Provincial<br />
                            4. Other Federal<br />
                            5. International<br />
                            6. Other AGE-WELL NCE<br />
                            7. Other non-AGE-WELL<br />
                        </td>
                        <td valign='top'>
                            PA: Pending Approval<br />
                            GH: Grant Held<br />
                            E/C: Expired/Completed<br />
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem-->
        <!--ReportItem id="milestones" type="Upload" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="MILESTONES" mimeType="application/vnd.ms-excel">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Milestones</h2>
                <a href='{$wgServer}{$wgScriptPath}/data/AGE-WELL Milestones.xls'>Download Spreadsheet Template</a>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem-->
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="bio" tooltip="PART 3 - Investigator Bio and Partner Letter of Support" title="PART 3 - Investigator Bio and Partner Letter of Support" name="Bio &amp; Letter of Support" type="EditableReportSection" blobSection="BIO">
        <ReportItem id="bio" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="BIO" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Investigator Bio</h3>
                <p>Highlight experience and activities relevant to the application. 2 page maximum.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="letter" type="UploadReportItem" blobItem="LETTER" mimeType="application/zip" fileSize="5">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Partner Letter of Support</h3>
                <p>Although cash and in-kind contributions from commercial or community partners are not strictly required for this funding program, projects will normally be expected to include partner organizations in dissemination or commercialization planning and should detail these in the application.</p>
                <p>For reporting purposes, all partnership activities should be quantified in <i>Part II – Appendix</i> of the application package and supported by a signed letter from the partnering organization.</p>
                <p>Partner letters of support must:</p> 
                <ul>
                    <li>appear on the letterhead of the partner organization </li>
                    <li>detail the specifics of the contribution and the timeframe that applies</li> 
                    <li>match the details provided in the project application</li>
                    <li>be signed by a person at the organization with the appropriate authority to authorize the contribution and commit the organization to providing the resources noted</li>
                </ul>
                <b>The uploaded file must be a Zip Archive</b>.
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
