<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="SIP Project Evaluation" pdfFiles="SIPProjectEvaluationPDF" extends="ProjectEvaluation">
    <ReportSection id="overview">
        <ReportItem id="instructions" type="Static">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The objectives of the NCE program are to mobilize multi-disciplinary research capacity from across Canada, engage partners from multiple academic institutions and various public and private-sector organizations, train the next generation of highly qualified people, work with end users to accelerate the creation and application of new knowledge as well as increase collaboration between research in Canada and abroad.</p>
 
                <p>The aim of the form is to allow the RMC to assess the performance against the objectives set in your application and the key impact objectives of AGE-WELL to demonstrate that the network is effectively working to achieve our goals.</p>

                <p>AGE-WELL produces products (technologies, services and policy) that MUST have impact. Progress towards achieving these products can be defined and measured across all projects in a consistent fashion. The Product Readiness Levels (PRL) is a method of estimating maturity and progress towards a product across 5 stages that overlay the Technology Readiness Levels (TRL). The five stage progression is based on the funding continuum of the innovation pipeline developed for CIHR’s eHealth innovations Partnership Program (eHIPP). The TRL is a well-established approach in engineering and other fields.  AGE-WELL has adapted both scales to be inclusive of the types of projects and products that are part of the Network. Please refer to the Product Readiness Levels Guideline table for definitions of the PRL levels, as well as example outputs at each level across product type.  Note that the current outputs in this table are only examples and will be added to as we continue to roll out this process. (Feedback is welcomed.)</p>

                <p>Each project is required to complete one table related to each of the 5 NCE objectives (Scientific Excellence, Networking and Partnerships, Knowledge Mobilization, Commercialization and HQP Training) <b>for the period of the award term</b>. <u>All projects are asked to only complete the cells relevant to their project</u>. Projects will only be reviewed against themselves and the progress they make towards the objectives they proposed in their application.</p>

                <p>The report consists of qualitative and quantitative information to appropriately capture the progress your project has made on the key impact areas.</p>

                <p>The report requests three types of information:
                    <ol>
                        <li>Narrative- a short written account of what the project has been doing to achieve impact;</li>
                        <li>Metrics- quantitative data (most values are auto populated via reporting on Forum) substantiating information must be provided for all entered values; and </li>
                        <li>Case study (optional)- a short vignette that describes an outstanding work or achievement by the project.</li>
                    </ol>
                </p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="research">
        <ReportItem id="pagebreak" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="planning" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="plan_head">
            <![CDATA[
                <table style="display:none;">
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="networking">
        <ReportItem id="pagebreak" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="planning" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="plan_head">
            <![CDATA[
                <table style="display:none;">
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ktee1">
        <ReportItem id="pagebreak" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="planning" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="plan_head">
            <![CDATA[
                <table style="display:none;">
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="ktee2">
        <ReportItem id="pagebreak" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="planning" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="plan_head">
            <![CDATA[
                <table style="display:none;">
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="hqp">
        <ReportItem id="pagebreak" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="planning" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="plan_head">
            <![CDATA[
                <table style="display:none;">
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="narrative2">
        <ReportItem id="justification" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="level" delete="true" />
        <ReportItem id="steps" type="Textarea" blobItem="STEPS" rich="true">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>What are the next steps for your product to progress along the PRL scale? What resources do you have in place/need to ensure ongoing success?</h3>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
