<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="Workpackage Report" reportType="RP_WP_REPORT" pdfType="RPTP_WP_REPORT" pdfFiles="WPReportPDF" personId="0" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role role="WPL">
            <SectionPermission id="summary" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="nce" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="additional" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role role="WPC">
            <SectionPermission id="summary" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="nce" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="additional" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="summary" tooltip="Executive Summary" name="Executive Summary" title="1. Executive Summary" blobSection="SUMMARY" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="summary" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="SUMMARY">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Report Description</h3>
                <p>Each WP is asked to collect information and examples from across its constituent members/projects in order to complete a 4-5 page WP Report. Responses will be used to help the Network Management Office to construct the 2019/20 AGE-WELL Annual Report which NCE will use to evaluate AGE-WELL this spring. WPs are not individually evaluated on the content of these reports.</p>

                <p>Note that the information requested in Sections 1 and 2 is drawn directly from the NCE Annual Report template. Section 3 enables WPs to highlight additional outcomes or benefits of network membership not captured elsewhere in the report. Given the brevity of the report, we are looking for concrete examples from across each WP as opposed to a full accounting of all WP activities. Should you have more to share with us than space limitations permit, please contact <a href='mailto:Jennifer@agewell-nce.ca'>Jennifer@agewell-nce.ca</a></p>
                
                <h3>2019/20 Executive Summary</h3>
                <p>Describe the top three achievements, successes, contributions, success stories from your WP <u>from the past year</u> and their impacts as they relate to the realization of AGE-WELL goals and objectives.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="nce" tooltip="NCE Evaluation Criteria" name="NCE Evaluation Criteria" title="2. Evaluation Criteria" blobSection="NCE" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="excellence" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="EXCELLENCE">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>a) Excellence of the Research Program (3600 characters / ¾ pg)</h3>
                <p><i>AGE-WELL’s research program is driven to address Canadian needs and problems, and is therefore expected to be multidisciplinary and multisectoral.  We are evaluated on the excellence, focus and coherence of the research program. For your WP, please comment on the follow providing concrete examples where possible.</i></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Describe the balance between discovery and application-based research in this WP</li>
                    <li>Describe the ways in which the work of this WP is addressing new and emerging social and ethical challenges</li>
                    <li>Highlight any notable achievements of researchers within your WP, including publications in top-tier journals, leadership awards etc</li>
                    <li>Provide examples from within your WP of international leadership or activities that have contributed to the visibility of AGE-WELL domestically or abroad</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="hqp" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="HQP">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>b) Development of Highly Qualified Personnel (2000 characters ½ pg)</h3>
                <p><i>The training and retention of HQP is imperative to maximize the effectiveness of the Networks’ contribution to the wealth, wellness and well-being of Canadians. The multidisciplinary and multisectoral nature of a network should be utilized to provide unique mentorship and training opportunities to maximize HQP retention and integration in all facets of the workforce.</i></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Give examples from your WP of HQP being provided with novel, transdisciplinary or innovative experiences, including examples of exposure to the economic, social or ethical implications of AGE-WELL research through training opportunities.</li>
                    <li>Give examples of any new training initiatives developed from AGE-WELL work (e.g. training modules in your WP area, for example)</li>
                    <li>If relevant, please highlight examples of HQP leadership / career development related to the knowledge mobilization of commercialization such as launching a start-up company, filing patents, hosting stakeholder consultations etc.</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="networking" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="NETWORKING">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>c) Networking and Partnerships (3600 characters/ ¾ pg)</h3>
                <p><i>AGE-WELL must demonstrate that it has brought together the key individuals and organizations needed to generate and implement multifaceted solutions to the complex Canadian challenges it is designed to address.</i></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Describe new collaborations developed during the reporting period (e.g. new links between national and international academic institutions, federal and provincial agencies, non-governmental organizations and private sector participants). Who was involved and what activities did the team engage in?</li>
                    <li>Describe any examples of optimization of resources through the sharing of equipment and research facilities, databases and personnel within this WP.</li>
                    <li>Describe cross-WP or cross-Project activities that your team engaged in this year, highlighting examples of working transdisciplinarily. </li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ktee" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="KTEE">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>d) Knowledge Exchange and Exploitation (3600 characters / ¾ pg)</h3>
                <p><i>NCE networks are expected to generate social and economic benefits by ensuring the rapid flow of ideas and innovations from researchers to Canadian receptors.</i></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Highlight notable KTEE successes such as new products, processes or services with commercial potential; social innovations that may contribute to public policy in Canada.</li>
                    <li>Describe examples of effective collaboration with the private, public and not-for-profit sectors in technology, market development, and public policy development</li>
                </ul>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="additional" tooltip="Additional Information" name="Additional Information" title="3. Additional Information" blobSection="INFORMATION" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="outcomes" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="OUTCOMES">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>a) Other Outcomes</h3>
                <p>While it is important that we demonstrate achievement in the NCE Program areas above, we realize that there are other ways to define success and achievement relevant to AGE-WELL’s mission and vision. In this section, please describe any success or achievements that you would like to highlight that have not been covered in the sections above.</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="benefits" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="BENEFITS">
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>b) Benefits of Network Involvement</h3>
                <p>NCEs ideally provide its members with benefits and opportunities that are realizable through a multisectoral networked approach. Please describe any benefits accrued by your team(s) resulting from your specific involvement in AGE-WELL (e.g. team cohesion, access to new partners etc.)</p>
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="initiatives" tooltip="4. Key Workpackage Outputs &amp; Initiatives (2015-2020)" name="Outputs &amp; Initiatives" title="4. Key Workpackage Outputs &amp; Initiatives (2015-2020)" blobSection="INITIATIVES" type="EditableReportSection">
        <ReportItem id="initiatives" type="TextareaReportItem" blobItem="INITIATIVES">
            <![CDATA[
                <b>*Note that this question pertains to all five years of WP funding.</b>
                <p>An important part of AGE-WELL’s mandate is to promote and put into action key outputs from our first five years. To achieve this, we are developing a knowledge repository of ‘shareable’ outputs to support and educate project teams and trainees within the network, or make available outside the network, if appropriate and with permission.</p>
                
                <p>Note that we are not looking for academic journal publications, but rather best practice guidelines, manuals, scoping reviews, white papers, policy briefs, educational materials, data sets, frameworks, toolkits, video/films and/or websites etc.</p>
                
                <p>Since your team has been reporting outputs on Forum and/or to the NMO for five years now, we expect that these key outputs have already been reported—we are looking for you to help us understand which ones you consider appropriate and relevant to share in order to support continued growth of AGE-WELL and development of the sector as a whole.</p>
                
                <p>Please list what you consider the top 5 ‘shareable’ outputs of this WP (can be either WP-level or project-level outputs). Please indicate whether each output should remain internal to AGE-WELL or whether you think it is ripe for broader dissemination (external). Please provide links and/or attachments of materials below.</p>
                
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload1" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD1" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload2" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD2" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload3" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD3" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload4" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD4" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="upload5" type="UploadReportItem" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="UPLOAD5" mimeType="application/pdf">
            <![CDATA[
                {$item}
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" name="Review" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" tooltip="PDF generation" name="Submit" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <ReportItem id="review" type="SimpleReviewSubmitReportItem" emails="jennifer@agewell-nce.ca" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
