<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report name="NI Report" reportType="RP_RESEARCHER" pdfType="RPTP_NORMAL" pdfFiles="NIReportPDF" pdfAllProjects="true" ajax="true" disabled="false">
    <Permissions>
        <Role start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" role="PNI">
            <SectionPermission id="status" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="dashboard" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="report" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="budget" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
        <Role start="REPORTING_CYCLE_START" end="REPORTING_CYCLE_END" role="CNI">
            <SectionPermission id="status" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="dashboard" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="report" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="budget" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="review" permissions="rw" />
            <SectionPermission id="submit" permissions="rw" />
        </Role>
    </Permissions>
    <ReportSection id="status" name="Report Completion Status" tooltip="Evaluation of your report against the reporting rules" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false" private="true">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This year's reporting is similar to last year's with a few changes due to the fact that, effective April 1st 2014, GRAND is entering Phase2</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>The report narrative section should refer to your activities from January 2013 to December 2013 on Phase1 projects, except that the "plans forward" section should refer to Phase2 projects.  To that end, you should make sure that you have been added to all Phase2 projects in the context of which you plan to work in Phase2.  The list of Phase2 project can be found at <a target='_blank' href='https://forum.grand-nce.ca/index.php/GRAND:Projects'>GRAND:Projects</a> (see the "Phase 2" tab) and additional information, including the PLs and co-PLs, can be found by following the individual project link.</li>
                    <li>The budget-request section will also refer to Phase2 projects.  In general, no request should be made for Phase1 projects.</li>
                </ol>
                <br />
                <p>This page provides an overview of the degree to which your report and the reports of those whose input you require are complete. Five aspects of your report are inspected:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Regarding the products reported in the dashboard, the degree to which their descriptions are complete is examined.</li>
                    <li>Regarding the open-ended sections of the report, i.e., your executive summary, your assessment on how you contribute towards the NCE evaluation criteria, your reflections and your budget justification, the number of text-boxes edited and whether or not any of them exceed the maximum number of characters allowed is reported.</li>
                    <li>Regarding the milestones of the projects in which you are involved, this page mentions the counts of the milestones on which you have commented, those that you have mentioned you are not involved with, and the ones on which you have not commented at all.</li>
                    <li>The status of your revised allocated budget is reported.</li>
                    <li>The number of your HQP that have reported (vs. the total number of your HQP) is reported.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>In addition to the summary table under the heading "NI Progress", you can find details on the degree to which your HQP have completed their reports. Clicking on the "Report PDF" downloads a copy of the HQP report. Clicking on the "On-Line Report" button enables you to impersonate the HQP in question and view and edit the parts of their report on the projects on which you supervise them (see more on how to impersonate HQP in the <a href='../index.php/Help:Contents'>FAQ</a>). Clicking on the "Notify HQP" lets you send a forum notification to the HQP and (if you wish) an email message, with a communication regarding their report.</p>
                <p><b>Note: All your Phase1 PLs have access to your on-line project-specific dashboard rows; your executive summary; your project-specific comments under criteria A B C and D; and your project-specific milestone comments.  The PLs of your Phase2 projects have access to your executive summary and your project-specific plans forward.</b></p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="my_progress_head" type="StaticReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[<h3>NI Progress</h3><table cellpadding="1" frame="box" rules="all" style="width:600px;">]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ni_progress_head" type="ProgressReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="my_hqp_progress_head" type="SupervisorProgressReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="dash_progress_head" type="DashboardProgressReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="progress_head" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[</table><h3>HQP Progress</h3>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="static_hqp_progress" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<style>#hqp_completion table tr:first-child td:first-child {display:none;}</style><table id="hqp_completion" style="background:#ffffff;" cellspacing='1' cellpadding='3' frame='box' rules='all'><tr><th>HQP</th><th>Completion Status</th><th>Actions</th></tr>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItemSet id="people_supervises" type="PersonSupervisesReportItemSet">
        	<ReportItem id="hqp_submission" type="ReportSubmissionStatusItem" reportType="HQPReport">
                <![CDATA[
                    <tr><td valgin='top'><a href='{$user_url}' target='_blank'><small><b>{$user_reversed_name}</b></small></a><br /><small>({$item})</small></td>
                ]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItem id="hqp_progress" type="ProgressReportItem" reportType="HQPReport">
                <![CDATA[
                    <td style='padding:0;'><small><table cellpadding="1" frame="void" rules="all" height="95px" width="100%">{$item}</table></small></td>
                ]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItem id="hqp_pdf" type="PDFReportItem" reportType="HQPReport" width="90px">
                <![CDATA[<td valign='top'>{$item}<br />]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItem id="hqp_report" type="SeeReportReportItem" reportType="HQPReport" project="false" width="90px">
                <![CDATA[{$item}<br />]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItem id="hqp_notify" type="NotificationReportItem" title="Notify HQP" url="Special:Report?report=HQPReport" width="90px">
                <![CDATA[{$item}</td></tr>]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
        <ReportItem id="progress_foot" type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[</table>]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="dashboard" name="NI Dashboard" tooltip="Overview of this year's activity and productivity" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="true">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The Dashboard is designed to provide an overview of a researcher's activity in GRAND, both within the context of specific projects (each represented by a row in the Dashboard table) and overall (reflected in the final "Totals" row of the table). The data reported in the dashboard has already been input to the Forum through the various functionalities of the "Toolbox".</p>
                
                <p>The dashboard is meant to provide a quick overview of the NIs involvement in GRAND during the reporting period (January 1 through December 31), in two tables. The "Network" table summarizes the number of HQP supervised by the NI, the average number of hours the NI devotes to GRAND, and the partners with whom the NI has interacted. The "Productivity" table reports the numbers of the various products of the NI's GRAND activity, such as publications, artifacts, presentations, multimedia stories, activities (e.g., event-organization) and press pieces, awards bestowed on the NI and any additional contributions the NI has obtained to support GRAND-related activities.</p>

<p>The content of these two dashboard tables is not editable. If they do not accurately reflect your activities and productivity over the current calendar year, you should use the Toolbox (to the left of the page) to update the relevant content on the Forum. Note that each row of the dashboard is project-specific and there might be redundancy across some rows. The 'totals' row only reports unique entities.</p>
                <h3>The Network Table</h3>

                <p>Under <b><i>HQP</i></b>, the network table reports HQP who have been listed as being supervised by the NI during the current reporting period. The detailed listing of the HQP (accessible when you click on and of the HQP column links) documents more precisely why each individual HQP is listed.</li>

                <p>Under <b><i>Partners/Champions</i></b>, the network table reports the organizations that have made a contribution (cash, in-kind or otherwise) towards the GRAND-related activities of the NI (i.e., Partners), and the champions(individuals) with whom the NI is working. An individual is a Champion if the NI has been collaborating with him/her in the context of a project, even if the relation is not formal yet. To specify a "Champion" you have to (a) add them on the forum (using the "add user" tool) and give them the "Champion" role, and (b) specify that you are "working with" them (using the "edit relations" tool).</p>
                
                <p>The last two columns of the network table reports are the <b><i>(NI) budget allocation</i></b> for the current funding year (2013-14) and the <b><i>budget request</i></b> for the forthcoming funding year (2014-15). If the first budget amount is missing, then you must upload your budget reflecting your actual 2013-14 allocation (not including carryover), through the "My Profile" -> "Budget" page. If the second budget amount is missing, then you have not yet uploaded a proper budget request for 2014-15 in the "NI budget" step of the reporting workflow; a corresponding error message will appear in your report-completion status.</p>
                <p>The hours/week shown for each project are as reported in the "NI Milestone Comments" tab, under each project-specific heading.</p>
                
                <h3>The Productivity Table</h3>
                <p>Under <b><i>Publications</i></b>, the productivity table reports any publication co-authored by the NI, with a date within current reporting year and two years into the future (to account for "to appear" publications). Publications are of different types but, in principle, are documents that appear in archival venues and can be cited.</p>

                <p>Under <b><i>Artifacts</i></b>, the productivity table reports any artifact co-produced by the NI, with a date within the current reporting year and two years into the future (to account for things like scheduled software releases and planned artistic installations). This category of productivity evidence includes curated data repositories, open-source software, and artistic works. They are annotated as "peer reviewed" or "non peer-reviewed".</p>

                <p>Under <b><i>Presentations</i></b>, the productivity table reports any activity in which the NI was involved, with a date within the current reporting year and two years into the future. This category is meant to include conference presentations and similar activities.</p>

                <p>Under <b><i>Activities</i></b>, the productivity table reports any activity in which the NI was involved, with a date the current reporting year and two years beyond. This category is meant to include conference or workshop organization and similar activities.</p>
                
                <!--<p>Under <b><i>Multimedia Stories</i></b>, the productivity table reports stories that might be of interest to the community at large, and could possibly be shared through the public web site. The text associated with the media piece (image/audio/video) should</p>
                <ol>
                    <li>explain why the story is important; how the accomplishment illustrated by the story will benefit Canadians; how it is different from existing technology and what problem it addresses;</li>
                    <li>identify the receptor community for this product/service/technology;</li>
                    <li>define 2-3 challenges in accomplishing the result illustrated by the story and explain how they were overcome; and</li>
                    <li>provide a caption for the video and or photo.</li>
                </ol>-->
                <p>Under <b><i>Awards</i></b>, the productivity table reports awards bestowed to the NI within the current reporting year.</p>

                <p>Under <b><i>Contributions</i></b>, the productivity table reports cash and in-kind contributions to the NI's GRAND-related research activities by agencies outside GRAND during the current reporting year.</p>

                <p>To reiterate, the Dashboard is designed to provide an overview of a researcher's activity in GRAND, both within the context of specific projects (each represented by a row in the Dashboard table) and overall (reflected in the final "Totals" row of the table). The data reported in the dashboard has already been input to the Forum through the various functionalities of the "Toolbox".</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="basic_info" type="StaticReportItem">
        <![CDATA[
            <div class='basic_info' style='margin-bottom:20px;'>
                <p><b>Name:</b> {$user_reversed_name} ({$user_full_roles})</p>
                <p><b>Position:</b> {$user_level}</p>
                <p><b>Department:</b> {$user_dept}</p>
                <p><b>University:</b> {$user_uni}</p>
                <p><b>Phase 2 Projects:</b> {$user_phase2_projects}</p>
                <p><b>Phase 1 Projects:</b> {$user_phase1_projects}</p>
            </div>
        ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ni_dashboard" type="DashboardReportItem" structure="NI_REPORT_STRUCTURE">
            <![CDATA[<h2>Network</h2><div>{$item}</div>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="top_prods" type="PersonTopProductsReportItem" max="5">
            <![CDATA[<h2>Top Research Outcomes</h2><div>{$item}</div>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ni_dashboard_productivity" type="DashboardReportItem" structure="NI_REPORT_PRODUCTIVITY_STRUCTURE">
            <![CDATA[<h2>Productivity</h2>
                        <div style='max-width:900px;'>If there is an error in any of the information reported in the dashboard, please edit the corresponding element through the appropriate tool. If the error is in a system-controlled field, please contact <a href='mailto:support@forum.grand-nce.ca'>support</a>.</div><div>{$item}</div>]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="report" name="NI Report" tooltip="Open-ended report narratives" blobSection="RES_RESACTIVITY" type="EditableReportSection" autosave="true" number="1,2,3" renderpdf="true">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The intent of this section is to enable each NI report in an open-ended format on his/her activities and accomplishments during the term of the report.</p>
                <small><i>NOTE: Clicking on the second-level headings of this page will cause the page to expand (contract) to show (hide) text boxes in which you can provide your information. The color of the heading indicates whether the text under this heading meets (purple) or exceeds (red) the maximum permitted number of characters.</i></small>
                <h3>I. Executive Summary: Overview of all of my GRAND Activity</h3>
                <p><i>(Limit: 3600 characters)</i></p>

                <p>Please provide a brief narrative overview of your accomplishments over the past year, highlighting the ways in which your work is contributing to the NCE program objectives of connecting research and development to the economic and social well-being of Canada.</p>

                <p>The executive summary should try to answer the following questions:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>What are the problems in the real world that your research addresses?</li>
                    <li>Why is it important and to whom is it important to solve these problems?</li>
                    <li>What did you do to address these problems?</li>
                    <li>What evidence do you have that your approaches are good ones?</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>II. Assessment: How I contribute towards the NCE Evaluation Criteria</h3>
                <p>The five NCE Program criteria used in assessing our network are described in detail on the <a href='http://www.nce-rce.gc.ca/ReportsPublications-RapportsPublications/NCE-RCE/ProgramGuide-GuideProgramme_eng.asp#a35'>NCE website</a>. Note that these criteria are written to describe the evaluation of the overall network, but we seek information from each researcher that can help build a composite story for progress, success and good management in the area of each criterion. Each of the boxes below has the definition of the NCE criterion that is required for the entire GRAND network, and some suggestions of information to be provided about the research in the project to elicit information relevant to the criterion.</p>

                <p>We do not expect each researcher to contribute equally to success against each criterion, but researchers with stronger contributions in several of the criteria will receive a more positive evaluation than those without strong contributions in at least some of the criteria. As such, please give us information about your contributions as measured by these criteria if relevant and significant.</p>

                <p>Note that for each of the first four of the five criteria, the text box is "split" into a number of separate fields corresponding to the projects with which you are involved. This is necessary for practical purposes, in order to forward the project-specific information to the corresponding project leader. The project-specific entries will be made available to the applicable project leader for assistance in the preparation of the Project Report. However, no matter the number of projects, each of the five criterion sections will be read as a whole as part of your individual evaluation as a researcher, so please construct your responses accordingly. Please feel free to devote unequal space to the individual projects and to make sure that the overall section reads well and communicates the information you want to communicate about your activity. You can see the overall report by clicking the "Preview" link right next to each of the criterion headings.</p>
                
                <h4>A. Excellence of the Research Program</h4>
                <p><i>(Reported by Project - Overall Limit (across all projects): 1800 characters)</i></p>
                
                <p>The Network's research program must be driven to address Canadian needs and problems, and is therefore expected to be multidisciplinary and multi-sectoral.<br />
In this section you should describe</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>the excellence of your research on a world scale and how it compares to leading efforts in other places;</li>
                    <li>the ways in which your research is tailored to the Canadian context in terms of topic and content, or in terms of needs of Canadian companies or other receptors;</li>
                    <li>the multidisciplinary nature of your work or the research team that gives this work more excellence or potential for impact and how it enables more multi-sectoral applicability of the results and interactions with receptors.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>You can reference Products by writing "@Product Title" in the text box and select the product from the drop-down box appearing below the textbox.</p>
                
                <h4>B. Development of Highly Qualified Personnel</h4>
                <p><i>(Reported by Project - Overall Limit (across all projects): 1800 characters)</i></p>
                <p>The training and retention of HQP is imperative to maximize the effectiveness of the Network’s contribution to the wealth, wellness and well being of Canadians. The Training Program proposed by the Network is expected to add value to the formal training initiatives already available through the academic community and should aim at helping students find employment in the Canadian economy (i.e., private sector partners, government, etc.). The multidisciplinary and multi-sectoral nature of a Network should be utilized to provide unique mentorship and training opportunities to maximize HQP retention and integration in all facets of the workforce.</p>
                <p>Please use this space to highlight the most significant examples that demonstrate added value to the training of HQP, and comment on the "philosophy" or approach for training HQP to position them well to contribute to digital media in Canada.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>How did the existence of the project affect the HQP (to get better training or position them better for jobs in Canada)?</li>
                    <li>How have HQP affected the project to create those benefits for other HQP?</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Please give examples if possible.</p>
                <p>You can reference HQP by writing "@HQP Name" in the text box and select the HQP from the drop-down box appearing below the textbox.</p>
                
                <h4>C. Networking and Partnerships</h4>
                <p><i>(Reported by Project - Overall Limit (across all projects): 1800 characters)</i></p>
                <p>The Network must demonstrate that it has brought together the key individuals and organizations needed to generate and implement multifaceted solutions to the complex Canadian challenges it is designed to address.</p>
                <p>Describe your activities networking with other GRAND researchers and projects, and researchers outside of GRAND.
Describe your involvement with receptor organizations, industry partners and Project Champions.</p>
                <p>How have these connections accelerated your research or broadened its scope and applicability?</p>
                <p>You can reference Project Members by writing "@Project Member Name" in the text box and select the member from the drop-down box appearing below the textbox.</p>
                
                <h4>D. Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation</h4>
                <p><i>(Reported by Project - Overall Limit (across all projects): 1800 characters)</i></p>
                <p>NCE Networks and Centres are expected to generate social and economic benefits by ensuring the rapid flow of ideas and innovations from researchers to Canadian receptors. Applicants are expected to demonstrate that the appropriate activities will be undertaken and the appropriate resources allocated to maximize those benefits.</p>
                <p>Describe the interactions with receptors, companies, Project Champions and others in which research challenges and outcomes from your work were discussed or presented.</p>
                <p>Describe any student internships, transfers of technology, unique publications, or other evidence of the impact of your research. How has the existence of GRAND, or GRAND personnel, influenced these activities?</p>
                
                <h4>E. Management of the Network</h4>
                <p><i>(Limit: 1800 characters)</i></p>
                <p>Each Network must have an organizational structure appropriate for the management of the research and business functions of a complex multidisciplinary, multi-institutional program.</p>
                <p>Outside of your role as a researcher, describe what role(s) you've had in GRAND, whether or not funded by GRAND, that contribute to the operation or success of the Network. As examples, this might include your role as Theme co-Leader or organizer of a networking event, which in turn might include some aspect of Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation.</p>
                <p>You can reference a GRAND Forum Member by writing "@Member Name" in the text box and select the member from the drop-down box appearing below the textbox.</p>
                
                <h3>III. Reflections: Other Aspects of my involvement in GRAND</h3>
                <h4>Proposed Activity: My Plans for 2014 in GRAND</h4>
                <p><i>(Report by Phase 2 Project - Overall Limit (across all Phase 2 projects): 3600 characters)</i></p>
                <p>In this section, you should discuss your objectives and plans of your Phase 2 projects for the upcoming year.  To that end you should contact the PL or co-PL of Phase2 projects in order to get added to their projects.</p>
                <p>You can reference Sub-Projects by writing "@Sub-Project Name" in the text box and select the sub-project from the drop-down box appearing below the textbox.</p>
                
                <h4>Benefits of Networking: The value to my research program of my participation in GRAND</h4>
                <p><i>(Limit: 600 characters)</i></p>
                <p>In GRAND's reports to the NCE Secretariat, it is helpful to describe ways that the existence of GRAND has benefited researchers and projects. If appropriate, please explain any ways in which GRAND has had a positive impact on your research or projects.</p>
                <h4>Additional Comments</h4>
                <p><i>(Limit: 1800 characters)</i></p>
                <p>If you have any additional comments that you wish to convey to the evaluators, please enter them here. If there have been delays in your research due to medical or other personal issues, you may wish to indicate the impact these have had and your expectations for future progress.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id='0_head' type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h2>GRAND Time</h2>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="grand_time" width="40px" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="RES_MIL_CONTRIBUTIONS" type="IntegerReportItem" private="true" min="0" max="168">
            <![CDATA[<div>{$item}<span style="font-weight:bold;"> Time Devoted to GRAND Research and Management (hours / week)</span></div>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="grand_percent" width="40px" blobType="BLOB_ARRAY" blobItem="RES_MIL_CONTRIBUTIONS" type="IntegerReportItem" private="true" min="0" max="100">
            <![CDATA[<div>{$item}<span style="font-weight:bold;"> GRAND-related Research Activity relative to Overall Research Activity (%)</span></div><br />]]>
        </ReportItem>
<!-- I. Executive Summary -->
        <ReportItem id='I_head' type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h2>I. Executive Summary: Overview of all of my GRAND Activity</h2>]]>
        </ReportItem>
    <!-- Ia. Overview of NI Activity -->
        <ReportItemSet id='Ia_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="Overview of NI Activity">
            <ReportItem id="Ia" rows="12" width="100%" limit="3600" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_OVERALL" type="TextareaReportItem">
                <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
<!-- II. NCE Criteria -->
        <ReportItem id='II_head' type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h2>II. Assessment: How I contribute towards the NCE Evaluation Criteria</h2>]]>
        </ReportItem>
    <!-- IIa. Excellence of the Research Program -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIa_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="A. Excellence of the Research Program: How my research contributes to the Network">
            <ReportItemSet id="OR" type="ORReportItemSet">
                <ReportItemSet id="ProjectLimit_IIa" type="LimitReportItemSet" limit="1800">
                    <ReportItemSet id="projects" type="PersonProjectReportItemSet" phase="2">
                        <ReportItem id="IIa" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_EXCELLENCE" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="PersonProductsReportItemSet" index="product_id" label="product_title" name="Products" tooltipOptionId="Product ID" tooltipOptionName="Product Title">
                            <![CDATA[<i>{$project_name}</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                        <ReportItem id="excellence_hqp_comments" type="PopupReportItem" title="See HQP Comments" text="{$report_excellence_hqp_comments}">
                            <![CDATA[{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                    </ReportItemSet>
                    <ReportItem id="IIa" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_EXCELLENCE" blobSubItem="RES_RESACT_PHASE1" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="PersonProductsReportItemSet" index="product_id" label="product_title" name="Products" tooltipOptionId="Product ID" tooltipOptionName="Product Title" private="true">
                        <![CDATA[<i>Phase 1 Projects ({$user_phase1_projects})</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IIb. Development of Highly Qualified Personnel -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIb_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="B. Development of Highly Qualified Personnel: My training strategies and achievements">
            <ReportItemSet id="OR" type="ORReportItemSet">
                <ReportItemSet id="ProjectLimit_IIb" type="LimitReportItemSet" limit="1800">
                    <ReportItemSet id="projects" type="PersonProjectReportItemSet" phase="2">
                        <ReportItem id="IIb" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_HQPDEV" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="PersonSupervisesReportItemSet" index="user_id" label="user_name" name="HQP" tooltipOptionId="HQP ID" tooltipOptionName="HQP Name">
                            <![CDATA[<i>{$project_name}</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                    </ReportItemSet>
                    <ReportItem id="IIb" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_HQPDEV" blobSubItem="RES_RESACT_PHASE1" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="PersonSupervisesReportItemSet" index="user_id" label="user_name" name="HQP" tooltipOptionId="HQP ID" tooltipOptionName="HQP Name" private="true">
                        <![CDATA[<i>Phase 1 Projects ({$user_phase1_projects})</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IIc. Networking and Partnerships -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIc_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="C. Networking and Partnerships: My efforts and successes in building linkages">
            <ReportItemSet id="OR" type="ORReportItemSet">
                <ReportItemSet id="ProjectLimit_IIc" type="LimitReportItemSet" limit="1800">
                    <ReportItemSet id="projects" type="PersonProjectReportItemSet" phase="2">
                        <ReportItem id="IIc" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_NETWORKING" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="ProjectPeopleReportItemSet" index="user_id" label="user_name" name="{$project_name} Members" tooltipOptionId="Member ID" tooltipOptionName="Member Name">
                            <![CDATA[<i>{$project_name}</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                        <ReportItem id="networking_hqp_comments" type="PopupReportItem" title="See HQP Comments" text="{$report_networking_hqp_comments}">
                            <![CDATA[{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                    </ReportItemSet>
                    <ReportItem id="IIc" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_NETWORKING" blobSubItem="RES_RESACT_PHASE1" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="ProjectPeopleReportItemSet" index="user_id" label="user_name" name="{$project_name} Members" tooltipOptionId="Member ID" tooltipOptionName="Member Name" private="true">
                        <![CDATA[<i>Phase 1 Projects ({$user_phase1_projects})</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IId. Knowledge and Technology Exchange and Exploitation -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IId_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="D. Knowledge &amp; Technology Exchange &amp; Exploitation: My efforts in disseminating research to receptors">
            <ReportItemSet id="OR" type="ORReportItemSet">
                <ReportItemSet id="ProjectLimit_IId" type="LimitReportItemSet" limit="1800">
                    <ReportItemSet id="projects" type="PersonProjectReportItemSet" phase="2">
                        <ReportItem id="IId" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_KTEE" type="TextareaReportItem">
                            <![CDATA[<i>{$project_name}</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                        <ReportItem id="ktee_hqp_comments" type="PopupReportItem" title="See HQP Comments" text="{$report_ktee_hqp_comments}">
                            <![CDATA[{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                    </ReportItemSet>
                    <ReportItem id="IId" rows="12" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_KTEE" blobSubItem="RES_RESACT_PHASE1" type="TextareaReportItem" private="true">
                        <![CDATA[<i>Phase 1 Projects ({$user_phase1_projects})</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                    </ReportItem>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IIe. Management of the Network -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIe_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="E. Management of the Network: My role in or contribution to Network operations and governance" private="true">
            <ReportItem id="IIe" rows="12" width="100%" limit="1800" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_NETMAN" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="AllPeopleReportItemSet" index="user_id" label="user_name" name="Members" tooltipOptionId="Member ID" tooltipOptionName="Member Name">
                <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
        <!-- IIf. Plans for Next Year -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIf_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="false" level="4" title="F. My Plans for {$next_year} in GRAND">
            <ReportItem id='IIf_head' type="StaticReportItem">
                <![CDATA[<i>(Phase2 Projects Only)</i>]]>
            </ReportItem>
            <ReportItemSet id="OR" type="ORReportItemSet">
                <ReportItemSet id="ProjectLimit_IIf" type="LimitReportItemSet" limit="3600">
                    <ReportItemSet id="projects" type="PersonFutureProjectReportItemSet">
                        <ReportItem id="IIa" width="100%" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_NEXTPLANS" type="AutoCompleteTextareaReportItem" set="ProjectSubProjectsReportItemSet" index="project_id" label="project_name" name="Sub-Projects" tooltipOptionId="Sub-Project ID" tooltipOptionName="Sub-Project Name">
                            <![CDATA[<i>{$project_name}</i><br />{$item}<br />]]>
                        </ReportItem>
                    </ReportItemSet>
                </ReportItemSet>
            </ReportItemSet>
        </ReportItemSet>
<!-- III. Supplemental -->
        <ReportItem id='III_head' type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h2>III. Reflections: Other Aspects of my involvement in GRAND</h2>]]>
        </ReportItem>
    <!-- IIIb. Benefits from being involved in the Network -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIIb_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="Benefits of Networking: The value to my research program of my participation in GRAND" private="true">
            <ReportItem id="IIIb" rows="12" width="100%" limit="600" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_BENEF" type="TextareaReportItem">
                <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IIIc. Additional Comments -->
        <ReportItemSet id='IIIc_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" changeColor="true" level="4" title="Additional Comments" private="true">
            <ReportItem id="IIIc" rows="12" width="100%" limit="1800" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_RESACT_OTHER" type="TextareaReportItem">
                <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet>
    <!-- IIId. File Upload -->
        <!--ReportItem id='IIIcd_space' type="StaticReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h2>Other</h2>]]>
        </ReportItem-->
        <!--ReportItemSet id='IIId_head' type="ToggleHeaderReportItemSet" level="4" title="File Attachment" private="true">
            <ReportItem id="IIId" blobType="BLOB_RAW" blobItem="RES_RESACT_FILE" type="UploadReportItem" fileSize="5">
                <![CDATA[You can attach any file to present to the Evaluators to review.  If you want to attach multiple files, then put them in a zip file and attach the zip file.<br />{$item}]]>
            </ReportItem>
        </ReportItemSet-->
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="budget" name="Budget Request" blobSection="RES_BUDGET" tooltip="Budget request and justification" type="EditableReportSection" autosave="true" number="4" renderpdf="true" private="true">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Below find a budget template, which you should download, complete with your funding request for 2014-15 and upload. As with the past year, the amounts you will be allocating to different projects should be listed in different columns.</p>
                <p>Budget Request Caps:
                    <ol type="a">
                        <li>PNI: $65K;</li>
                        <li>CNI: $35K; exception: CNIs who are also co-PLs of Phase2 projects may request up to $45K;</li>
                    </ol>
                    Note: Budget requests that relate to special projects (e.g. SYNTHIUS) do not apply against the caps.<br />
                    <b>Important:</b> You should only request a budget for the Phase2 projects.  If a Phase1 project is included in one of the columns, an error will be shown once the budget is uploaded.  A list of valid projects can be found in the "Project List" worksheet.</p>
                <p>Each PNI is expected to include $2000 in his/her overall budget for the GRAND Annual Conference.</p>
                <h3>Budget Justification</h3>
                <p><i>(Limit: 600 characters)</i></p>
                <p>Please comment on why your funding request is appropriate based on your contributions to the network and your expectations for contributions in the coming year.</p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="budget_just" rows="10" width="100%" limit="600" blobType="BLOB_TEXT" blobItem="RES_BUD_JUSTIF" type="TextareaReportItem">
            <![CDATA[<h3>Budget Justification</h3> {$item}</p>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="budget" blobType="BLOB_EXCEL" blobItem="RES_BUD_BUDGET" type="BudgetReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="review" name="Review" tooltip="Review of on-line report content" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                    <p>This section provides (a) an online document with all the information currently contained in the report pages, and (b) an online approximation of what the resulting PDF document will look like. If you are satisfied with this content, then you can proceed to the final step of the reporting workflow where you can "Submit" your report to be forwarded to the RMC.<br />
Note that there are two distinct differences between the online document that you can see in this page and the PDF document that will be forwarded to the RMC.</p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Over-limit characters are included in the online document, where they are shown in red. These characters will not be included in the PDF document.</li>
                        <li>Section VII, on "Milestones Comments" is not part of the document that will be reviewed by the Research Management Committee (RMC). If there is information here that you want to be considered as part of your evaluation, it should be included in a previous section. Please provide the full details in Section VII - this section will be provided to your project leaders to assist with their project reporting.</li>
                    </ol>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="report_review" type="ReviewReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
    <ReportSection id="submit" name="Submit" tooltip="PDF generation and submission to the RMC" blobSection="SEC_NONE" type="ReportSection" renderpdf="false" private="true">
        <Instructions>
            <![CDATA[
                    <p>To submit your report, follow the following three steps.</p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Generate a new report for submission: this step will generate a PDF document.</li>
                        <li>Download the PDF document for your records.</li>
                        <li>Submit your report: this step indicates that you have read and approve the contents of the PDF document to be forwarded to the RMC. Note that "submitting" does not lock the reporting workflow; you can regenerate and resubmit your report as many times as you wish before the deadline, if you need to make additional edits to your report. The most recently submitted PDF is used for evaluation.  If no PDF has been submitted, then the most recently generated PDF is used for evaluation.</li>
                        <li>Download the PDF which will be used for evaluation; To verify that the correct PDF will be used for evaluation, you can download the submitted PDF.</li>
                    </p>
                    </ol>
                    <p><b>Note: All your PLs have access to your on-line project-specific dashboard rows; your executive summary; your project-specific comments under criteria A B C and D; and your project-specific milestone comments.</b></p>
            ]]>
        </Instructions>
        <ReportItem id="my_progress_head" type="StaticReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[<h3>Report Completion Status</h3><table cellpadding="1" frame="box" rules="all" style="width:600px;">]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="ni_progress_head" type="ProgressReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="my_hqp_progress_head" type="SupervisorProgressReportItem">
            <![CDATA[{$item}]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="dash_progress_head" type="DashboardProgressReportItem" reportType="NIReport">
            <![CDATA[{$item}</table>]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItem id="review" type="ReviewSubmitReportItem" />
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
