<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report pdfFiles="Letters/19" extends="Letters/Base">
    <ReportSection id="letter" title="FEC Preliminary Decision - Application for Promotion to Professor Denied">
        <ReportItem id="body">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This is to inform you that the Faculty Evaluation Committee (FEC) does not support the recommendation of your Department Chair and has made a preliminary decision not to approve your application for promotion to the rank of Professor (preliminary position). Although FEC values your contributions in many areas, the following matters are of concern to the Committee:</p>
                <ul><li>{getText({$report_type}, TABLE, COMMENT, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}</li></ul><br />
                
                You may wish to consider the following options:
                <ul>
                    <li>Pursuant to Article A6.19.3 of Schedule A, I am willing to meet with you during the week of {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)} to discuss your individual case, as it was presented before FEC. Please contact me by email at dean.science@ualberta.ca for an appointment.</li>
                    <li>Pursuant to Article A6.20.1 of Schedule A, you have the right to request reconsideration of FEC's decision by informing me, in writing, within 5 working days from the receipt of this letter.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <p>It is advisable that you consult the Association of Academic Staff University of Alberta (AASUA) for advice.</p>
                
                <p>If you have your case reconsidered by FEC and they stand by their original decision, you have the right to appeal this decision to the General Appeals Committee (GAC) under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A. A request must be made to the Chair of the GAC (Provost, cc’d to Faculty Relations), in writing, within 10 working days from the receipt of the letter confirming FEC's reconsideration decision.</p>
                
                <p>Should you have any procedural questions, please contact the Secretary to FEC, Brigitte Martin, at 780-863-9232 or brigitt2@ualberta.ca.</p>
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
