<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Report pdfFiles="Letters/42" extends="Letters/Base">
    <ReportSection id="letter" title="Incrementation - FEC Reduces Recommendation and Awards 0d">
        <ReportItem id="from">
            <![CDATA[
                FEC Chair
            ]]>
        </ReportItem>
        <ReportItemSet id="bodyset">
            <Static>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>As per Article A6.19.3 of Schedule A, I am informing you that at its meeting of December 2 - 6, the FEC did not support your Department Chair’s recommendation of {getText(RP_CHAIR, FEC_REVIEW, INCREMENT, {$user_id}, 0, 0)} increment. Instead it is prepared to award an incrementation of 0d. The Department Chair continues to support their original recommendation [now supports the preliminary position of FEC]. Under Article A6.19.1 of Schedule A, this is the preliminary position of FEC. This decision was based on the following:</p>
                    <p>{getText({$report_type}, TABLE, COMMENT, {$user_id}, 1, 0)}</p>
                    
                    <p>You may wish to consider the following option:</p>
                    <ul style='margin-left: 1em;'>
                        <li>I am willing to meet with you during the week of {getText({$report_type}, TABLE, FOLLOWUP_DATE, {$user_id}, 1, 0)} to discuss your individual case as it was presented before FEC. Please contact my office at sciea@ualberta.ca for an appointment.</li>
                        <li>As per Article A6.20.1 of Schedule A, you have the right to request reconsideration of the FEC’s preliminary decision by informing me, in writing, within 5 working days from the receipt of this letter.</li>
                    </ul>
                    
                    <p>If you have your case reconsidered by FEC and they stand by their preliminary decision, you have the right to appeal this decision to the General Appeals Committee (GAC) under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A.</p>
                    
                    <p>If you choose not to have your case reconsidered and appear before FEC to present your case or submit documentation in support of your case, the decision will be final and binding. Under Article A8.03.1 of Schedule A, you may not appeal this decision to the GAC.</p>
                ]]>
            </Static>
            <If if="{==({getText({$report_type}, TABLE, 0D, {$user_id}, 1, 0)},Yes)}">
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Since the increment award is 0d and this is the second 0d over the last three years of review, the record will be forwarded to the Provost in accordance with Article A7 of Schedule A if the GAC upholds the FEC decision</p>
                ]]>
            </If>
            <Static>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>It is advisable that you consult the Association of Academic Staff University of Alberta (AASUA).</p>
                    
                    <p>If you have any procedural questions, please contact the FEC Administrator, Lakhan Khara, at sciea@ualberta.ca.</p>
                ]]>
            </Static>
        </ReportItemSet>
    </ReportSection>
</Report>
